Chapter 908: Dead Pit 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“So this is the resonance skill?” Garen stood far off away looking at the man lacking actual combat experience. He was suffering from mental confusion by Cold Chaos and was simply directing his resonance skills against something imaginary.

“Amazing!” For someone who was not particularly good in any aspects to be able to release such powerful strength in an instant just because of the resonance skill, it is pretty unbelievable.

Garen sighed. If it was not for Cold Chaos, he would have suffered at the outbreak of the enemy. Even if he did survive, his Mech would have been corroded or damaged severely.

Moreover, after the resonance skill was stimulated, the white Mech’s speed strength improved by approximately 30%. In addition to the large number of vines which contains highly toxic corrosive effect, his Mech could have…

“Damn, this is no good!!”

Garen was startled. The enemy actually managed to get out from the shackles of the illusion, and as if suddenly teleported in front of him with a huge bunch of vines were swarming towards him.

“What ability is that!!?” Not only did he suddenly shifted in front of his sight, but also escaped the illusion as if the Cold Chaos did not affect him at all.

“Stupid! I may be incompetent, but with the aid of a master within a short distance leap, I am able to kill anyone I want! Hehehe!! Go to hell!!”

The white Pilot seated in the cabin roared. Hanging from his chest was a white, shimmering necklace which was helping to resist against the mental confusion created by the Cold Chaos.

Several thick vines were swarmed towards Garen. Its dark green surface dripped of disgusting, green slime. As the slime made contact with the ground, it rapidly evaporated into a fermented mist.

Chi chi chi!!

Only three swings were yielded from the blade to cut the vines.

Both blades in Garen’s hands broke at the same time, melting into a form of black liquid dripping on the ground.

His body retreated swiftly as a large area of his front external armor was being corroded, exposing strips of his silver skeletal system.

Without his external armor and only left with his skeletal system, Garen’s Mech was at risk of being instantly paralyzed if he was shot by even just an ordinary high-powered ray gun.

“Hahaha!! Too many people have died from this move of mine! Did you really think that I was completely incompetent?” Sinister laughter was heard from the white Mech.

“As expected, New-Moon Level is nothing simple!” Garen finally understood the cruel reality that in order to achieve New-Moon Level Five Resonance, those masters must have experienced a lot of combat. Even the guy in sight right now who seemed harmless had tricks beneath his sleeves.

If any other Level Five Pilot was to be replaced by the move previously, he might have been caught by the vines and his body completely ruined by the corrosion. Even some of the New-Moon Level Resonance Pilots under such ambush might not even be able to use their resonance skills on time before getting themselves killed.

“This guy… trying to be a ringer huh?” At first, Garen thought that the person was just another good-for-nothing young man from a rich family who had been forcefully nurtured. Maybe he was a little talented, but unexpectedly…

“Run! You better keep running, you little pest! I wasted so much time and energy chasing after you! You better run!” The white Mech let out an arrogant laugh.

“With just your ability and you dare to challenge Big Brother Fila, do you really not know how to spell the word death!”

The vines around him danced around madly as if they were turning into a huge monster. From far away, they look like a gigantic vine monster at least ten meters long. Not just was it entirely green, but it was also continuously dripping a large amount of disgusting slime.

“Now, I want you to give me everything you have with you, then kneel on the ground and call me Grandpa thrice. Maybe then I would consider to spare your life.”

The white Mech exclaimed in a frenzy of rage.

“You have a death wish.”

Garen scoffed and threw away his half corroded blade. Straightening his body, he released his Mech’s defense.

“It seems that you really do want to die…bastard!” The white Mech’s voice suddenly turned low and solemn.

“I’m begging you to kill me,” Garen grinned with a hint of mischief. “Please.”

“I asked you to beg me!!”

With a loud rumble, the vines around the white Mech burst once again and expanded twice its original size before darting towards Garen’s direction.

Simultaneously, it flung out massive amounts of green slime everywhere. Even the stones were etched in puddles of black liquid, with white smoke fizzling up.

Just when the white Mech was about to charge towards Garen, something happened…

Ow!!

A humongous black mouth suddenly emerged from the quagmire and grabbed the white Mech at his entire lower body together with the vines.

This mouth was no different than a fish’s. It was black with smooth shiny edges, just that ithere were large, thick tentacles within. The tip of the tentacles actually had suction cups the size of a basin, which pegged the white Mech down tightly.

Springing out all of a sudden, the gigantic fish’s mouth was at least twenty meters wide and had at least hundreds of suction cups sucking onto the white Mech tightly, while making a sharp, sucking sound.

“No…!!! You beast…! No!!!” The white Mech froze for a moment as if it was paralyzed by the beast’s toxins. Motionless, it was just howling in pain.

Snap!

The fish swallowed the white Mech in whole.

Garen who was just watching from the side was shocked and frightened. This was the true Level Five New-Moon Powerhouse! The Mech which almost ruined him just moments ago was entirely vulnerable in the hands of this mutated creature.

Previously, he could also tell that there was something fishy about this quagmire hence attracting the white Mech to go there. However, he did not expect that he would feel a sort of hidden threat during the battling process hence he had intentionally tried to stay away from its murky waters.

His soul intuition told him that this quagmire was definitely dangerous.

And now, a New-Moon Level Mech that he was unable to defeat was just swallowed by a gigantic fish beast in just one gobble.

The gigantic fish had no eyes, just an enormous mouth above the water surface. After biting around for a moment, it retracted back into the quagmire when it did not sense anything else for it to gobble further.

The strange thing was the hole in the quagmire caused by the beast somehow returned to its original form along with its retraction. Large tracts of the quagmire automatically moved from its surrounding and formed a disguise unrecognizable from its previous form.

Garen stood on the edge, his body continued radiating icy Cold Radiation. The frost froze the scent emitting from his Mech. He deduced that this beast mainly relied on scent and breathings to identify its prey, then deliberately reduced its own breathing to the minimum, hoping to lure the arrogant white Mech to step into its trap.

And that was how a tragic incident happened …

“Gee…such misfortune, not even a single bone is left.” After retreating about ten meters back, then only did Garen felt the faint hint of threat slowly disappearing.

“The Radiation Belt really is full of danger. This has got to be the first time I witnessed a terrifying mutated beast strong enough to threaten a Pilot.”

Heaving a sigh of relief, Garen turned around and flew towards the direction of the Flying Batoid City.

Shortly after he left, a black shadow fell from the clouds above, surveyed the quagmire area and then looked towards the direction of where Garen was heading.

“He is no doubt the gifted student who is much taken care of by Professor Van Doe, not even once did he need me to help or interfere along the way,” the black shadow said lightly. “Even though he was still a student, he actually managed to deal with the White Light Elite Army Powerhouse. What are these children nowadays?”

The enemies faced by Nonosiva and Anda were beyond the range of the academy’s usuals, almost like the Three Marshals and One Star, nearing the cruel reality of the adults’ world.

Within the academy, perhaps a New-Moon Level Five Pilot would make the top class of the human chain already. However outside the academy, although such level Pilots were uncommon, they were not rare. After all, the students’ time of growth were at maximum a fraction of the others, sometimes even one-tenth or one-fifth. With such a gap, a lack of power could not be simply made up by just talent or hard work.

As one of the geniuses respected by Black Flood, how could he simply roam around without any extra security? Even Garen managed to work this out, and was not concerned for his safety, which was also why he seemed to be calm and collected the whole time.

“If no trouble lies ahead, it is time to send a message to the professor,” the shadow muttered. He leaped back into the sky and ejected blue flames from his back, flying into the distance and disappeared among the grassland margin in a blink of an eye.

************

“Who else!?”

Blackboard Academy, right in front of the central teaching block.

The huge courtyard was filled with nearly hundreds of people from other academies, standing across crowd were a group of girls. Nobody in the crowd spoke a word.

Lying in front of Leanna was a man’s charred body. He was not dead, but his body’s Willpower had nearly deteriorated by half. This was the consequence of accepting a quick gunfight challenge with Leanna.

“Blackboard Academy, also known as the most brutal, dark academy. It seems that it is only so.” A girl standing beside Leanna sneered out loud and laughed.

“Where is your so-called strongest Three Marshals and One Star? Come out, stop using such garbage to drag time,” Leanna commented lightly as she loosened her wrist joints.

Buzz…

The students around now only realized that these girls were not joking, and were really challenging the elite of Blackboard Academy – the small Three Marshals and One Star.

The infamous rapid gun, Leanna of Maria Academy, was just a nobody before this. But right here, right now, this was the stage for her talent to bloom.

This girl is actually using Blackboard Academy as a stepping stone for her to shine!

“Small Three Marshals and One Star had been known as the strongest of the younger generation. Who knew someone would actually stand out to challenge them?” An unknown sharp voice sounded from the crowd.

Leanna’s mouth slightly curved upwards, only she herself knew what her true intention was. She purposely picked a time where Three Marshals and One Star were away from the academy and came to challenge them just to make herself known.

The first one who voiced out among the crowd was actually a student from Blackboard Academy whom she just bought off.

Three Marshals and One Star were the strongest presence known in Blackboard. Ranking forefront, they were no doubt the most powerful beings in the academy. Ranked first was naturally Diofie, nicknamed Black Star, who was also the main support of Blackboard Academy in the future, followed by three parallels, Red-Eyed Medero, Karfi and Narisiss.

The four of them were collectively known as Blackboard Academy’s Three Marshals and One Star. As to the small Three Marshals and One Star, those were just the recent rise of new powerhouses over the years but they were nothing compared to these four people. As for the others? The ones ranked behind like Britney, Fila, and others, they would not even appear on such occasions. They were not just princesses at a higher status, they also had connections so there was no way they would exert deadly forces just for Blackboard’s sake. However, even given a shot, Leanna would not be afraid. Her true target this time around was actually Britney, the fourth rank star…

Chapter 909: Return 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“People from the Maria Region dare to be this arrogant?”

An army of black Mechs flew across the sky. A few of them descended slowly, suspending in the air right above the teaching block, overlooking below.

The one that spoke was a Mech with two curved horns attached to its chest.

“Who are you?! Get down here!”

Leanna looked up, two rays of electrical light shot out from her eyes with a bang. The blue electrical lights with rolls of thunder shot towards the Mechs in the air.

At the same time, the men in the sky released a black fog-like Willpower Mist Force which was fiercely sweeping downwards.

As the blue electrical light came into contact with the black mist, an electrical light followed by a shutter sound broke through the blanket of darkness, hitting the surface of the black body. Its Pilot let out a painful howl as it took a few steps back.

“Stupid,” a look of underestimation flashed through her eyes. “Do they think they can just rely on a Mech booster?”

“Right! The Blackboard Region is getting less and less advanced nowadays, using Mech boosters when they can’t guarantee a winning fight. If this is the case, we might as well drive our bodies over for a battle. Three Marshals and One Star, they’re just alright,” a woman behind Leanna grunted loudly.

“You bitch!!” The black body could not suppress its anger and roared. He was very pissed. Not only was he being shot at while driving a body, but he was shot by a woman in front of a huge crowd!

“Calm down, Jack! She’s targeting the people of Blue Narcissus. Just observe quietly.” Just as Jack was about to attack back, a tremendous power from behind held him down instantly.

Leanna sneered.

“I will be here waiting for three days. If your so-called small Three Marshals and One Star don’t show up by then, I’ll know that I’ve witnessed Blackboard’s so-called elites…”

She turned to lead the way towards the dormitory area with the other women quickly keeping up behind her. No one dared to step in their way and they soon disappeared into the crowd.

“Let’s go!”

The black Mechs continued to soar in the sky, flying in the direction of the Inner Courtyard.

Inside the main teaching block, there was a huge French window in the middle of the room.

Several masters were observing the commotion beneath them.

“Not bad, Maria Region is producing more and more outstanding disciples. It seems that they are progressing pretty well.” A bearded middle-aged man commented with a smile.

“Just right to give these lazy kids some motivation to work hard instead of constantly thinking that they’re the top elites, maybe all they need is a trigger.” Another plump middle-aged woman nodded. “So long they grasp well to a certain degree and do not go over the line.”

“That young lady has probably reached Half-Moon Level already and she’s only thirty years old. How young,” another master muttered.

“She’s the daughter of the Maria Region’s King. Besides her illustrious background and abundant resources, she also has talent. For her to be able to reach this level is not surprising at all.”

“Notify all the chiefs to hand up a list of outstanding students from each department. We shall pick suitable candidates to fight this young lady,” the middle-aged woman instructed.

“Understood.”

“The candidates must be strong. Those slightly weaker ones might be ruined if they are unable to endure through it all. Uh, this kid sure knows how to pick the right time. The elites are all out?”

The middle-aged woman was silent, as she remembered the Three Marshals and One Star were all out on quests.

“I shall go report to the Vice-Chancellor now.” A master turned and walked out of the room. There was only one president in the Outer Courtyard who is also the Dean. In reality, the Chancellor did not have much matter to worry about whereas the other vice president was the one managing the academy issues.

Soon, offices from other teaching blocks had received the notice from the Vice-Chancellor to assign elite students from each department to accept Leanna’s challenge.

Inside an office full of mahogany furniture, two men let out continuous sighs as they chatted. One was leaning against the mahogany desk, the other seated on a leather chair behind the desk, both of them wearing the same bitter expressions on their face.

“My department, Supporting Combat department, won’t be able to make it. Their average level of Willpower is weaker than the Main Battle department by another level. It’s up to you, Ansader.” The one standing said helplessly.

“I have no way either,” Ansader was the chief of the War Machinery department, also mainly responsible for the mobilization of the department. “Besides the Boot System, don’t we still have the Field Battle department and the Specialty Department? No way we’re bearing all these right?”

He too observed what just happened outside the window, a Half-Moon Level Five Resonance Degree. This level was considered elite in the Inner Courtyard already. How was he supposed to find someone suitable from his department?

“Didn’t you recommend a few prodigies to the academy every year? Filter through the ones who got admitted and shortlist the few exceptional ones,” the man standing by the side asked.

He dropped by on purpose to find potential students to represent the Supporting Combat department for the upcoming challenge so they won’t lose too badly. He did not have any other plans as the kids over at the Supporting Combat department simply would not have stood a chance against the power of Willpower. 99 percent of the students could not even build an Exclusive Mech, let alone achieving Half-Moon Level resonance degree. If they can’t even reach Level Five Willpower, needless to say, resonance degree is pretty much impossible to achieve.

Majority of the Pilot students generally waited until they graduate and earn money before building their own bodies, then producing resonance degree.

“I do recommend people but it’s not easy to find someone at Half-Moon Level Five!” Ansader let out a wry smile with his hands spread open. “Those few who achieved Half-Moon Levels in the academy’s Inner Courtyard are either out on quests or not in the academy, so tell me where do I go look for such people?”

“Well, the Chancellor had already let the word out that every department in the academy must nominate at least two students. The seniors won’t do as Leanna is a neo-human student, and is one of the top five outstanding prodigies of the Maria Academy. If we dispatch the seniors, it wouldn’t matter even if we win,” the standing master said.

“That is to say so.” Ansader was getting frustrated as he rubbed his temples. “Students of the Half-Moon Level can’t be old either, how are we going to find someone suitable!”

Both of them were very well aware that within the whole of Blackboard, the ones who reached Half-Moon Level were just a handful of people. Ranking behind the Three Marshals and One Star were Britney, Fila, and the others. Of course, they had already graduated. However, the ones who were currently active on duty were Medero, Karfi and Narisiss. The three of them were actually old already but they had special reasons as to why they still stayed in the standings.

“I’m getting a headache from this… did the three parties of the academy respond?” He looked up and asked.

“Among the three parties, the Black Star Party is keeping quiet; the Black Rain party led by Medero and the others would probably send their backup Black Rain team to take action, it’s just a matter of sending who.” The man heaved a sigh before replying.

In fact, both of them knew that within the whole of Blackboard, the ones who managed to reach Half-Moon Level Five were truly just a handful of people. After the Black Star, it was Medero, Karfi and Narisiss, then Britney, Fila and Leila. These people were the pillars of strength for Blackboard. The first four were known as the Three Marshals and One Star by the outside world, whereas the three at the back were star students who were highly sought after by countless other academies. They were truly the only ones above Half-Moon Level Five.

“Where did this Leanna come from? How is it that I’ve never heard about her before today…” Ansader sank into deep thought.

“Nevermind, someone notified Britney already…” the master standing at the side frowned while taking a look at his watch displaying the clear message.

“Who informed her? Isn’t she holidaying in South Sea? How is she able to return so soon with such short notice?” Ansadar frowned and asked.

“It was intentional.”

“It should be directed at her alone,” Ansader nodded in agreement.

Both of them felt a sense of premeditated atmosphere in the air.

“This is troublesome… Blue Narcissus has never been known for its combat skills,” Ansader commented softly.

Both of them stood up and went to the French window. Far away, multiple blue airships were moving in the direction of the entrance of the Inner Courtyard.

******************

Radiation Belt, Flying Batoid City

Floating across the calm quiet sky of the Flying Batoid City were gigantic flying batoids. These creatures with fan-like wings would constantly let out a long cattle roar.

The huge black trees stood high like forts on the mountain, with lights flickering from the people’s homes.

Below the grey town was a green farmland with its crops swaying gently in the breeze. The crops were bizarre looking, and at the top of it was an extraordinarily, fat green maggot which seemed like it was squirming once in a while.

Garen’s tattered body flew from a distance, suspending over the town and slowly descend once he reached the city’s main gate.

“Lord!” Two teams came swarming towards Garen. Vendant who hosted Garen the previous time reappeared, “Lord, you are back! Where are the other masters?”

He took a step forward and gave Garen a respectful bow.

“Don’t ask questions that you should not be asking. Get me a new armor for my Mech.” Exhausted, Garen exited the body. After rushing back without stopping for any breaks and constantly on the watch throughout the way, he was tired.

“Nobody is allowed to open the cabin. If anything goes wrong, you will not be able to afford to bear the consequences! Don’t say I didn’t warn you!” The knowledge ores were likely to melt if he cabin is opened and exposed to the temperature outside.

“Yes, yes, yes!” Vendant acknowledged hurriedly. With a wave of his hand, he motioned the men behind him to search for a tractor to drag the body into another garage.

Truth be told, Garen was not worried about sombody opening the body’s cabin and ruining the knowledge ores. After all, nobody dared to disobey his command as this area was close by to the Blackboard Region and there were plenty of Blackboard Pilots patrolling around.

Moreover, the difference in strength between both sides is very large. People from the White Light would not dare to enter this area so if the people here promised not to open the cabin, they would definitely not do so.

Led by Vendant, Garen entered the city once again. This time around, he opted for a quiet, comfortable place to just sleep instead of his usual choice of entertainment.

When he woke up, Little Bitch was already resting beside him naked.

“Hu…”

He groggily chose a place groggily last night to sleep. Sitting up, he surveyed his surroundings. The bedroom was clean and neat with a low radiation count. Every corner of the room was spotless and it was obvious the room was well kept.

Bright rays of sunlight shone in and the crisp sound of birds chirping could be heard. This was considered rare in the region since it had been a long time the region had birds.

“You are awake?” Little Bitch also woke up around the same time, hazily straightening her frame.

“Go back to sleep,” said Garen. He got down from the bed and walked out of the bedroom. He was still dressed in his radiation suit so he did not need a jacket.

The small yard outside had a lot of green plants that looked very good.

“Oh, you’re awake. Did you have a good night’s sleep?” Anda was seated in the middle of the yard by a small stone table. He had a tablet in his hands, which was playing a TV series showing a man and a woman hugging each other and crying. It was obviously one of those old-school TV plots where one of them was diagnosed with cancer.

Garen walked over to sit beside him. Picking up the drink on the table, he poured it into the filter pipe of the radiation suit.

“When did you come back?”

“Yesterday. Actually, you arrived just two hours earlier than me.” Anda smiled, “I say, you are so insensitive. You said you will ditch me and you did just that. If it wasn’t for my little tricks, I would have been crippled already just because of the psycho. Then we met the lunatics, you said run and you really did ran.”

“Isn’t singling one by one out not good? Look at us, our limbs are still intact,” Garen laughed.

“So how was it?” Anda inched nearer and asked mysteriously.

“How what? Don’t come any closer.” Garen swiftly distanced himself away from Anda. After experiencing such a life-death experience, they could get along much better now.

“Stop pretending, you definitely took more stash than me!” Anda cried out loud. The calm and mature composure seen in this guy from the beginning was gone, and all that was left was his thick-skinned attitude.

“What are you planning to do?” Garen pondered for a moment and asked.

Chapter 910: Return 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Me? I just don’t want to always be on the run, constantly chased by people who want to kill me. I’m just going to settle with building Exclusive Mechs this time with my return. I have already found a processing laboratory and most of the materials, in addition to the stash this time around, I should be able to build a pretty decent body,” Anda explained proudly.

Garen nodded. This bastard really was not bad. If it was not for him, they would not have been able to find where the Mastery Energy Ores were hidden. Come to think of it, Anda was the reason he was able to receive so many benefits. However, listening to the tone of the bastard right this moment, it was clear that he was as experienced as a hunting dog.

At the thought of that, Garen’s expression turned serious and solemn.

“If you ever need any help with other quests like this, feel free to find me and I will try my best if it is within my capability!”

Anda immediately gave him a look of despise.

Actually, the only reason why the both of them got along harmoniously was that they were the same kind of people. Life and death meant nothing to them and they had strong wills, not something an ordinary Pilot was able to relate to.

“To be honest I am still being hunted by my family, and you had offended Fila and the bunch of people. From the look of it, they seem to be related to White Light. You have bigger problems than me, man,” Anda sneered. “The psycho probably came for you, while I was just unlucky enough to be dragged into this mess.”

“Forget about it then!” Garen was speechless. Honestly, he also did not want to be on the run anymore. Now that he was in possession of the Mastery Energy Ores, Blood Silver, and with the materials for the body prepared by Master Fila, he just needed to go back to construct most of the plane’s body. The only thing lacking this moment were the engine skills and materials for the skeletal system.

The energy machinist’s biochemical pool was just right in radiation belt. The Flying Batoid City acted as the largest pool in the radiation belt to have sufficient materials for a biochemical pool, especially the one needed by most — the Stony Heart Cells.

“My body still lacks a proper sensory system and there’s nothing much to do here already, so I’m planning to return to finish up and return to the region in the afternoon. What about you?” Anda asked.

“I still need engine skills and skeletal materials. I will go to the marketplace this afternoon to get some radiation materials, then return after taking care of some other things. No rush at all,” Garen shook his head.

Anda murmured in thought.

“Although we failed the quest this time, we should be satisfied with what we managed to get. The engine skills can be bought, but in terms of materials, more specifically, the materials to construct the skeletal system, I am still missing parts that are needed for the joint. These parts are rare, but I might have a way to get them. Just tell me when the body is finished, we can do a bulk order so it would be cheaper.”

“My goodness, bulk order…” Garen was speechless once again. As elites of the Inner Courtyard, they could exchange technology and materials with their masters. If it was something difficult even for them to acquire, naturally it was harder for the outsiders. Yet Anda even has the nerve to bring up ordering it in bulk as if it was something common.

“Consider it settled then! This is my personal secret connection’s password. Just contact me if you need anything!” Anda gave Garen his contact.

Both of them stood up. Looking at Anda leaving hurriedly, Garen could not help but feel relieved. Although the mission was unsuccessful, the purpose was still achieved indirectly. With a sufficient supply of Blood Silver and Mastery Energy Ores, it was enough for him to create the costly Pilot biochemical pool. With the amount of radiation materials collected, he should be able to create something of excellent quality.

This time, the search for Blood Silver was ridden with all sorts of trouble. It was definitely getting messier outside. The friction between the regions was worsening by the day. Even Level Five powerhouses like them could barely make it back. It was no wonder nobody volunteered to step out the radiation belt.

Just as these thoughts surfaced, Garen could hear the sound of a body’s engine flying overhead. It were three black Mechs slowly flying towards the Flying Batoid City’s landing point. Each of them had a clear Blackboard logo and a large white ‘V’ printed on its side, indicating that they are from the Blackboard region — not from the Blackboard Academy but from other academies.

**********************

The three white-V Mechs touched down slowly. Each Mech was holding a blue triangular shield, and carrying a white sword on its back military-style.

“This is the Flying Batoid City. Both of you must be extremely careful during this trip! Understand?” One of the Mechs said coldly, it was actually a young girl.

“Yes, we understand, big sister.” The other two Mechs quickly responded.

The staff from the Flying Batoid City walked up and received them. They started to clean the three Mechs by removing the excess radiation from their armor and painting the spots which got 6chipped off.

The cabins of the three Mechs opened, and out walked two men and a lady. They were all dressed in blue and white striped radiation suits, their face mask was completely transparent. At first glance, it resembled a space suit and you could see the person’s entire face in it.

“Master Vecil, welcome to the Flying Batoid City once again!” A fat man who literally rolled his way in greeted them with a grinning face.

“Enough, I am not in the mood to exchange courtesies. Just arrange our rooms for us to rest,” the woman-in-charge answered in an icy tone.

“Yes, yes, yes.”

Vecil and the duo turned to go but then noticed a black Mech parked in an open space not far away. The Mech’s body was barely recognizable, its armor seemed ruined by a corrosive substance. If it was not the fact that the shape still resembled a Blackboard Mech, it would have been probably been scrapped off.

“Such a body damaged to this extent yet still wanting to fix it? Is this some sort of a joke?” The woman commented scornfully as she turned to exit the hangar.

“Yes, yes, yes, what Master said is…” The fat man agreed repeatedly.

“Huh? Wait, Big Sister!” A young looking teenager among the trio suddenly called out to Vecil who was leading the group. When he looked back inadvertently just now, he actually saw that the broken Mech was exposing some sort of skeletal material that was seemingly better than their body’s material.

“What is it?” Vecil looked back impatiently.

The young boy pointed towards the smashed body with a flicker of surprise in his eyes.

“Big sister, that Mech’s skeletal system…” He lowered his voice intentionally.

Just as he pointed out, the other two only realized what stood out. Even though damaged, the Mech’s skeletal system’s material was actually still much better than theirs! The silver white emitted a faint glow of blue – it was obviously coated with an expensive blue gel which could only be seen in Mechs above average. Generally, such materials were difficult to be found in the market. If you had no special connections, there was no way you would be able to snag it.

Vecil also noticed something abnormal about the Mech and her eyes turned bigger.

“That set of broken body looks just exactly like that one we dragged in the last time we were out…how did it end up here!?” She whispered harshly.

“This…” The little fat man did not know anything about this. He and Vendant just minded their own business. They do not maintain a good relationship, and they both don’t even communicate with each other. “I’m not really sure…”

“I will go to check and see. Thank you for helping me to keep this garbage when I dragged it back earlier on. This time around, I’ll drag it back along with me.” Vecil gave a satisfied smile, “I will give you exactly the skills you requested for.”

The trio strolled casually towards the broken black Mech. As they were nearing it, the three of them realized that this destroyed Mech actually used materials comparable to the military’s finest grade. Whether it was the bones, the Willpower transmission tube, or the sensors at each assembled part, everything was specially picked out.

Vecil was getting more satisfied as the minutes passed.

“Come!” She shouted.

“Here, here, here…” The little fat man and a few other maintenance staff ran over straight away.

“Remove these sensors and the Willpower transmission tube from the top, then install it on our body. I can’t believe, the garbage we dragged back last time actually had good parts,” Vecil said with contentment.

Soon, a few of the maintenance staff removed the parts from the black body and fixed them onto the blue body.

“I’ll go have a look!”

The young man beside her pounced at the direction of the elevator platform excitedly, who was then lifted and sent in front of the cabin.

“Open the cabin!” Vecil ordered.

“Big sister, something is weird! There’s air-conditioning in the cabin!” The young man exclaimed loudly.

“Ah?” Vecil scowled. She followed suit and leaped up several meters high, landing on the elevator platform. She looked in through the surface of the transparent armor.

A subordinate beside the little fat man mumbled into his ears.

“Boss, this body was brought in by Vendant and he ordered that the cabin must not be opened. Maybe you should say something?”

“My ass! Ignore him! We should do according to what Master Vecil says! If we end up angering her, she would be unhappy and you know the consequences!” The little fat man’s face was dark.

“But…” The subordinate wanted to say something but was interrupted by the little fat man.

“How long will it take for you to go find Vendant now? Ten minutes? Twenty minutes? Even if you notified him through the communication device and ask him to come over, what if he stirred things up and cause trouble? Can you afford to bear the consequences?” The little fat man sneered.

Frightened and sweating in fear, the subordinate nodded his head.

“You have to understand, Master Vecil is one of the important VIP in this city! You must not delay her wants and needs!”

At this very moment, Vecil and the other man were standing in front of the cockpit and looking inside.

Vecil’s heart was pounding faster by the second. Through the glass and the white frost, she saw stacks of blue-white dense metal blocks. The blocks were shiny and seemed like they were processed by a factory machine.

“This…this is…is this…!!” She suddenly felt as if a huge chunk of pie fell from the sky and hit her hard. She couldn’t help but feel delirious with joy.

Yes, those were the legendary Mastery Energy Ores that only Pilots could use! One block of that could easily trade for thousands and millions!

After repeatedly confirming her findings, an irrepressible ecstasy from within caused her to smile twistedly. It was a result of her trying to suppress her facial expressions, an absolute contrast to the amount of joy flooding her.

“Let’s go! We must leave the region right away!!” A crazy idea formed in her mind. “As long as we get hold of all these, I will never to worry about my entire life anymore! There will be endless of wealth for me!!”

Vecil’s body was shaking.

They must immediately get their hands on this large fortune. Vecil only had this one thought in mind. To her, nothing else mattered anymore.

Drive the body and leave immediately!!

Chapter 911: Settle

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What! Is someone making a move on Sir Garen’s Mech?!!”

In a pub somewhere in Flying Batoid City, Vendant expression changed drastically as he pushed away the beautiful woman at his side and stood up in shock.

“Didn’t I tell you guys to not let anyone know that Sir Garen’s Mech Body is under repair?!” Vendant felt a chill rushing to the back of his mind. His back was soaked in cold sweat.

The expression on Sir Garen’s face when he instructed him was very clear how important that Mech was. This was the body that a Blackboard Academy’s elite pilot regarded with high importance!

If anything happened, 10,000 of his lives were not even be enough to appease Sir Garen!!

Vendant’s shocked expression also affected the subordinate who reported to him. His face paled too as he did not expect the consequences would be so serious. Looking at Vendant’s face, it seemed as though the sky was about to fall!

Vendant paced back and forth in a corner of the pub.

“Notify the City Master immediately! I will assemble the miniature Mech team!” Vendant was decisive and immediately instructed his subordinate to contact the leader of Flying Batoid City.

“But…there’s…there’s still Master Vecil…”

“Damn your but!!!” Vendant kicked his subordinate mercilessly. “If he is enraged, even Vecil will die!!”

He roared loudly and bolted out of the pub, running towards Garen’s dwelling.

*****************

At the courtyard, Garen was quietly practicing what was once the most basic set of secret technique. It looked ordinary and does not seem to be different than those which was generally practiced for wellbeing purposes. However, as he moved around slowly, a faint flow of air around him started to gather and pick up speed.

It was very tranquil in the peaceful Flying Batoid City. The people here were satisfied as long as there was enough food in this radiation belt. What they yearned for was to live a life inside the regions but due to the radiation, they could never return to the region ever again. The only possible exception was their children.

Children born from radioactive people had a chance of not having any radioactive sickness. These babies appeared to produce some kind of antibody due to their radioactive parents, causing them to be immune to certain radiation sickness.

It is the parents’ greatest hope that the people from the region would select their children. Henceforth, their children would soared high with their ambitions and became part of the region’s people.

This was why there were always a lot of people gathering outside the courtyard where Garen was staying. Even with the guards, people still crowd around and most of them were young parents with their children. Some of the children seem be newborns, whereas some were a few years old. There were even children around the age of 11 or 12 who were brought there. Surprisingly, the children had no traces of radiation on them.

These people looked on hopefully at Garen in the courtyard. They hoped that Garen would take a liking to their children. Those who were immune to radiation also had naturally good talent. Training their Willpower would generally yield positive results.

However, even if that was the case, the radioactive people were commonly discriminated against. Adding on to that, those who were able to bring people inside the regions all had very strong background with pilots. That was why the last time Garen and the others were here, these people did not gather around.

But it was different this time. The people found out Garen and the others’ identities from the guards.

The inner court elites of the Blackboard Academy!!

The Blackboard Academy’s name itself was already an awe. 99 percent of the students who gathered there were children of the wealthy and powerful. They all come from strong backgrounds and forces, which helps to add on to their identity as Mech pilots. Although most people would not understand what does ‘inner court’ means, but they at least understood the meaning of elite.

Noble status, elite Mech pilot. Subconsciously, they all started to form such an impression on Garen.

“Sir!! Sir!!!”

Just then, a guard riding a black horse-like creature from afar rushed down the streets, knocking down a lot of people in the process while crying out loud.

The door of the courtyard that Garen was in was actually opened. In fact, he did have the intention of picking a few of these kids and bringing them into the region. He noted a few of those who are talented when they were practicing secret techniques. It was sad to know that these talented ones were not noticed, and learning more from the guards, some of them who were more than 10 years of age also missed the chance the previous two times when a pilot was there. What a pity.

Most importantly, the children here have lots of life experience, and even though they were young at age, they are all very matured and sensible. They knew how to read people’s expressions and moods and were street smart. They could be treated as adults even if they were to be brought into the region. For him who lacked confidants, they could be his subordinates.

Hearing the guard’s cries and rushing in, Garen frowned and stopped his practice.

“What’s the matter?”

The guard rushed down from his ride and panted heavily. He rushed up to Garen and whispered in his ears.

Garen’s expression changed.

“Let’s go!! Bring me there!”

He pulled up the guard and strode out the courtyard.

*****************

Inside the Mech Maintenance Hangar

Vecil had somebody to tie the black Mech to her Body. The cockpit of the black Mech was so cold that she could not endure for long with her physique. However, if the Mastery Energy Ore was cooled, it was likely to release high temperature and melt down. In order to avoid any accident, Veci decide to tie the black Mech to her own Mech.

She was instructing the worker to use the semi-automatic robotic arm to firmly tie the two bodies together.

Soon, both Mechs were bounded tightly.

“Let’s get out of here now!!” Vecil glanced at both of her companions and winked.

Both of them could not keep the the smile off their faces any longer. After knowing that there were so much Master Energy Ores, their whole world was shaking as if a huge pie dropped out of the sky. It took them awhile to react to their findings.

The three of them split up and went to their respective Mechs.

Under Vecil’s orders, the little fat man and the others were nervously keeping a look out so that no one could enter.

“Wait!!!”

Suddenly, a loud growl came from the hangar’s entrance.

It was Vendant at the slope of the entrance gate of the underground hangar. He bolted in angrily and was unsteady on his feet and fell. He picked himself up quickly and continued to run towards Vecil and the others.

“Master Vecil!! You cannot touch that Mech!!!” He shouted as he ran faster. His voice was hoarse from his shoutings, and he sounded as if his mother has passed away.

“What? I cannot touch?” Veci was surprised.

“That Mech belonged to somebody important from the Blackboard Academy!! You must not touch it under any circumstances! Or else the whole Flying Batoid City will be in trouble!!!” Vendant roared loudly as he ran.

“Blackboard Academy’s Mech?” Veci’s heart shook. Her academy was ranked third, naturally she knew how terrifying the number one Blackboard Academy was inside the region. If there were 100 elite pilots, then 80 of them must be from Blackboard.

“What do we do now, Big Sister!?” The young boy was also nervous. He was just still living his fantasy moment but now he was panicking. Robbing a Blackboard Academy’s Mech inside the Blackboard Region, needless to say, it was definitely a capital punishment!

“What Blackboard Mech!! Trying to scare me! Don’t even think about it! Let’s go!” Veci suddenly roared. “How could it be so coincident? We met a Blackboard’s pilot going through their maintenance the moment we go out? We can’t even f****** meet a few pilots in Flying Batoid City in a year!! It must be fake!”

She turned around and rushed into her cockpit even faster. As long as she got into the cockpit and started the Mech, not even a Level Five pilot could catch up with her Level Four Mech at their own speed. Without a body, the difference in speed between a pilot and a Mech on the same level was vast.

Her two companions also came to a realization that with this wealth, even if they could not stay in Blackboard Region, they could still live as they like at Maria Region or Royal Region! There was no need to care about Blackboard Region!

After hearing Vendant’s words, they ran even faster.

Chasing from the back, Vendant wanted to cry but there were no tears. For the sake of confidentiality, he did not tell anyone that Sir Garen’s Mech was being maintained here. This was also Sir Garen’s orders. He never thought that V Academy’s Vecil and two others would be blinded by their greed. This was truly uncalled for.

He thought that the moment he yelled out Blackboard’s name, those three would stop. He never expected that they would actually be more decisive and ran away faster. They were obviously planning to escape with the things they robbed!

Seeing the three of them were fast approaching the lift platform, Vendant knew he had to make a choice. Whatever the stuffs are that made these three pilots so greedy to the point that they are willing to forsake everything, it must be extremely valuable and priceless. Needless to say, even if he sold off his whole family up to his ancestors, he may not even still be able to compensate for the losses. And for somebody with such riches…there was no need to even think, his status is surely higher than the City Master!

If they really managed to escape with the valuable items…not only his whole family will die, all the people here and those related to them would get convicted and killed off by the City Master!

Vendant roared again, waking up all the maintenance workers and the little fat man to their sense. “Do not let them get away! Otherwise it will be genocide for us all!!”

At this moment, the little fat man finally reached his senses. His mouth trembled and he wanted to say something, his heart was beating so fast that he did not know what to say or do.

“Shoot them!!!”

A cold hum resounded throughout the hangar.

Chi Chi Chi!!

Numerous lines of green rays aimed and shot at the three persons who were still running to the lift platform. One of them glared and three, small triangular blue shields floated in mid-air and shielded off the shooting rays.

“Shoot them, shoot them, shoot them!!” The little fat man finally reacted and shouted instructions too. Knowing that he had gotten himself into deep trouble, his complexion was green, and sweat was forming and streaming down his chin and neck non-stop.

All the ray guns used for repairing and maintenance were now directed and shot at the three convicts. Unfortunately, the guns were not powerful enough as they were all used for engineering works and were too short-ranged. Those who were closer managed to shoot but were all blocked by the shields.

The three of them managed to escape into their respective cockpits and close the lids.

“Let’s go!!” Veci shouted.

Chapter 912: Alliance

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Suddenly, the three Mechs soared into the sky and their backs shot out blue flames about one meter long. The thick ropes that were stuck on their bodies snapped off and the sheer force of it caused it to whip two other people. They bled all over their bodies and crashed into the wall before falling to the ground, dead.

The Mechs forced open the ceiling of the hangar before flying out.

Garen who had just arrived at the hangar narrowed his eyes, staring at the middle Mech. His black Mech was precisely tied to its back.

He glanced over the area with his eyes.

Shua!!

He did a series of backflips and left behind vivid after-images and arrived at a huge piece of black metal, one meter thick.

“Up!!” he growled and picked up the piece of metal so easily as if he was uprooting a willow tree before rotating his body like a spinning top.

Amid the sound of wind, the piece of metal let out a shrill sound, hurting the ears of all the people in the hangar.

The spinning top then suddenly stop.

‘Boom!!!’

The sharp end of the black piece of metal was thrown out by Garen like a railgun, straight for the blue Mech that was turning.

Clang! A loud sound was produced.

The metal did not pierce through the Mech’s armor and bounced off.

“Idiot!” Veci was startled inside the Mech but now that she saw this scene, her heart relaxed.

Just as everyone below were disappointed, something changed.

The black Body that was tied to the back of Veci’s Mech suddenly slid and fell. It turned out that the black metallic rope that was tied around her was broken.

Garen’s expression remain unchanged. Looking at the black Body that fell down from the sky, he took a few steps back, giving the Body some distance to land.

With a loud sound, the black Mech crashed down on top of the hangar by the edge of the entrance and then tumbled down through the opening and rolled towards the crowd of people.

Peng!!

Little fatty and the others did not even managed to react before they were crushed into pulp, leaving only traces of flesh and blood on the ground. Blood kept flowing out from under the Mech.

Garen was expressionless. He did not even look at the blood by his feet before slowly walking forward and slipping into the cockpit.

In the sky, Veci saw this scene unfold and was totally dumbfounded. Adding to that, her two companions were as dumbfounded as she was.

He could precisely throw up a piece of metal weighing a hundred kilograms with flesh and blood, accurately smash apart the metallic rope tied around the Mech. Although the armour of the Mech had been tampered with to ensure its toughness was stronger than any normal metal, the metallic rope that was found hastily did not have the same toughness.

“Weng…”

The eyes of the black Mech on the ground lit up. A strong and terrifying aura spead and the Level Five Willpower and Field activated.

The black Mech pushed the ground with both its hands and jumped upwards with its thrusters releasing blue flames behind it while charging towards the three in the sky.

“L-Level Five Pilot!??!!” Veci’s eyes showed traces of fear. “Run!!”

She roared. There was no will to even resist it in her heart so she directly activated the largest output of the thruster and flew away.

The talent of a pilot also had its limits. This talent decided not only the speed but also the upper limit of the the training method.

Those with a normal talent had a limit to their willpower. Even if they spent their lifetime in training, the would only be able to reach a certain level of their own limit, which was Level Four.

Only excellent pilots could reach Level Five in their lifetime and it was the level of those who were instructors and professors in academies.

Veci herself was one of the most outstanding people in the V Academy. She naturally understood what Level Five pilots signified.

The talent of a pilot was the innate limit of the body. The body was like a fixed basin and the amount of water the basin could hold was fixed from birth. Normal people was limited at Level Four and outstanding ones could become Level Five. The world of Level Five pilots were different from normal people. They did not seek wealth, but instead something ethereal like Resonance pilot and Inheriting pilot.

Due to the fact that the limit of a human body was Level Five, only with the help of Exclusive Mech with a resonance degree could they gradually improve their talent and improve even further.

Veci was already thirty years old and was close to graduation but had barely entered the initial stage of Level Four. If she did not earn some money now, she would not be able to enter and exit the radiation belt with the academy’s name. She would also lose the method which would enable her to earn a lot of money.

However, the change that had happened was something she had never thought of.

Without another word, the three Mechas flew away with full power.

“One Level Four and two Level Three. This kind of trash dares to meddle with my Mech?” Garen sat inside the cockpit and moved his Willpower.

Crouched Eagle Talons’ explosive force burst and a circle of white gas bloomed and slowly spread out.

Comparing explosive force in limited range, the Crouched Eagle Talons was comparable to those training methods that were quite good!!

The black Mech became a black line and his standard was a level higher than the other three. Those three Mechs were branded Mech that could be found in the market and was similar to Battlenet’s Mechs, which used civilian technology. Compared to the military’s Blackboard Captain-class Mech, they were inferior and no to mention that Garen himself had a skill that allowed him to speed up his flying.

Garen’s Mech shot out as fast as lightning with both arms open like a large black bird. One of his arms got around the neck of Vici’s Mech and in a flash, he had all three Mechs by their necks in his arm. He mercilessly slammed them down onto the ground which caused a gust of wind to pass.

Peng! Boom!

The three Mechs that were caught in his arms like slices of bread were smashed violently onto the ground, causing the whole Flying Batoid City to tremble.

One of the Mechs who would not bear the impact exploded into flames and fragments, causing the other two Mech pilots that were to scream in panic. Due to the close proximity, both Mechs were greatly damaged and burnt.

“Don’t kill me, I beg you!”

Sounds of cries and screams came from inside Veci’s cockpit. This woman was on the verge of collapse and the moment of greed caused her endless remorse. She had always had a careful attitude, even when she was out in the radiation belt so that she could avoid disaster again. She never thought that one time of greediness could cause such a consequence.

Garen pulled out a sword from the waist of one of the Mechs and stabbed the cockpit of another Mech by his side. A subtle sound came from inside and then blood started flowing along the sword. The armor that was heated up by the explosion then evaporated the blood, which caused a fishy smell and a hissing sound.

While ignoring her pleading cries, Garen tore off the sensor on Veci’s Mech, along with other things he needed like scabbard. Within a flash, the sword in his hand chopped off all four limbs of the blue Mech. The strong armor of the Mech was no different to tofu under his sword skill. This was not the only difference in their Mechs’ specs. Although it was only a common, standard sword, it had transformed into a weapon of God in Garen’s hand. His understanding of the gaps in the Mechs’ Body allowed him to cut through them easily.

“No!!!” Veci seemed to have noticed her end and her body jerked.

Chi!!

The tip of the sword pierced through the cockpit without even a hint of hindrance.

Her voice stopped.

Garen stood up and stowed the blue sword in his hand. This came just in time as both his swords had corroded and now, he had obtained another weapon to use.

Opening the cockpit, he started inspecting the bodies on the pilot. One of them were completely unrecognizable due to the explosion and nothing much remained while the other was penniless and had nothing valuable.

As for Veci’s body, he found a V Academy’s eighth year student card and a silver-white identity card. He brought them both back to his Mech and read the information inside. On the identity card was written something like Namu Clan.

“Such a small clan and yet she dare rob them?” Garen helplessly said.

The Mech went back to the hangar where all the workers had already gathered. With Vendant in the lead, they were all kneeling with their heads hanging down and did not dare move a muscle. There were pieces of debris that had flew and fallen at their side with the edges covered in blood. Vendant and the others’ heads and backs were covered in blood and wounds. Apparently, the debris had fallen on them and caused those injuries.

Other people were gathered at the side with bewildered expressions on their faces.

“Find out who helped those three pilots and get rid of them”, Garen said. The Mech slowly fell and Garen came out of the cockpit and jumped down. He got out of the hangar while ignoring the people who were kneeling. This allowed Vendant and the others to sigh in relief.

In radiation belt, the most worthless thing was human life. They thought they were going to die for sure but did not expect that Garen would spare their lives. If it were other people in the radiation belt, they would have been executed at the first sign. There were too many people that were implicated in genocide due to the failure of important tasks they were in charge of. There would also be people ready to join Flying Batoid City out there.

Garen had not gotten far away from the hangdar before there were cries pleading for mercy. Unexpectedly, just as he returned to his small courtyard, he saw the crowd standing outside, staring at a figure in a black cloak.

All the radioactive people only dared to stay outside the courtyard but this man dared to stand in the middle of it and he seemed to be waiting for Garen to come back. As though sensing his line of eyesight, the man turned around and revealed a face covered by a silver white mask.

“I’ve been waiting for you.”

Chapter 913: Rescue 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Who are you?” The black cloak chuckled.

“Waiting for me?”

Garen froze. He had left Blackboard Academy not long ago as it was under absolute secrecy. Moreover, no one knew of the route and time of his return. So, how did this person find him here?

There was doubt in his mind, so he separated from the crowds and walked over to the man.

“A few days ago, we found some abnormal energy reaction from somewhere in this area”

The man’s purple lips under his cape did not move and yet, his voice passed perfectly into Garen’s ears.

Garen noticed that the crowd around him did not give any attention because no one else heard this person speak.

“We’ll talk more when we get inside,” the man said while he strode into the courtyard. He then waved his hand and the for of the courtyard was instantly shut, blocking the view of the outsiders.

Regarding his Mech, the incident just now was a trivial matter. It would be considered not bad if there were a few people who would come here the whole year long. No pilots in the inner region were willing to come here and take the risk of contracting the radiation disease. Most of them could do other tasks to earn money. Although it may take more time, safety was a priority.

The previous incident of snatching Master Energy Ore was a one in a thousandth percentage.

Garen however, was not worried. His cabin was completely locked and unless someone was a high-level with decrypting talent, they would not be able to open the door unless they move the entire Mech away. However, this was his teacher’s Black Flood Party’s patrolling site. Even if they ran away, he could contact the patrolling powerhouse anything to get it back. Furthermore, White Light’s people would not dare mess around within an area of ten thousand meters.

“There’s no need. Here will do,” the man said as he flung his arm. A black shadow shot out accurately at Garen and his hand caught it.

Garen looked and saw that in his hand, was a pitch-black metal key. It was simple and antique-looking. It looked like any ordinary key that had been used for a long time, except that there were very few notches on its side, only a single tine.

“This is one of the identities of an Energy Machinist. You have succeeded in becoming a Level One Energy Machinist and are eligible to enter the energy trading market”, the black-cloaked man said with a deep tone.

“Energy Machinist?” Garen was surprised. He had never told anyone about his breakthrough to Level One Energy Machinist Willpower. He did not expect the other party to find him that quickly and pass him this so-called key.

“Who are you guys?” Garen asked with narrowed eyes.

“Federation of Energy Machinists. You will understand when you enter the market, but please do not expose the location of the Energy Market even though it will shift once in a while”, the man chuckled.

“Alright, young lad, see you when I see you.”

He flapped his cloak, turned around and headed towards the small garden of the courtyard. As he walked between the flowers, his body started to fade and become increasingly transparent until it completely vanished.

“What means is this!?” Garen was shocked in his mind. He had never seen such a hand even in Secret Technique World and Totem World. As he thought around it, this was the era of great cosmic science and technology and any kind of technology suddenly appearing was not impossible. It could be invisibility or some other kind of powerful skill, no one could know for sure.

“Energy Market…”, holding the key in his hand, Garen felt for the first time that this world was not as simple as he had imagined it to be. Pilots were probably only one of the segments here.

Garen was not very bothered because the other party did not seem to have any bad intentions, so he carefully tucked away the key.

It had been days since Veci and the others of the V Academy had been killed. Garen continued to stay in Flying Batoid City as he waited for the return of the team sent out by City Master to look for Clint and others. At the same time, he was also collecting materials for the making of biochemical pool in Flying Batoid City. The outgoing search party finally returned after seven days and brought some not-so-good news with them.

The whereabouts of Clint and others had been tracked down, but they seemed to be pursued by White Light’s people.

***********

“Pursued?”

Garen sat in his own courtyard. The hand that was flipping the pages of an old book paused momentarily.

“What is the strength of those who are pursuing them?”

The one reporting was Vendant, who still had a white gauze on his face. He bent over to answer.

“We do not know much about their exact strength, but as we observed from a distance, they were at least Level Three elite Mech soldiers. Shining Mech seems to be involved as well.”

“Oh?” Garen was dazed. Shining Mech was the level of the Red-White which he killed off last time in the inner region, Level Five. It also relied on special Mech ability and its capability was very strong. Of course, not all Shining Mech were of Level Five only. There had to be a powerhouse with resonance degree.

But what astounded him was that resonance degree could only be stimulated with an Exclusive Mech. So how did the Shining Mechs coordinate and stimulate it? Was it relayed over to the person to adapt to the Mech’s body?

“What is the situation of the people who were being pursued?”

“Unclear. However, the Shining Mechs were roaming around and should still be searching on a vast scale. It’s very likely that they have not been found yet. Our people dared not to get too close in fear that we might be killed by the other party”, Vendant replied softly.

Garen lightly put down the book in his hands and began to deliberate.

He had to make sure that Baylon was alright before he could bring the news back to his family. After all, he needed to construct the main frame of his Exclusive Mech which meant that he would head back for a long time before being able to come out again. Although not all the materials had been found, some of the less important parts could be bought with Universal Units nonetheless.

“No, no”, a voice suddenly rang in his mind.

“Red Moon?” Garen immediately responded. He waved off Vendant and at the same time, passed him the tech information that City Master needed and let him take it away. It was remuneration for helping him search for the materials of the biochemical pool.

After Vendant had left the courtyard with the others and shut the door, Garen had Little Bitch sit on his lap, reach out his hands and caressed freely while conversing with Red Moon in his mind.

“That’s right. It’s me. Finally, the signal is clear. The radiation interference is too strong.” Red Moon let out a heavy breath. “Looks liked you should be very near to where we are. You must come over right away to rescue them.”

“Rescue them?”

“Clint is dying and Lonnie can’t hold on much longer as well. If you don’t come, they will all die!” Red Moon briefly said.

“What’s the matter? How much longer can they hold out?” Garen’s gaze became serious.

“Three days. If you don’t come, then there really is no hope. I can only cover for them for three more days at the most. My energy is running out”, Red Moon said helplessly. “Lonnie has contracted radiation disease and it’s quite serious. Her whole body has wilted and she has become extremely skinny. Clint is also heavily injured and his wounds are seriously infected. In order to seize some medication to slow down Lonnie’s radiation disease, he…Sigh, you will know when you get here.”

“Specific location”, Garen said with unrest in his voice. He had achieved one of his goals of this trip. As long as they were not dead, with current science and technology means of treatment, they could still be saved.

“I will point out the direction for you! It’s not far from Flying Batoid City, but be careful of White Light’s Shining Mech! They have dispatched many elites in search of the core!” Red Moon said solemnly. “Don’t bring anyone else. Our situation is very dangerous! Whether is it White Light or other people from the region, they are all seeking us!”

Disconnecting, Garen could clearly feel Red Moon’s Willpower leaving rapidly.

Pushing off Little Bitch, he got up, pushed open the door and instructed the two soldiers who were standing guard.

“Prepare for me the anti-injury and anti-radiation drugs. Two standard sets!”

“Yes, sir!” The two guards looked at each other. One of them quickly ran to the medical center in the city. Since all the expenses were reimbursed by City Master Quarters, just recording it directly in the bookkeeping would do.

Soon, two standard medical treatment packages were placed in front of Garen. The small, white, square packages contained anti-inflammatory drugs, large portions of anti-radiation drugs, bactericidal water, gauze tape for dressing, blood test device, some oral medicine and more.

After examining them, Garen took them and headed out of Flying Batoid City alone.

*************

Inside a concealed small cave in the underground hundreds of meter away from Flying Batoid City.

Clint was straining to carry Lonnie’s body and walking deeper into the cave one step at a time.

He had found the anti-radiation medicine, but the amount the Shining Mechs had with them were far too little. Although it was stolen by Red Moon, the dose could only be used to prevent mitigation. It was not much of a help for Lonnie’s condition.

After the two miraculously stole the medicine from the Shining Mechs, in their moment of exhaustion, they finally managed to make one last leap and fled away.

“Almost there. It’s right in front.” Deep in the cave, a dark-skinned girl with many little black braids was walking in front of Clint. She held a fire torch and her body had the obvious odor of radiation disease. In the midst of the burning sound of the torch, it reflected her thin and slender body and face.

It was this girl who had rescued them when Clint had fainted and helped them from being found by White Light’s patrolling searching-soldiers.

“Lola, how much longer to arrival?” Clint did not have a trace of blood on his face. His lips were cracked and his skin was as if it had been soaked in water, white and blistering. It gave off a feeling of puffiness and his entire body had expanded. Some places even appeared swollen and purple.

“Soon, soon. We usually live in the underground of the city. All the people there are those who could not survive on the ground. They are either wanted criminals, or the resisting strength that are being hunted down everywhere”, the girl revealed her white teeth as she turned back and said smilingly.

“Resisting strength? Resist what?” Clint’s voice was a bit hoarse as he asked.

“Of course it is against those who caused us to fall to this point. Regions, each big region, all the people of the region are our target of resistance”, the girl said in a low voice. “Some called us the Underground Rebel Army.”

“Underground Rebel Army?” It was the first time Clint had heard of this term.

“We have been observing you for a long time. The hut where you previously lived in was one of our temporary strongholds. It was our people who planned to rest there but unexpectedly found you two there”, the little girl, Lola, briefly explained. “Then we found out that you are newcomers who have just came out from the region and are being hunted and struck everywhere , and did not even have the awareness of basic self-protection. It was extremely miserable. Even our children are better than you.”

The girl Lola’s words made Clint speechless and his face flushed.

‘Uueehh!’

His throat had a sudden itch and he vomited a mouthful of blood.

Purple blood with tiny black worms that were vaguely seen crawling in it.

“This… This is…” Clint saw that there were actually worms in his blood. His heart instantly became cold and he was terrified. Standing on the spot with his face looking defeated, “Lord… How much longer can I live…?” he asked tremblingly in his heart.

“If all goes well… three hours.” Red Moon paused for a moment before replying in a low voice.

Chapter 914: Rescue 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“These are bloodworms!!” Lola who was in front, heard the commotion and looked back, she was instantly taken aback. Looking down at the blood and spotting the worms, she was so frightened that she immediately took a big step back.

“You!”

She looked up shockingly at Clint and the dry body that he was carrying by his side which looked more like a dead body.

After being parasitized by bloodworms, people could not live for more than five hours. This was common sense in the radiation belt. Thinking of this, Lola looked at the disastrous-looking face of this young man and her heart sank.

“Looks like I’m going to die”, Clint sat down on the floor, too demotivated to continue the journey. He was going to die anyway, continuing the journey or not would end up with the same result.

“I’ll go get you medicine! There is a way for blood filariasis!” Lola gritted her teeth and swiftly ran deep into the cave, but she understood that it would take at least six hours to go to and fro. This amount of time was not enough at all. Furthermore, the medicine for bloodworms was an extremely expensive drug in the Underground Cave Rebel Army.

“I’ll tell uncle. There may be a glimmer of hope!” Lola made up her mind and quickly sped up, running deep into the cave.

Clint sat down at the side of the cave hole and looked up at the surrounding cave walls. There was a faint green light on the wall. It was the only lighting in the cave.

He touched his right rib, where a fist-sized blood-hole wound was. The flesh on the edge had rotted and there were many tiny bloodworms growing there. These black, earthworm-like bugs were constantly worming in and out of the flesh and blood. Yet, Clint did not feel pain because the nerves were already paralyzed.

From the blood hole of this wound, he could even reach in with his hand to touch his internal organs.

The stench that he was emitting was growing stronger.

“This time will really not work…” Clint sat down helplessly. There was deep fear and panic in his eyes, so much so that his voice was trembling.

“Hold on!” Red Moon encouraged. “There is still hope! Believe me!”

“I wonder what my sister is doing…” Clint blankly stared in front of him, but his consciousness had drifted off elsewhere.

He did not even dare to look at his own body because it was so unbearable that it made him contemplate taking his own life.

Lonnie had been in a coma for a long time. Although he had given her radiation drugs, the dose was not strong enough and her situation was still deteriorating. Perhaps it would not take long for her to die like him.

Time went by, minutes and seconds.

*********************

Garen sprinted across the grassland. He had a simple miniature-Mech on him. His body was almost floating on the ground. Every time his feet touched the ground, he had ran approximately seven or eight meters. It was very scary, almost the same as the average Mech’s low-flying speed.

Suddenly, he stopped in his track and dropped onto the edge of a deep pit in the grassland.

This pit was obviously the remnants of a bomb blast. Some fragmentary components of the Blackboard Mech’s body were faintly visible inside. Clearly, there was a confrontation between Blackboard patrols and White Light soldiers.

‘Whirrr…’

A white Mech flew at a low altitude and was rushing towards Garen. Without any inquiries or speech, it gave a slash of the knife, as if to cut Garen into half.

“The hell with you!!” Garen looked up and thrust out a strong Willpower Pierce.

With a loud bang, the white Mech fell to the ground, rolled a few times and there was no more movement.

An ordinary Level Three Mech soldier, even with the Mech’s outer armor, was no opponent to Garen’s single Willpower Pierce. Without reaching Level Five, even with the Mech, one would not be the opponent of Level Five in close range. Once the moves were seen through, a Willpower Pierce within a range of ten meters would end the battle.

Therefore, pilots of Level Five and above were very dangerous. They generally used long-range focused attacks.

The Mech rolled on the ground. Garen approached it and wanted to pull the cabin door open but the door was tough and the switch could not be easily destroyed by him. He could only let it be, so he jumped off the Mech’s body and rushed towards the direction pointed out by Red Moon.

Clint’s death would have a very troublesome effect on him. It would cause him to lose the Willpower.

Fortunately, as he dispelled the nameless Willpower, the Willpower that this imprint could affect would only be Crouched Eagle Talon. It would not have any effect towards the Energy Machinist Willpower that was acquired later on.

Obviously, this imprint was aimed at the previously accumulated Willpower. But for the part that was completely re-cultivate later, there was no way to implicate it.

“That is, if I completely break off the connection with Red Moon and destroy the last layer of the nameless Willpower, then the imprint will be destroyed and the Level Four Crouched Eagle Talon will be affected and completely destroyed as well, leaving only the residual remains of Level One.”

Garen thought about it while dashing. He was not one to be controlled by others.

“For other people, this loss is huge, but for me, it is not a big issue. As long as there is potential, re-cultivating is not a big problem!”

“It’s just that this connection with Forbidden core may be useful in the future. It’s a pity if it’s broken”

He made up his mind that this imprint could serve as the key to connecting with Red Moon. Clint and the group did not look like they would easily die off. Red Moon, this mysterious Forbidden Core, was definitely not a simple character and might be of great use later on.

Unconsciously, the location that was established with Red Moon gradually appeared in his field of vision.

Suddenly, Garen made a leap and easily hid in a grassland radiation ditch by the side. He laid flat on his body and soaked his entire body in the ditch, masking the temperature and the color of the miniature-Mech.

Three White Light soldiers roared past overhead and held a rifle-like weapon in their hands.

Two of them had two horizontal lines engraved on them while the other only had one. Judging by the Mech’s Willpower force field, it was apparent that they were two Level Two soldiers and one Level One soldier.

After waiting for the three Mech soldiers to fly away, Garen jumped up and rushed forward with a spray of water.

Very quickly, he evaded the White Light patrolling soldiers a few more times and finally came to the location where Red Moon had pointed out.

Opening a camouflage mud-board on the ground, the deep black tunnel below was exposed. Garen jumped into it and closed the lid with a backhand.

The moment he hid inside, Garen felt the horrifying vibration of Willpower exploding on the ground outside.

The ground shook violently, like an earthquake.

“This is…!!??” Garen hid in the ground and did not immediately go down. He stopped in his track and carefully felt the movement on the outside.

Suddenly, there was a frantic laughter outside and it seemed like it belonged to a man.

“Hahahaha!! Run! Still want to run?? After killing the people under my command, you actually dare to run!”

Boom!!

Another violent wave of vibration came and the earth seemed to tremble.

Garen tensed up and felt that someone was fighting outside.

“Karfi! Don’t go too far!! This is our White Light area!” Another man shouted angrily.

“What about it! If I want to chase, I chase. If I want to kill, I kill!!” Karfi said coldly. “Double-end Robbing! Die!!”

“You… actually broke through Inheriting level…!!”

Before the voice fell off, a fierce wave of force field once again shook the entire ground.

Even Garen, who was hiding in the ground, felt a numbness in his body.

“This… is Inheriting level!”

Garen looked up as if to see through the mud and watch the battle on the outside.

He now noticed this wave of force field. Similar to the Red Whale’s battle he had watched, this was also of Inheriting level!

“Karfi… the existence of Three Marshalls and One Star, similar as Medero, is terrifying. Some time ago, there was news that Medero had broken through to Level Five Twin Moon Level. After suppressing himself for so long, he finally reached the peak of Twin Moon in one-shot. Unexpectedly, the same Three Marshalls Karfi also broke through Inheriting level. Truly the top talent of this era!”

Garen mused. The progressing speed of these geniuses were horrific. Some accumulated non-stop while some were not known. If it were not for coincidentally coming across Karfi battling White Light’s high-level pilot here, he probably would not even know that Karfi had already broken through Inheriting level.

“Master Nottingham would not let you off! Retreat!!” There seemed to be someone else. After that, the friction of the beam cannons with the air produced strange tearing sounds.

In Karfi’s mad laughter, it seemed that he had killed some of White Light’s people. Then, it was completely quiet on the outside. Finally, it was the sound of the Mech flying away.

Garen slowly walked and headed towards the deeper parts of the cave silently. He did not expect that the so-called task of Three Marshalls would be coming directly to this outer region field to hone themselves. The progressing speed of these geniuses was extremely scary. Perhaps in less than a few years’ time, there would be a qualitative change.

Among Medero the trio, he wondered who else had broken through Inheriting level, whether it was a recent breakthrough, or had already made a breakthrough long ago but stayed hidden.

After all, the trio had become Three Marshalls for many years.

Taking a deep breath and throwing off these thoughts, Garen sped up.

“After dealing with all these issues, then it’s putting all the effort into creating my Exclusive Mech! I must step into the resonance level as soon as possible!”

There were still some potential points that were sufficient for the time being. The main thing was to improve his strength first, so that he could be better emboldened to compete for resources and at the same time, have better capability to collect the new Staff of Absolute Yin!

Accelerating his pace, Garen took the medical package and quickly ran towards Red Moon’s location point. His speed was getting increasingly faster!

Soon, a glowing light red dot appeared in front of Garen’s view.

Clint’s disastrous face was facing him and he was already unconscious.

“Hurry! Clint is going to die! It’s blood filariasis!” Red Moon’s voice sounded panicky, but it was also very weak. “My accumulated energy was used to forcibly jump once. I can’t hold on any longer. Everything up next will depend on you!”

“Got it!” ,Garen nodded. That little red light finally was unable to hold out and completely extinguished.

Garen lifted Clint’s eyelid and examined his eyes. He quickly took off his jacket and saw the terrible wound and the black tiny worms that were worming in and out of the blood vessels near the wound.

“Humph!”

Garen placed his hand on Clint’s chest. The Secret Technique was a practitioner’s high-level technique and Quake, was initiated. Due to his power in reaching the peak of Martial Arts realm, Garen was able to precisely control the vibrations to kill all the bloodworms inside of Clint’s body.

These worms were much more fragile than flesh and bones and so, they were all killed instantly.

Garen reached out and gave a hard smack. Clint instantly vomited a large mouthful of blood and the floor was covered with the corpse of worms and it was all black.

Pulling off a halved-worm from Clint’s mouth, Garen quickly examined his physical condition. His fingertips gently stroked the wound under the ribs and a large piece of rotting flesh was cut off.

In Totem World, Garen was a leading biochemical expert who could perform a heart fusion transplant on himself, not to mention this kind of common emergency surgery.

After stopping the blood using a vein-cutting manner, he then opened the medical bag and took out the drugs. Quickly feeding Clint the drugs to kill the worms in the body, he disinfected, sutured and dressed the wound. Garen then looked at Lonnie who was by the side.

Baylon was already emaciated. The entire person looked like a patient suffering from muscular dystrophy for a long time, delicate and fragile. Her skin was somewhat transparent and she was unconscious as well.

First, she was consecutively given three doses of anti-radiation drugs. Then, Garen quickly took off her clothes and began a full body examination for the spots that had the most serious accumulation of the radiation germs.

The parts underneath the skin that had the most radiation germs could be clearly identified through the color of the skin.

There were too many radiation germs on Lonnie’s body. Even the bloodworms in Clint’s body did not dare to worm in.

Large chunks of purple-black skin resembled one huge black mole after another. Lonnie’s entire body was shrivelled, like being soaked in water for a long time. The skin was completely inflexible and apart from the black moles, it was terrifying white and pale, completely unrecognizable as a human.

Using fingernail instead of a scalpel, the severely infected skin of Baylon was cut off and covered with artificial skin. After suturing, Garen quickly looked for a blood bag and began a blood transfusion for Baylon.

Two bags of blood flowed into the body rapidly under his fingering method.

Baylon’s heart was instantly filled with new vitality and gradually began to recover. The anti-radiation drugs also started to show its effect. Most of the radiation germs began to vanish as they were killed.

Like a miracle, Baylon’s body seemed to be like a blown-up doll. The thin body shell slowly recovered in a speed visible to the naked eye and returned to its normal appearance. The over-whiteness of the skin was completely gone and the soft-breasted chest on the body also began to slowly rise.

When Garen saw this scene, he was stunned and slightly displeased. Some of the emotions originating from Nonosiva affected him and caused frustration. A good brother actually underwent sex reassignment surgery and became a sister!

But looking at that pair of plump breasts, Garen did not see any traces of surgery. This made him somewhat puzzled and stretched out his hands to squeeze it. The feel was very natural!

“What?”

After all, parts of Nonosiva’s memories in Garen were still somewhat worried about his younger brother and sister. Although he had always looked down upon them, they were still this body’s only family in this world.

He could not help but reach out and carefully rub again, looking for signs of surgery left, right, up and down. And yet, there was no sign of the slightest.

Garen’s eyes narrowed and felt that something was off.

Suddenly, he reached out, grabbed Lonnie’s trousers and pulled it down.

Baylon’s pants were taken off together with her panties.

The entire lower body was completely exposed in front of Garen.

“This!!” He scrutinized. It was totally a girl’s construction.

“It’s not sex reassignment surgery! Even if this world’s biomedical technology is powerful, there would still be traces of it! This was not something that can be caused by surgery!”

Garen quickly put Lonnie’s pants back on and stood up.

“Was it the influence of the training method?” He suddenly thought of a possibility, silently watching the two lying on the ground.

Chapter 915: Two Years 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Whether it was the effect of the training method or not, it was likely to be related to Red Moon.

A glimpse of understanding flashed through Garen’s mind.

The origin of Red Moon, this Forbidden Core, was very mysterious. No one knew how it came to Mother Planet, or how he was involved with Clint.

Pushing aside these thoughts, Garen reviewed the injuries of the two. Now he was faced with a dilemma, should he bring them back?

“People with radiation disease were not allowed to enter the inner region at all. This is unavoidable… Once discovered, they will have to be executed immediately.” Garen knew about this rule. “But if I don’t take them back, there are battles everywhere on the outside… Security is also a big issue.”

After contemplating in his heart, Garen squatted down and still did not choose to take the two away. With Red Moon here, both of them should not have too many problems. Since they had overcame difficult and dangerous situations before, what might come next would just be a little hardship at the most.

Furthermore, when he had just checked, he discovered that the Willpower of both of them had actually broke through to Level Two. And in the light Level Two fluctuations, there vaguely was the general pilot’s Level Three or Four. It simply was terrifying.

“Indeed it’s Red Moon, the existence of Forbidden Core… In this kind of in-defiance-of-nature training method, advancing one level is equivalent to other people advancing two or three levels.” While being astounded at the same time, Garen cautiously left some medicine and necessary pure drinking water behind. Eventually, he chose to leave.

Staying in the radiation belt now with the care of Red Moon, perhaps this was the greatest training for them.

Radiation disease might affect the body’s immune system, life expectancy, and body constitution, but even so, there was Red Moon. To live past fifty or sixty years was definitely not a problem. Even seventy or eighty years was not impossible. This guy’s means seemed to be endless.

It was also said that when the pilot’s Willpower reached Inheriting level, there would be physical reincarnation, which would remove most of the symptoms of the disease.

After carefully inspecting for dangerous creatures around and determining that there was no danger, Garen chose to leave quietly.

He could not have any ties with Clint and the other two at this stage and must not allow others to know of this relationship. Both Blackboard and White Light were currently searching for them both and the temptation of Forbidden Core was simply deadly for a pilot’s force.

Garen quickly returned following the original way he had come from. He believed that Red Moon would handle the situation well. This was White Light’s patrol area. If he did not hurry to leave, the battle just now would definitely attract a large number of high-level White Light pilots and that would only make it harder to leave.

As he opened the mud-board at the entrance of the tunnel, Garen quickly rolled over and rushed out, speedily leaving and heading towards the way that he had come from. The mud-board slowly fell back into place and before it had touched the ground, his figure had already disappeared at the end of the plain.

In the underpass, depths of the tunnel beside the unconscious Clint and Baylon, subtle footsteps could be heard.

In the darkness, an ordinary middle-aged man dressed in brown leather slowly emerged and was whistling. Suddenly, he saw Clint lying on the edge of the tunnel.

“What?”

His eyes flashed and he instantly fixed his sight on Baylon among the two. Fair-skinned, beautiful facial features, high chest, and slim waist; this was simply the highest grade kind of young girl to radiation people.

Gulp. The man swallowed his saliva, quickly walked over and squatted down.

“Hey, wake up”, he pushed Baylon’s arm.

No response.

“Still alive? Wake up, wake up!” He continued to push Clint’s arm. Seeing that there was no response from the two, the man’s throat bobbed even more. He reached out his quivering hands towards Baylon’s towering breast.

Pap.

Suddenly, something seemed to roll down from Clint’s body just as he moved.

His line of sight moved towards it, but he could not withdraw it again. Even the sight of Baylon that had attracted him previously could not cause him to return his gaze.

“Water, it actually is pure water!!”

It was a transparent glass bottle filled with clear water. That type of clear-color water, at a glance, could only appear in at least grade two or higher grade pure water!!

In the radiation belt, the lower the radiation level of pure water, the better the water quality and the more effective it was for radiation people to detoxify.

Consuming true pure water without radiation in large amount could discharge the radiation viruses out of the radiation people’s body and result in the lowest one percent of radiation constitution. This kind of radiation constitution could greatly enhance life expectancy. The general body constitution of radiation people had about fifty percent degree of radiation. This was the counterbalance achieved between the body’s immune system and the radiation virus. The lower the degree of radiation, life expectancy and what not would increase.

It was said that the highest one percent of radiation constitution could even live longer than those in the inner region. Perhaps the long-term radiation variation had changed the constitution of the people in the outer region so that they became more robust. As long as there was enough pure water, they could exceed the weak body constitution of the inner region people who were like hothouse flowers.

Gulp…

Another greedy bobbing sound from the throat. The middle-aged man’s claws reached out and with lightning speed, grabbed the bottle of pure water. He dared not open it hastily as he was afraid of polluting the water.

Then, he quickly found some anti-inflammatory drugs, anti-radiation drugs, and other things left behind by Garen beside Clint.

These things were basically expensive items in the radiation belt. The middle-aged man who quickly collected the good things, could not suppress his excitement. When he looked at the two people, a murderous look flashed in his eyes.

“If I kill these two people, then these things will all be mine…”

This idea continued to turn over in his mind.

He slowly extended his hand and bit by bit, stretched it out towards Clint’s throat.

“Whoo…”

A strong wave of Willpower force field suddenly spread out. Clint made a sound and so happened to slowly regained consciousness.

A pair of eyes directly met the middle-aged man.

He blinked and realized that his injuries were much better. He looked at the medical bandage and other objects that were in the man’s other hand.

“Was it you who saved us?” he asked blankly. After examining Lonnie who was beside, it seemed that her situation had also improved by a great deal.

The man was just an ordinary person with Level One Willpower. At this time, his face was a little stiff. Feeling the force field of Level Two with its amplitude actually exceeding that of a Level Three pilot’s force field, his heart trembled.

He managed to squeeze a smile.

“These bandages, these medicines…” Clint’s eyes widened and instantly got up. “Thank you so much!” He bowed his head low. “If it weren’t for you, who knows what would have happened to my companion and I!”

Looking at the unabashed, pure gratitude on Clint’s face, a flash of doubt appeared in the eyes of the man.

Was this guy not aware of the existence of the medicine?

“What happened to you guys? How come you’re here?” He tried to make himself smile more naturally and asked gently.

“My partner and I were seriously injured. There was no other way. When we arrived here, we were completely unconscious. We haven’t had water and food for two days.” Clint said with a wry smile. Through this journey of experience, the originally-somewhat-naïve-him had become a little serious now.

“It’s alright now that you’re fine. It’s alright.”

“I really can’t thank you enough”, Clint knew how important the medicine and water were in the radiation belt. His eyes were full of gratefulness. “If it weren’t for you, we would probably really have died here.”

“It’s nothing, it’s nothing. Seeing you is like seeing my younger brother and sister.” When the man had confirmed that the person before him really did not seem to know anything at all, he was overjoyed. At the same time, he also began to play pretense.

“My name is Clint. She is Lonnie. And you are?”, Clint introduced himself.

“This is where the Underground Rebel Army is. I am a member of it. How did you come here?” the man asked.

“We came in with a girl named Lola. If it weren’t for her, we would already be…” Clint said helplessly. “She had previously said that she would go and take some medicine for us. She should be back soon. ”

“So, that’s how it is.” The man’s eyes flickered. “I’m Ning’en. I have lived here for four years. If you don’t have a place to go to, just come with me. At least I can lead you the way.” He was now completely certain that the two individuals in front of him were indeed unaware of the medicine and water on them. Otherwise, they would not have said that Lola had gone to get some medicine for them.

Although he was unclear of what was going on, it was impossible for him to give up such a large sum of wealth. He had to secure these two people first before anything else!

He also knew Lola, that child, who was relatively well-known in this area. She particularly liked helping people and could be considered as an unusual being among the radiation people. She was still willing to continue helping others no matter how much losses she had suffered.

“Really thank you so much!” Clint immediately rejoiced.

“Come with me. I will inform Lola”, the man smiled and his facial expression was much more natural.

*****************

Upon returning to Flying Batoid City, Garen went to the City Master’s material warehouse and exchanged some of the required radioactive materials with the little remaining drinking water. Although the main material of the biochemical pool was not found, other auxiliary materials were available and they were all prepared in many portions. After all, he was also afraid of failure. Novices naturally had to prepare more.

For the rest of the time, he either cultivated his Willpower or went to the hangar to look at how the repair of his Mech’s outer shell was progressing. It just needed a little covering of an outer layer shell. Regarding the Mastery Energy Ore inside, after the last incident, the people here were now keeping a strict watch. The City Master had sent a large group of miniature-Mech soldiers to stand guard and at the same time, changed a maintenance point for Garen, which belonged to his personal maintenance ground. This greatly enhanced the security.

Nobody here knew what the Mastery Energy Ore was like. Without Garen unlocking the cabin himself, unless the cabin was forcibly broken into, no one could open the door to see what was on the inside. This was because Garen learned his lesson and had filled the inside with lots of yellow smoke gas, completely covering all of the Mastery Energy Ore. At the same time, the transparent cabin shell was painted black so that people could not see the things that were on the inside.

After taking such measures, adding to the protection of City Master, the safety factor rose greatly.

There would only be a few pilots flying through Flying Batoid City in a year. Under normal circumstances, no pilots were willing to deal with radiation people too much. Therefore, the last situation was really a result of Garen’s poor luck.

After a few days had passed, the materials had been bought back, and no more new types of radiation materials had been found, only then did Garen decided to leave. Although he did not reach the final destination of this trip since he was intercepted and had to turn back halfway, the overall goal was still achieved and the material used to construct the Mech’s body had been found. The auxiliary materials for the Energy Machinist’s biochemical pool were also at hand. However, what was troublesome was that many of the materials for the biochemical pool had a shelf life. Some of them could only last a very short period of time, just a few days. Garen’s use of cold storage could only extend their shelf life to half a month.

After rearranging and checking the situation of the Mech’s body, he supplemented and traded some energy batteries. Finally, he took off and left Flying Batoid City, flying speedily towards the direction of Blackboard Region.

This time back, he must build his Exclusive Mech and create a biochemical pool. The way of Energy Machinist should be the best path for him to develop his Living Secret Technique.

It did not matter back then since he did not know the special nature of this profession before and could only take the single route of being a pilot. But now that he knew of it, naturally he could not deviate from the main theme.

Garen intended to create his own Exclusive Mech while carrying out the transformation of the biochemical pool, developing both sides together. If he could do it, maybe the course of Energy Machinist would be his main direction.

******************

Time flew by and in the flash of an eye, two years had already passed.

The battle between Blackboard Region and White Light went into a stalemate. In relation to Maria Academy challenging Blackboard Academy, no one could actually fight. After twenty-three consecutive wins, the friction between the students of both academies began to intensify.

Later on, one of the Three Marshalls and One Star, Karfi, continuously went out to hunt and kill the members of White Light. Once, he actually caught a Maria Region pilot mixing with White Light. Naturally, a war broke out.

There were continuously large and small-scale battles between the two sides. Maria Region publicly supported White Light, but the confrontation of Inheriting-level was not many. It seemed that both sides were constantly accumulating and suppressing their own strength, like two spring fists, constantly pushing back in order to erupt a powerful moment.

On the other side, Royal Region was involved with Central Academy of Mother Planet. All kinds of friendship exchange students’ activities and so on were constantly being done as if taking the stance of sitting on the mountain and watching the tigers fight.

But everyone knew that this region must also be the source of support behind White Light Organization.

Polar Region, on the other hand, had an outbreak of civil war. There was a frictional conflict between the royal family and the territorial and aristocratic alliances. A large-scale civil war broke out and it had been surging for a time.

It seemed that the peaceful state that had been going on for decades would once again revert back into war.

As for Garen, after he returned to the region, he never went out but instead put all his effort into creating his Exclusive Mech, not giving Fila any chance to retaliate. It was a calm and peaceful period for him.

Chapter 916: Two Years 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Somewhere in the underground space in Blackboard Academy, a simple Mech which only had its skeleton built was quietly erected inside the hangar. Unlike the surrounding black standard Mechs, this Mech’s body was entirely made of the most advanced middle-grade material, using Erm Alloy Steel as its skeleton system. Through the empty skeleton, one could see the heart of the engine flashing a white light.

The entire Mech was like a giant’s skeleton frame, but with a vibrant heart.

The Mech’s body was seven meters tall, with a long tail like a Tyrannosaurus rex hanging behind it. Although the main body material had not yet been filled in, it had already given people a strong sense of terror.

Around the body were a large number of thick black cables connecting to it, as well as large and small robots that were constantly going up and down, working on the details. There were several engineers below executing remote commands.

The Mech’s body was facing a white semi-circular observatory platform which extended from the wall. Although it was enclosed with thick, high-strength glass, the condition of the Mech could be clearly seen from the inside of it.

At this time, a few people were standing in the observatory platform.

All of them were wearing dark-black military uniforms and they were tall and striking. A tight black belt was pulled diagonally from the shoulder and buckled at the waist to give off a concise and capable temperament.

“Captain Nono, your Mech’s body has been built for two years with an investment of 1.8 billion. The major systems are all in place, except for the last one. Filling in the main material will complete it all. I was wondering, if you are satisfied with the engineering process of our White Dragon Base?”, a middle-aged man with short white hair asked with a faint smile.

As one of Blackboard Region’s Black Flood Party in-house Mech manufacturing base, he had personally led his students and vice-president to oversee this Mech for two years, giving serious attention to this young man.

Using two years to build a Mech from scratch, especially an exclusive Mech, was not considered a long time. However, having half of the base concentrating on processing just one Mech, it was extremely shocking.

White Dragon Base manufactured hundreds of units of standard Mechs every year. Now all of them were discontinued in order to give way to this huge investment of exclusive Mech.

All this was due to the terrific strength of the young man in front of him.

Thinking of this, the man’s heart could not help but trembled.

He looked at this strong, lion-like man standing in front of himself.

He was probably twenty-two years old but was already able to create his own Exclusive Mech… Such a genius was undoubtedly rare even in Black Flood Party. After all, a Level Five pilot, who was also this rich, was hard to come by, what more such a young one.

Hearing his question, the young man in front chuckled.

“Don’t say that. These two years were all dependant on the full support of Major Baylor to reach this level of progress. If it were the normal manufacturing speed in other places, don’t even think about it without at least three to five years. Many things could not be that easily arranged even with a lot of money.”

“You are very modest, but for the next filling material, we will need you to prepare it as soon as possible. According to your plan for the Mech, the filling material must be of higher grade. For the best kind of materials to be used in a Level Five Mech, I’m afraid the cost…” Major Baylor didn’t finish his sentence, but everybody knew what followed.

Such high-grade materials could not be bought with Universal Units.

Garen smiled and looked at the white shimmer that was wrapped around the engine of his Mech’s body. In it were vague traces of blood. It was the special luster of Blood Silver.

In the past two years, he had sold most of the Mastery Energy Ore through his teacher and had gotten lots of the materials for the manufacturing of Exclusive Mech. However, because the materials he needed were too high-graded, it was very difficult to find all of them even through the exchange with his teacher. Therefore, after spending so much time, he had barely managed to gather most of the things. Now, he only lacked one thing, the main filling material of the Mech’s body.

“The filling material must first meet the conductivity of Willpower. Then, it is the hardness index, tenacity index, memory metal index, corrosion resistance, radiation resistance, temperature tolerance, et cetera. I have carefully selected. The best one should be Ring Light Silver”, Garen replied.

“Ring Light Silver? This is a rare metal that is difficult to find even in the whole of Blackboard Region…” Baylor frowned slightly. He was only euphemistically reminding him, but he was speechless on the inside. Ring Light Silver was a type of precious metal that the general pilots could only manage to buy small portions of to fuse into their own Mech’s body for the purpose of enhancing the performance of the Mech’s body. Nonosiva actually wanted to use Ring Light Silver to completely build the entire Mech’s body. This was no different from building a house with diamonds! Luxury to the extreme!

“I’ve got some prospects in this matter”, Garen did not say much.

With the full support of Blackboard Academy these two years and the full support of Teacher Van Doe, everything was going well. However, the only thing that made him unhappy was that Fila had advanced again and he seemed to be ready to break through to Twin Moon Level.

As one of the top geniuses that had emerged in recent decades, the recent progress of Fila was getting increasingly faster, probably triggered by Medero.

It was said that within a month’s time, he would be able to reach Twin Moon Level.

Garen himself was still at Level Five without the slightest improvement. Instead, he had familiarize himself with a variety of skills in the area of Energy Machinist. His Energy Machinist Willpower had entered Level Two. The Energy Machinist’s computing power advancing method was very strange. The Willpower imprint did not exist in the body at all, so that even with potential points, the existence of the Energy Machinist imprint could not be found.

This made Garen very surprised. In the case that the pilot’s training method could not be advanced, he chose to focus on the area of Energy Machinist. After raising the intelligence attribute to eight points, his computing power had leaped a big step and successfully entered Level Two. However, there was bit of trouble with Level Three. The required computing power actually rose a lot which made Garen faintly sceptical that he seemed to lack a very important thing of an Energy Machinist. He did not believe that all the Energy Machinists in this world could have much stronger computing power than he had now.

After talking to Baylor about the details of the Mech’s body processing, Garen left White Dragon Base and returned to his villa that was on a mountain nearby.

In these two years, his parents had opened a construction company and used the ties that Garen pulled to acquire projects, earning with much joy. Every year, they would easily earn millions of Universal Units.

After the disappearance of his brother Baylon, the family slowly got used to life without Baylon, whereas the only sister of Garen did not go outside and mingle around much anymore. Instead, she was hooked on gambling. She would mix with some so-called princesses’ clique all day long in the name of Garen and was living it up.

Garen was too lazy to bother about her. Now, he was already the eighth grade elite of Blackboard Academy Inner Courtyard. After continuously jumping grades and passing the assessments easily, he had successfully became Teacher Van Doe’s not-very-outstanding, but also not-a-mediocre disciple.

By virtue of the reputation and influence of Black Flood Party and the conflict with Fila, he also had minor fame in Inner Courtyard and had actually entered the top 100 in the overall rankings.

Inside the villa, Garen had just entered the door when he saw a familiar figure sitting on the couch in his hall, boringly clicking on the TV.

“Celine, no training today?” He smiled and walked over, taking took off his coat and handing it to the maid. Someone beside sent over a warm natural juice.

It was handed to Celine but Garen took it and drank it himself.

Celine was dressed in a tight-fitting, white leather suit with a little dark golden flower logo on her shoulder. It looked somewhat mysterious.

Glancing at Garen, she grinned.

“Is your Mech completed? Running over there every day, you think it’s a junk battleship that could be completed in such a short time?”

This girl kept shoulder-length hair, but also seemed to have dyed her hair, the same black as Garen’s. Her body was getting hotter, her front and back protruding, waist slender, legs slim and powerful. She had one of her leg crossed and both arms laid out on both sides of the sofa. It was very chic and gave off a strong and powerful feeling like that of a leopardess.

“It is still lacking the last material, Ring Light Silver”, Garen sat down, grabbed the remote control board next to her and changed the TV to a military channel.

“Damn, still fighting to watch TV with me. How old are you now? Already a captain yet still snatching the TV from me, an ordinary student!” Celine retorted.

“You broke through?” Garen smiled and sized her up. The Willpower force field had already reached the zenith of Level Four. Indeed, this girl was from a big household. There was no shortage of resources and her talent was not-too-bad. It seemed that she could use her own Exclusive Mech before the age of thirty.

“Although I’m not as abnormal as you are, I could still manage to advance.” Celine nodded arbitrarily. “Black Flood Party’s top talents like you cannot be compared with me, this type of small household. Tsk tsk. Look at you. Ring Light Silver. Although I have guessed that you are very ambitious, yet using Ring Light Silver as material…” She put her thumb up, indicating that she was incomparable with him.

“Does your side have a way to source this?”

“I can find some of it. How much do you want?”

“Five tons”, Garen lifted up a hand.

“I can only provide you with half of it”, Celine frowned. “The household also has a great demand for Ring Light Silver. It is priced according to the internal procurement. With my authority, I could give you half price.”

“Thanks a lot then. This can also save me a lot of money”, Garen smiled.

“Why don’t you just go and die! With tens of millions of income a month, you would have made at least a thousand million in these two years! Talk about saving more money!” Celine scorned.

Garen himself however, had a clear understanding in his heart. The absorption of White Rainbow Stone was of no use to him anymore and the progress of Living Secret Technique was extremely slow. It had already been two years but, it was only eighteen percent complete. From the original two percent till now, it seemed that there was a direct resistant to the Rainbow Stones. The advancing of Hellfrost Peacock Technique Level Six seemed to be harder than all the previous levels.

Most of the Mastery Energy Ore that he obtained had been sold to acquire nearly three billion worth of materials. Most of them were spent on the Mech while the leftovers were used to purchase some materials and technologies for the Energy Machinist’s experimental platform. He did not have much left now.

However, fortunately, the cost of the Ring Light Silver should not exceed one billion, and so the money at hand could still cover it.

“There will be an auction very soon. Although this item, Ring Light Silver, is rare, but the annual output is also very large. The main reason is that its expense is huge, so the shortage of output leads to a high price. The finale of that auction is a piece of four-tons, natural Ring Light Silver. The purity is said to be very high. If you are interested, you can go and have a look”, Celine mentioned briefly.

She then added another sentence.

“Fila is also said to be going.”

“Fila?” The corner of Garen’s mouth ticked up slightly. “This guy recently had been snatching the Rainbow Stone mine source from me and putting a lot of effort into doing it.”

“What are you going to do? That person is probably a Twin Moon Level powerhouse”, Celine was suddenly piqued.

“So what? As long as I don’t go out of the region and if he dares to touch me in Blackboard Region, my senior brother would also dare to take action against him in the open”, Garen was not worried about this at all even though Fila took him seriously. His Black Wind, which could only be released once an hour originally, could now be released dozens of times without any problem. He could even release a plume of the more advanced black smoke. This was the powerful capability that could only be used by the Divine Wind General and it belonged to a more purified Black Wind. Although it took a longer time to build a superimposed pyramid, it could already reflect his terrific savvy. It did not matter if the body constitution was slow, his understanding of Black Wind was unattainable for anyone.

A Divine Wind General’s strength was that wherever one went, black smoke would fill that place. Just with a horrific automatic territory-liked attack, it could easily destroy any lower-level pilots.

Chapter 917: Energy Machinist 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After chatting with Celine in the hall, Garen sent her away. When he had finished his meal, he went back to his room to cultivate his training method. Currently, all that he was cultivating was the Energy Machinist’s training method because Crouched Eagle Talon could not be progressed as it required an Exclusive Mech to produce resonance degree.

He lived this lifestyle for nearly two years. Every day, he would calculate the Energy Machinist’s Level Three training question bank.

Sitting cross-legged alone in a cultivating room, Garen meticulously calculated a large number of computational models displayed on the wall while constantly using Willpower to repeatedly stack them. In this horrific process of complex computation, he could feel that his Willpower had gradually changed and become better in calculating. The Willpower that emerged from the Energy Machinist Imprint was completely different from that of Crouched Eagle Talon’s Willpower.

Crouched Eagle Talon was entrenched in the arms, almost like two groups of cold Blackboard air current. Using his inner vision, Garen could easily identify it.

The Energy Machinist’s Willpower was a kind of vague air mass in which its shape was indistinguishable. Sometimes, it was round and other times it was a square. However, more often, it was a distorted, irregular air mass which was transparent on the inside. Without looking carefully, its presence could not be noticed at all. Moreover, the Energy Machinist’s Willpower was located in the void at the back of the head and not in the human body at all.

This totally overturned all the knowledge that Garen had previously learned about Willpower training method.

In the white room, Garen sat cross-legged and closed his eyes slightly. Behind the back of his head were two seemingly transparent spiky masses which were floating about. They were emitting a faintly transparent gas that was drifting upwards.

“Intelligence has reached eight points. From henceforth, to raise every one point will need sixty potential points. Currently, the remaining thirty points are not enough. I must find the Staff of Absolute Yin as soon as possible!”

He had been searching for the whereabouts of the Staff of Absolute Yin in recent years. Through various channels, he managed to find a clue. However, because he had to get his Exclusive Mech done for the time being, he could not spare his time to go look for it.

With the ongoing war between White Light and Blackboard Region, there could be extremely dangerous encounters everywhere in the radiation belt which made it far more dangerous than before.

After practicing calculating for a while and feeling a little increase in the Energy Machinist Willpower, Garen was satisfied and opened his eyes. But he realized that time had flew past and it was almost eight at night. It was already dark outside. Looking through the window, he could see a black shuttle-shaped battleship patrolling in the sky not far away. Its surface was covered with a lot of flashing lights.

Garen let out a breath. He took out a black key from the pocket of his shirt. There was only one tine on the key. No matter how he looked at it, the key was too simple and did not look like it was used to open a door. What kind of door could be opened with just one tine? That would not be able to keep the thief out at all.

Every time he finished practicing calculating, he would take out this key to carefully check and scrutinize it. Intuition told him that this key was not a simple object.

Through the tines of a variety of sophisticated instruments, Garen realized that the material of this key was very solid and basically, there was nothing that could destroy it.

Holding the key repeatedly in the palm of his hand, suddenly, Garen froze. He held the lower end of the key and put it upright in front of his eyes, examining it carefully.

Every detail of this key had been fully engraved in his mind in these few years and he was extremely familiar with it.

But now, this key actually had an additional super tiny black diamond pattern, only the size of a grain. It looked complicated, making him dizzy.

Garen gazed at this pattern carefully. It looked like many flower patterns superimposing on one another. It also looked like a lot of weird symbols combined in a pile, giving a mysterious and ancient feeling.

As he focused his attention on this pattern, suddenly, a white light burst out from the pattern. It split accurately into two beams and shot into Garen’s eyes.

Woom…

Garen felt a kind of inexplicable dizzy feeling in his head. His vision went white and he only felt a spinning sensation in his head and his upper body became very heavy.

His eyes were covered with white light and nothing could be seen. Only his ears could hear the subtle sound of the air tearing, as if he was flying at a high speed, but his skin did not feel any real airflow.

After he had slowly adapted to the spotlight caused by the white light in front of him, he did not know what was going on but found himself standing in front of a small white wooden door. There was a flower-like intricate pattern carved on the wooden door, except that Garen had never seen this flower before.

“Welcome to the Federation of Energy Machinists”, a crisp girl’s voice sounded from the door.

“This is the place where Energy Machinists can communicate with one another. The area you are at is Mother Planet a54 area; the number of people is 789. You are the 790th newly added official Energy Machinist. Please keep your identity key well. If it is lost, please go to the Central Academy Energy Machinist Division to replace it. Thank you for your cooperation and I wish you a pleasant time.”

The female’s voice faded.

The door in front of Garen opened with a bang.

Outside, a somewhat lively square with a fountain pool appeared in front of him. The people coming and going were dressed differently. They did not look like they came from the same place but looked more like a mixture of different ethnic groups of various nationalities. Their skin complexion varied from white, black, yellow and red with a variety of shades. Garen even saw two human beings with two lizard tails, squatting at a stall and bargaining with the stall owner.

A burst of lively voices flooded the door, making him a little surprised.

As he attempted to walk through the small door, Garen tucked away his key and looked at the sky and the surroundings.

The sky was a very ordinary blue sky with white clouds, but there was no sun. Still, it was very bright but he could not tell where the light came from.

Around was a medium-size circular town structure, surrounded by ordinary single-storey houses that were neither too high nor too low. Beside the houses hung different patterns of gray-brown cloth, fluttering slightly with the breeze. What was very strange was that when Garen looked at these fabrics, he could recognize the meaning of the fabric patterns. These fabrics were the names of various shops.

“Can you not block the road?”

A voice sounded from his right. It was a dark-skinned woman with a white headscarf. She was tall and thin and looked emaciated, almost comparable to a mummy.

Garen was stunned and made way for her, watching the woman walk through him and head towards a shop on the left.

He just so happened to be standing at the left side of the stairs to this shop.

“Is this place an illusion or…” Garen frowned and carefully distinguished his body.

Soon he discovered that the core of Living Secret Technique was missing from his body. His Soul Seed had also disappeared. It was apparent that this place was purely a virtual community.

“Real illusion simulation?”

He began to imitate other people and went one round past the circular shops of the town. There were many people entering and exiting the shops, but the flow of people was even greater at the street vendors. The fountain square in the middle of dozens of shops was densely packed with little stalls. It seemed that over time, there were more and more people setting up stalls.

Garen tried to walk towards the main door of a shop.

However, he found that a transparent barrier was blocking him. A bald man beside him strode up the steps and gave a contemptuous look at him.

“You have no money and still want to enter the shop?? Stupid.”

Garen was not angry, as if he had not heard him, but continued to explore everything here.

He began experimenting with all the dozens of circular shops around the square but found that he could enter none of them. And over time, some shops would suddenly disappear in a flash. After that, other shops would automatically move closer to one another like wooden blocks to expand themselves and fill in the gap left by the previous shop.

“How magical”, Garen tried to break the corner of the wall of a shop but found it to be extremely hard and could not be damaged. It seemed that the rule imposed here was firmly regulated so that it could not be destroyed.

“This brainless man is still here, how retarded. He actually wanted to pull off the wall stone here?” That bald headed man just happened to walk out of the shop, followed by a beautiful woman with a charming face. The two were cuddling tightly together, almost like they were merging into one.

Garen gave him a glance and ignored him.

“How does the Federation even have this kind of country pigs? How annoying to look at.” Baldhead started to curse arrogantly.

Another thin red-skinned man was about to enter the shop at this time, but was pushed to one side by him.

“Go away. So f****ing frustrating to see Red Ghost.”

The red-skinned man was silent and did not dare to reply.

Baldhead swaggered his way out and headed towards another shop.

Garen looked up at the cloth of this shop, Intelligence Point.

Obviously, a place to sell intel.

He tried to go in but regretfully, that transparent light screen blocked him.

“Don’t waste your energy. Without money, you cannot enter the shop. This place will automatically detect the money you have on you.” The red-skinned man who had been pushed away just now, smiled bitterly and told Garen, but he did not enter. Instead, he walked over to the side of the steps to the shop where Garen was at.

“Are you here for the first time?” His Universal language accent was very standard. Clearly, there was some kind of language translation system here.

“Yeah.” Garen nodded. “May I ask, what is this place actually?”

“The more you come, the more you will know.” The red-skinned man whispered. “This is a small trading market of the Federation of Energy Machinists. It is a virtual market that only trades knowledge and technology, known as a knowledge market. However, there will be an item market that will be held in real time. There will truly be many people at that time and you can directly trade real items there.”

“Knowledge market? Item market?” Garen frowned. “Is this place convened by that Energy Machinists whatever federation?”

“Of course, all Energy Machinists will be automatically issued a guide key from the guide to enter this virtual world and conduct various transactions. This is where the true secret of Energy Machinists lies. Only Energy Machinists are able to enter here. There isn’t any way for others to get in and out.” The red-skinned man explained softly, “This is your first time in here and you didn’t even have your tutor with you. Be cautious when you trade so that you don’t get cheated.”

“Who are the people involved in the market here? Are they from the same area?” Garen continued to ask since it was difficult to meet someone who was willing to answer him.

“No. The people here could be from anywhere. Some of their appearance may not even be true. There are expensive face-changing tools that can allow people to modify themselves. The people here might be from nearby planets, star regions, or even Energy Machinists from space ships caravans who are passing by. Anything is possible.” The red-skinned man shook his head and said.

“Thank you for your explanation. I haven’t asked for your name yet.”

“Olse, my name is Olse. There is still a long list of surnames behind it but there is no need to bring it up. I’m an Energy Machinist of a caravan that is passing by here, only Level Three.” The red-skinned man smiled ruefully. “Level Three Energy Machinist is considered the lowest degree of level here.”

“I’m Garen. It can’t be true. Level Three is actually the lowest level?” Garen said. He had worked hard to practice calculating for two years and until now, he was only Level Two, not even close to Level Three. And this person in front of him actually said that Level Three was the lowest level at the bottom.

“Indeed, it’s like that. What to do? I do not have a good Energy Machine Imprint. The one I am using is the lowest grade Wasp Imprint. Its auxiliary calculation is only three times and it can only create the lowest level of Investigating Wasps”, Olse smiled bitterly again. “The higher grade Energy Machine Imprint is too expensive. Our caravan gathered all the funds and only managed to buy me such an ordinary imprint. Energy Machinist is simply a money-burning profession.”

“Energy Machine Imprint? What is that?” Garen heard about this for the first time.

“What? You don’t even know what Energy Machine Imprint is!?” Olse’s expression this time instantly turned bizarre. “What kind of tutor did you really have? Without the support of the Energy Machine Imprint, don’t even think that that our Energy Machinist’s computing power could enter the third level!”

Garen was slightly shocked. Sure enough, he had always felt that he was probably missing something. He did not expect that the facts had completely confirmed his conjecture. Indeed, what he lacked seemed to be something that was absolutely indispensable to an Energy Machinist – an Energy Machine Imprint.

“Come come come. Let’s go and have a drink first. I really admire you. Your tutor didn’t tell you about the basic knowledge before letting you in here”, Olse shook his head helplessly.

The two went in front of one another to a tavern-like shop at the edge. Olse paid for Garen so that he could finally enter the shop.

Inside the tavern was very large. A vast area like that of a football field was filled with white tables and chairs of the same size. They were sparsely occupied as the people sat far apart, even their voices were not heard. Clearly, there was sound insulation.

The two found a seat by the wall and sat down. Olse then knocked on the table.

“I want two ale. Hot.”

With a whoosh, two hot cups of light brown ale immediately appeared before the two, all of which were large cups and there was a lot of bubbles overflowing out of it. When the bubbles were about to drop onto the table, they immediately disappeared.

“Thank you.” Garen nodded. There was no waiter here so it seemed that there was an automatic program controlling everything.

Chapter 918: Energy Machinist 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Its okay, back then I was abandoned by my teacher as well, and had to come in here to explore on my own. I know how much you have to go through to reach the beginner level if you start off exploring without any real knowledge.” Olse drank a gulp of the ale, and sighed, “That’s why every time I see a rookie come in, I’ll help them however I can.”

“Could you tell me what the Energy Machine Imprint is?” asked Garen in a low voice.

“The Energy Machine Imprint is a mysterious, magical piece of special equipment that you can embed into your Willpower Imprint. It can improve our calculation skills, simplifying a lot of those complicated, repetitive methods. With it, we just need to find the calculation method, and calculate it once. After that, the Energy Mech Imprint will record down the calculation method, and then it can calculate that way every time, greatly reducing the burden on we Energy Machinists,” Olse explained.

“It’s like my Yellow Wasp Imprint.” He snapped his fingers, and a piece of metal in the image of a yellow wasp slowly appeared behind him, suspended in mid-air and glowing with a faint yellow light. “He can more or less triple my calculation speed and ability, and this includes counting statistics. In real combat, it can automatically control the Biochemical Pool to create more Yellow Wasp Surveillance Soldiers. These surveillance soldiers work well in space, and can spray out particles to help them move at high speeds. They have no offensive power, and can only move quickly or share their vision with you, that’s why they can only be surveillance soldiers. As the lowest-level Yellow Wasps, mine can only scan a radius of fifty kilometers, and is only active for half an hour. If you get the material, you can use it for the re-synthesis next time, you’ll only lose 50% of the materials that way.”

“Can’t I store it in the Biochemical Pool to start with?” asked Garen.

“You can’t, it won’t work. The Biochemical Pool can only make on-the-spot ones, longer-lasting ones can only be evolved through the experimental platform, so that they acquire new functions. And the longer-lasting ones require many expensive materials, it’s just like creating a Mech, the skills required are very troublesome too,” Olse said helplessly. “Just how hopeless is your teacher? They didn’t teach you anything properly.”

“Uh… To be honest, I’m self-taught, I don’t really have a teacher,” replied Garen honestly, and also slightly exasperatedly. “I didn’t think that the path of an Energy Machinist was so complicated, at first I had thought it was about the same as regular training methods, but I didn’t know it was this troublesome.”

“Well, of course, you were self-taught– What!” It seemed that only then did Olse react, and he stood up abruptly, his expression full of shock as he stared at Garen. “You’re self-taught?!”

“Yeah…” Garen nodded.

“H-How long did you spend?” Olse’s voice was trembling slightly.

“Urk—Six years.” Garen thought about it, and decided not to say two years, so he tripled it. Looking at the way this guy was reacting, it seemed that the fact that he was self-taught was already a miracle in itself.

“Six years, huh… No wonder.” Olse heaved a long sigh of relief, and sat down. “I was saying that you’re still so young, if you were self-taught and still managed to become a Level Two Energy Machinist within three years, then that would be truly terrifying. But even so, without a teacher, you are still rather exceptional to reach Level Two in six years.”

“I see…” Garen nodded.

“I don’t really know about the Energy Machinist parties over here, but I advise you to find a decent party and apply for the recruitment test to join, it is impossible for you to advance in this line without a teacher, because there are a lot of things you simply won’t come into contact with if you’re self-taught,” advised Olse sincerely.

“Join a party? How do I join?” Garen was interested.

“Most of the Inherited Level pilots from the pilot parties would have Energy Machinist parties working together with them, it’s very common for the two sides to help each other fill the gaps. So you just need to find a powerful Inherited Level faction, and you should be able to find a corresponding Energy Machinist party. If you can learn so much yourself, you can totally try out the test.”

“Yup, I will.” Garen instantly thought of the Black Flood Party. He was in the Black Flood Party now, and they might have an Energy Machinist in their ranks too.

“Alright, I’m headed off now too, the ships are going to leave this region soon, and the signal will grow weaker and weaker. I’m from the Tidal Thunder Planet, you can come by for a vacation if you have time, I’ll show you around,” said Olse with a smile as he got up.

“I will if I get the chance.” Garen nodded, and stood up as well.

The other person disappeared with a whoosh, and after his vision blurred for a moment, he also appeared in the plaza outside the shop.

There were a lot fewer people in the plaza now. The stalls had also become sparser, they had evidently either completed their deals, or the vendors had simply left.

Garen continued to walk around the area, looking at the wares sold on the stalls. In the end he realized that they were mostly strange and bizarre materials, some were things he had seen briefly introduced in the Energy Machinist training methods, but most were completely unheard of.

“The wing of a Flying Mantis, it can be installed onto biochemical creatures, it’ll be even faster than a Level 2 Mech!”

“The unihorn of a Burrowing Mole increases your sharpness by one level for half an hour.”

“The distilled genetic liquid of an unknown mutated snake, it can increase the vitality of mutated creatures from the Biochemical Pool by 0.4 levels for ten minutes.”

“The gallbladder of a Giant Bear, price fixed at fifty crystals, no haggling.”

Some of the stalls had a screen introducing the uses of their wares, while other items seemed to be too common or famous, so there was no explanation, just the prices.

The stall owners did not yell, they just relied on the rectangular screens beside them to show their advertising.

The plaza was not big, and soon enough Garen had finished looking at most of the stalls. He noticed that they were mostly used for the Biochemical Pool, most of them were materials or items used to modify the cannon fodder creatures that came from the Pool.

Only a few of them were used for the experimental platform, but those tended to be very expensive and were sold as soon as they were brought out.

“Scram!”

Suddenly there was a shout from ahead.

Garen raised his head and glanced there, and realized that it was actually those two raucous baldies from before. Right now, the two of them were kicking a young man with rabbit ears, making him fall hard on his butt.

“You dare fight for the stuff that I want? You should consider it an honor to be able to hand them to me! You have no sense of the glory bestowed upon you!” Baldhead was as raucous as ever, but no one around them dared to step up. Someone who dared to be this high-key would certainly have a powerful background.

“But I’ve even paid the money already!” The rabbit-eared young man got up, and started arguing, his expression pained.

“So what if you’ve paid? You’re trash from a backward place, it’s your fortune to be able to stand and speak in front of me, how dare to speak back!” As his girlfriend giggled away, Baldhead slapped the rabbit-eared young man hard.

Garen was completely speechless, he really could bump into such people all the time. That included in the Federation of Energy Machinists, even though it sounded all high and mighty.

But when he saw that Baldhead actually slapped him, and the rabbit-eared young man’s face was even starting to swell, he became slightly surprised.

“You can just start hitting people here?”

“Of course, you can’t kill anyone, but other than that, all the attacks here will cause the same amount of pain and damage,” said a talkative old man who was watching from the sidelines. “That baldy is from the Mother Planet’s Magnetic Field, that’s one of the three strongest Energy Machinist factions, together with Star Cloud and Black Blade. That’s why no one dares to interfere.”

“Magnetic Field, Star Cloud, Black Blade.” Garen quietly memorized these three names.

“If you encounter that baldy, just tolerate him. Most normal people can’t afford to provoke him, that’s a huge faction with an Inherited Level Energy Machinist,” the old man sighed, shaking his head.

“Inherited Level powers, how impressive,” a young man could not help but say sarcastically, his expression cold.

“Shh, you’ll get in trouble if they hear you,” the young man’s companion hurriedly yanked his hand.

Garen watched that baldy over there calmly, he understood the position of Energy machinists now. And as one of the strongest Energy Machinist parties of the Mother Planet, he did not know just how powerful that was, but he did know it was at least at the same level as the Black Flood Party. It was impressive indeed.

“Baldhead Monba is the most overbearing person in this market, nobody dares to fight him,” said a low voice.

“So what? If he continues on like this, he’ll meet his match sooner or later.”

Garen could not be bothered with this, and turned around to leave. Suddenly his gaze swept across the crowd, and he froze on the spot.

A familiar figure appeared in front of him. Skintight white leather clothes, with some dark gold patterns on the shoulder. That sexy figure, curves in all the right places, and that clear scar on her pretty face that did nothing to hide her charismatic aura, making her seem stronger instead.

“Celine!”

Celine had not seen him yet, and instead she walked up, frowning, until she was behind Baldhead. Then she kicked him hard.

Bam.

Baldhead turned around and grabbed her long leg.

“You dare ambush me!” When Baldhead turned around and saw Celine, his fierce expression instantly turned slightly pervy. “Yo, not bad, what a pretty little lady.”

“Let me go! Or you’ll suffer the consequences!” A hint of coldness flashed through Celine’s eyes. She had not thought that Baldhead would be so good at close combat, and would react so quickly.

“That’s strange. Everyone saw that it was this woman who purposely attacked me first,” said Baldhead loudly, laughing coldly.

“Celine, it has nothing to do with you!” The rabbit-eared young man hurriedly rushed over and tried to separate the two of them, but Baldhead blocked him and then swept him away. He fell onto the ground with a whoomph, and groaned, unable to get up.

“So you two know each other…” Baldhead looked up Celine’s long legs to the place between them pervertedly. “What pretty legs, let me cop a nice feel.” His other hand flew out and caressed Celine’s inner thigh.

“Let go!” Celine’s expression turned cold, and she gave him a hard jolt, but unexpectedly, she could not escape his control. Feeling that hand go past her knee and towards her the inner sides of her thigh, she started to grow anxious.

But for some reason, she felt all the energy slowly leaving her body.

“Celine, you’ve encountered a powerhouse, haven’t you? I told you a long time ago, there will always be someone stronger than you.” Suddenly, a familiar voice came from beside her.

Celine followed the voice and somehow saw Garen looking at her with a smile, walking to her slowly.

Chapter 919: Auction 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“And what the hell are you?” Baldhead glared at him coldly, staring at Garen as he approached.

“It’s all a misunderstanding, let’s make love, not war, and call it quits, shall we?” Garen said with a smile.

Joy flashed through Celine’s eyes, she knew just how powerful Garen was. While Baldhead was distracted, she gave her legs a jolt, and spun them hard, breaking free from his grip. She quickly took two steps back.

But that sense of powerlessness did not disappear.

“You used poison?!” Her expression instantly changed slightly.

“What do you mean by poison, little pretty?” Baldhead laughed, his eyes narrowed. “Did you think that you can get away unharmed after touching my body?”

“Didn’t you hear what I said?” Garen walked over and stood in front of Celine, facing Baldhead. “It was all just a misunderstanding, let us all calm down, and understand each other better.”

He would not put him and his companion in trouble just for something as meaningless as pity.

Baldhead seemed to have a considerable background and strength, it would truly be troublesome if he provoked a powerful faction just like that.

“I say, who do you think you are? Scram!” Baldhead’s expression turned cold. He actually stomped forward, his large foot aiming hard towards Garen’s face.

Garen tilted his body away slightly, avoiding that stomp, and then he abruptly grabbed Baldhead’s stomping foot with his hand. He released a slight breath.

“Garen, you never were the type to hold yourself back!” said Celine from behind, mercilessly.

“We can’t kill anyone here, so it’s pointless to fight back and forth, we should all try to be more peaceful,” said Garen, his expression calm as he shook his head.

When they heard that, Baldhead and the people around him all paused for a moment, they vaguely felt a hint of cold killing intent from Garen. All their hearts shook slightly.

Looks like this guy was a tough one too. The surrounding crowd knew that now.

At the same time, having been blocked, one of Baldhead’s legs was being held in Garen’s hands. But as Garen exerted more force in his grip, there began to be a faint sound of bone cracking.

“Let go!!” A sheen of sweat appeared on Baldhead’s forehead.

“Relax, can’t we all sit down and chat properly?” Garen smiled.

“I’m telling you to let go! Bastard!” howled Baldhead fiercely.

“Let him go! Unless you want to die outside, away from home,” the seductive woman beside Baldhead spoke as well, staring at Garen icily.

“Okay, okay… I’ll let go.” Garen smiled and relaxed his grip lightly, letting go of Baldhead’s leg.

All of a sudden, he turned around, and his booted leg became a grey shadow that whipped over. As though it was truly a lightning-fast whip, it even made an exploding sound in the air.

Bam!!

Blood sprayed everywhere. Baldhead’s whole head had been blown apart, blood and brain matter spewing all over the place. His body fell to his knees stiffly, and as the woman beside him screamed, he fell forward, and was completely lifeless.

In an instant, his corpse had turned into a large field of white lights that scattered and vanished.

“Tsk-tsk-tsk… See, it’s not like I can kill him for real, this will lead to troublesome consequence,” said Garen, shaking his head.

“You—y-you!!” That seductive woman could not even speak properly anymore, all the blood had drained out of her face, and she pointed at Garen as she stumbled backward. Suddenly she seemed to trip on something, falling to the ground, but she could not get up again no matter what she tried.

“That’s what I said, there’s no way you could be that kind of soft, weak, useless type of guy.” Celine seemed to have recovered some too, so she walked up to Garen and stood shoulder to shoulder with him. She lifted one leg, and kicked up a metal shard that was on the floor.

The metal shard spun quickly, and nailed itself into the woman’s brow.

With a bam, the woman fell onto her back, turned into many white lights, and vanished.

The people who had gathered to watch were all shocked, these two were unnaturally ruthless, and just seeing how decisively they acted, they surely must be that type of cold-blooded, killing maniac from the real world outside. Otherwise, they would not have simply taken lives just like that in here.

“Alright, everyone, break it up, break it up,” said Garen loudly, waving his hand. “This is just a virtual world anyway, it’s not like they’re really dead, so it’s fine.”

“Young man, you two have done it now!” the old man who had been talking and standing next to Garen just now spoke. “That baldy was from the Magnetic Field, if they discover your location in the real world…” He did not complete that sentence, but they knew the immense severity of it from his expression alone.

“It’s fine.”

Since Garen made his move, he would naturally have been prepared for this situation.

“Are the people from Magnetic Field that big a deal?” said Celine coldly. She had settled some messages for Garen beforehand, otherwise Garen would not have acted so decisively either.

“Let’s go!”

She split the crowd apart, and left with Garen, one after the other.

Bam bam!

After two crisp sounds, the two of them instantly exploded into many white dots, and vanished from that strange space.

In the room, Garen opened his eyes slowly, and lifted his wrist to see the contact request from Celine.

He tapped ‘confirm’ lightly.

“Nono, that baldy is just the younger brother of some Level Three Energy Machinist in Magnetic Field, don’t worry, it’ll be fine.” Celine’s face appeared on his wristwatch. “Last time I went to the main family’s ranking competition and won ninth, so I finally reached Level One of that Energy Machinist level I’ve been keeping a count on. I found one of the elders in the family to be my teacher, but I never thought I would bump into you there.”

Garen did not expect it either, to think he could meet Celine in the Federation of Energy Machinists’ virtual space. After she learned all those combat skills from him, this little brat’s position in the family kept rising as well. From her original place several dozen steps down, she had risen to ninth in the past two years. Even if he had not stepped out back there, Celine would not have gone down so easily, she would surely have her own way of dealing with it.

“Magnetic Field is the weakest faction in the Federation of Energy Machinists, the Star Cloud that I’m in never got along with Black Blade, but if it weren’t for the conflict between the two of us, Magnetic Field would not have had a snowball’s chance in hell. So Magnetic Field can show off a bit in front of regular Energy Machinists, but to us, even if my family’s Energy Machinists aren’t all that impressive, compared to small fry like him, hmph…” Celine explained in detail. “Your Black Flood Party has Energy Machinists too, they’re also in Star Cloud. When you get back, you can ask if you get the chance. To people with large factions behind them like us, there’s no need to worry about trash like that at all, it’s good enough that we’re not dominating the streets like that.”

“You sure are direct.” Garen had more or less understand where he stood, and he knew now that after all that mess, they probably had a higher status that Baldhead. The shade under a large tree was wider, after all.

“I always was! If it wasn’t in a virtual space, and was in reality instead, I’d have offed him with one shot a long time ago!” Celine was still unhappy.

“Alright, if we have time, we can enter the special ability space together. I don’t have a teacher at all now, neither do I have an Energy Machine Imprint, so it’s not easy for me. Could you get me one?” said Garen with a smile.

“It’s not that easy to decide on an Energy Machine Imprint, if you decide on one, it’ll take up a slot in your Willpower. Two levels of Willpower can only support one Energy Machine Imprint, and once you’ve decided on it, it’s practically impossible to change it, no, it’s more than impossible!” said Celine solemnly. “I heard my teacher say that once you’ve decided on an Imprint, you have to be Inherited Level or higher before you can change it, and even then you’ll need to use up a ton of resources.”

Hearing Celine advise him so seriously, Garen also learned the importance of this, and his intention to carelessly look for one just to scrape by lessened.

“What are the prices of the Energy Machine Imprints like?”

“They’re usually between two to five billion units each, and these are the lower grade ones. Many people want the better ones, and Energy Machinists are all pretty loaded, so once the competition gets heated, the price can vary drastically. At the highest point, a decent Imprint even sold for more than forty billion. As for the even better ones, the peak-level Imprints, don’t even think about them, no one will even sell them. It takes a lot of time and effort to create one of these, to an Energy Machinist, it’s a long and pointless effort. Without up to a hundred years, don’t even think about creating a stable Imprint. That’s why the Imprints we’re using now were mostly the product of our elders’ efforts from more than a hundred years ago.”

Garen was beginning to see how complicated the field of Energy Machinists was.

“Give me a copy of your info regarding Energy Machinists.”

“Sure. I’ll arrange it and hand it to you later.” Celine nodded.

After hanging up, Garen quickly received all sorts of basic info about Energy Machinists. And he had a better understanding of the whole deal with Energy Machinists now too.

Energy Machinists mostly formed units according to the teacher, students, and the workshop, the different numbers of styles resulted in the workshops forming many different parties.

One workshop could consist of just one Energy Machinist, or it could have many, depending on the scale.

Energy Machine Imprints were tools Energy Machinists created to support themselves, at first they were just very normal high-functioning support tools, but after many generations of improvement and distillation of Willpower, the power of the Energy Machine Imprints grew stronger and stronger, and gradually more perfect. That was why Imprints with a longer duration of Inheritance tended to be stronger, and many Energy Machinists who could not afford ready-made Imprints also resorted to creating their own. But those may just be empty white boards, that required using Willpower to carve and strengthen step by step, from the very beginning. These had no strengthening effect at all.

So the longer the duration of Inheritance, the stronger the Imprint. Some Imprints had even become the foundations of many parties.

Energy Machinists did not interact much with each other normally either, they tended to research their own thing, and only gather on specific dates, exchanging knowledge and making deals for items and Imprints through the special ability space.

In other words, the Energy Machine Imprint was just like a pilot’s personal Mech, its importance could not be overstated.

The difference was that every Energy Machinist was not just limited to one, they could have multiple Imprints.

In the time after that, as expected, Baldhead, who was killed off, made no ripples whatsoever. He had evidently been suppressed by Celine’s power, he was just a small fry from the lower levels of Magnetic Field, compared to the elite of a large family and party on this side, the difference was decided instantly.

The days passed one after the other, and soon, the day of the auction was upon them.

The Ring Light Silver auction that Garen had been waiting for all this time had finally arrived.

Chapter 920: Auction 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The auction will take place in a remote mansion deep within the mountain forests of the Blackboard Region.

On the surface, it was just a lonely white private vacation home, but five hundred meters underground, there was a huge square underground space.

The space was like a giant opera house, with thick red carpets adorned with gold patterns, and neat lines of white seats arranged compactly. On the two sides, there were many floating box seats, they were just suspended light golden spheres, with the fixed number of each box carved on the outside.

Just then, the lower seats of the auction were almost completely packed with people, most of them properly dressed, the so-called upper classes. There were also others who did not sweat the details and dressed like the normal people on the street. The sounds of whispers and the buzz of voices kept echoing through the whole area.

The important guests on the two sides were also beginning to enter their boxes now.

Garen and Celine appeared at the leaping point to enter the room on the left, and they followed the path, walking towards one of the boxes.

There were quite a few VIPs like them, and all of them were walking along the walls on the sides to enter their boxes now.

“Looks like the organizer of this auction is a pretty big deal.” Garen swept his gaze across the area. The people in front and behind him were all the sort of hotshot characters you saw on the television. There was a constant stream of celebrities and public figures as well.

Some of the young students with considerable backgrounds that they were familiar with were here as well. Of course, he was also one such student with a considerable background, so he was no different from these prodigies and elites.

“Are you going to use your alias Garen, or your real name to bid?” asked Celine in a low voice beside him.

“My real name, I guess, quite a few people know me here.” Garen smiled. These past two years, Celine also knew that his alias was Garen.

“Nono.” Suddenly a voice came from not far ahead, it was a beautiful woman dressed in a black cocktail dress who turned around to smile at them, while standing with two men. The voice came from the beautiful lady.

“It’s Vivienne and Wade.” Garen smiled as he greeted them. These two were the people he worked with for the Rainbow Stone business. At first, they did not get along so well because they were just business partners, but after that, they began to familiarize with each other, and their relationship grew better. Even so, they were barely just normal friends.

Vivienne was pretty calculative for a woman, back when they were haggling prices, she showed that she had considerable business acumen. These two years, she had been developing very nicely as well and was getting hold of more resources and channels within the family.

The Sina family that Vivienne belonged to had wide connections and influences in Blackboard and even several of the regions around it. Although their higher-ups were not particularly powerful, their influence was spread extremely wide. They were a large-scale power, just beneath the peak-level factions.

Garen looked at the last person. He was dressed in a normal grey suit, with short grey hair, and looked like a very young, pretty boy.

“This is?”

“My friend, Penton.”

Vivienne introduced with a smile.

Penton reached out his hand to shake Garen’s lightly.

“Nice to meet you.”

“Yeah, nice to meet you too,” Garen replied with a smile, the latest information instantly appearing in his head. Rumor had it that Vivienne fancied a regular young man with no background despite her family’s objections and nearly broke it off with her family members. Looking at it now, this young man called Penton was standing beside Vivienne, and their stances seemed to be hinting that they were dating, so this could likely be that rumored boyfriend.

Although Garen did not know why she would bring a normal man with no background or talent here, he still greeted them politely.

Seeing Garen’s actions, gratitude flashed through Vivienne’s eyes.

She had already taken Penton to meet several young talents and young heirs from the upper classes, but the only one who treated them equally without contempt was Garen.

“Celine, you are very beautiful today.” Vivienne looked at Celine beside him. The whole Blackboard Region knew about the relationship between Nonosiva and Celine, those busybodies mostly arranged the two of them into a couple, and they were considered to be very well-matched. However, the two people themselves had no such intention.

“You’re very pretty too, Vivienne,” Celine nodded and said with a smile. She was wearing a large white knitted coat, wrapped tightly around her like a jacket, and her hair was plaited into an intricate, elegant lady’s style. On one side, her green hair was tied into small, uniform braids and pinned to her head, whereas the other side was a simple bun. Two white pearl studs stood out on her earlobes. She looked magnificent and cold.

“I went to the Polar Region’s Wellforest Mountains a while ago, and found a pretty decent project regarding Frigid Stones, are you two interested?” Beside them, Wade never stopped talking about business.

“I think I’ll pass, if you’re not doing business with Vivienne, I wouldn’t dare to invest haphazardly,” said Celine relentlessly.

Garen, on the other hand, just laughed.

“Give me the market report after some time, I’ll consider.”

Wade was instantly overjoyed and began to talk endlessly about his business plan with Garen.

“Vivienne, it’s been a while.”

They were about turn around and walk towards their box seats when someone else greeted them from behind.

Turning around, Vivienne’s expression turned cold.

“Brenforst.”

The blonde man behind them held a folding fan in his hand as he smiled, two middle-aged pilots following behind him. Waves of Level Three Willpower spread from them slowly, both of them were actually Level Three pilots.

To normal people, a Level Three pilot was already a very formidable presence, and Vivienne’s family was not a peak-level one. Her own bodyguards were only at the same level, so this guy was obviously equal to her in standing.

“I wonder, how are your preparations going for the exchange meeting this time? The man beside you is your so-called beau, right?” Brenforst was a genius among the Blackboard Region’s business circles.

Actually, even though the circles were extremely large in the Blackboard Region, the people inside at a certain level were still the same familiar old faces.

“You don’t have to worry,” said Vivienne with a cold laugh. “I won’t disappoint you at the exchange meeting.”

“That puts my mind at ease.” Brenforst smiled as he nodded, and walked past their group. He did not know Celine or Garen, perhaps he had heard of them, but he had never met them in person. Celine and Garen actually belonged in a circle one level higher than theirs.

“The people here are all heirs from powerful families, or else they are elites from large factions with considerable backgrounds. I wonder, this boy that Miss Vivienne has brought today, what right do you have to join our circle?”

Someone else spoke from behind, as they walked out of a leaping point and came out of a room.

The voice made even Brenforst, who was about to leave, turn around to watch the show.

The one who spoke was dressed in a white suit, and his eyes were piercing, giving off a sharp aura.

“Jacht, since when have you had the right to speak in my matters?” said Vivienne icily.

The man in the white suit, Jacht, laughed coldly.

“Vivienne, get that boy to speak for himself, what kind of a man hides behind a woman?”

Vivienne’s expression was freezing cold, and she was about to speak, but Penton, who was standing beside her, reached out his hand to stop her. He stepped out instead.

“And what right do you have to speak to me? Other than your family background, you’re just a piece of trash.”

“Trash?” Jacht’s expression changed.

“How dare you!” A middle-aged man stepped up from behind him, and reached out his arm fiercely, pressing for Penton’s head.

His fingers were sharp, and actually seemed to glow slightly blue, they had evidently been strengthened by some mutated genetic liquid. They even left a sweet fragrance in the air as they sliced through, making those who smelled it feel dizzy.

“Scram!!” Penton did not give way at all, blocking with one hand in front of him. His arm suddenly bulged, his whole hand growing one size larger. Like a monster, his skin turned green-grey, the green veins popping.

Bam!

The two arms crashed into each other, and the middle-aged man was actually forced back, taking three steps back before he could steady himself.

“What strength!” someone gasped in admiration.

Everyone looked towards his feet and saw that the middle-aged man had left three clear footsteps in the hardwood floor. It was evidently the marks left behind by his trying to divert the momentum.

“Martial arts powerhouse!” Jacht’s eyes narrowed. Clearly, he was angry for real this time.

Garen and Celine stood at the sidelines and watched, with no intention of interfering whatsoever. For one, this conflict was completely meaningless, and even boring, in their eyes. Also, Jacht’s own status was not at the same level as theirs.

“Nono.” Suddenly, Celine yanked Garen’s sleeve. “Over there.” She gestured with her eyes and looked towards the opposite direction of the corridor.

Garen followed her gaze, and saw, on the corridor to the box seat opposite them, Fila looking back at them calmly, dressed in white. There was someone beside him, skinny and pale, short in stature. He seemed to be young, and looked like a drug addict, weak and powerless, and completely unenergetic.

This young man frowned as he looked in Garen’s direction, and saw Garen and Celine as well. His eyes lit up slightly when he saw Celine, but other than that, he just hugged the pretty woman beside him and walked into the box seat, as though completely disregarding Garen’s and Celine’s statuses.

“Who’s that person next to Fila?” Garen frowned slightly.

“I’m not sure, I’ll get someone to investigate right now.” Celine sensed something amiss as well. Although Fila did not dare to make a move against Garen directly due to the pressure from Black Flood, that guy had plenty of tricks up his sleeve, so they had to be careful.

The group entered the box seats, and by the time Garen and Celine left, the conflict between Vivienne and Jacht had escalated slightly. That young man called Penton actually went toe-to-toe, not allowing Jacht to get back at him at all, and was somehow keeping his own against the two bodyguards.

Shockingly, this young man was actually a Level Two pilot. Although his Willpower was not very strong, he could still take more than a hit from Level Three Willpower. Add that to his powerful martial arts, and he never backed down, from the start to the finish.

This gave Garen and the others a fairly good impression of him, but it also angered some of the other upper-class heirs that some kid from a regular family would actually look down on them as a whole.

That guy just kept saying that you upper-class boys were all trash! You’re nothing without that layer of skin, and he insulted them from all aspects, instantly inviting all of their hatred!

Even Celine, who was sitting beside them, occasionally felt like punching someone. The sounds from outside kept coming through the open door, but soon enough, things slowly calmed down. Vivienne’s older brother, her cousin Azeria appeared, and calmed down the conflict between them. Plus, the auction was about to begin, so both sides entered their boxes and said no more. The grudge remained, however.

“Previously Vivienne’s Cina family and Jacht’s Duncan family ran into some arguments regarding economic distribution, and tempers ran high on both sides. That’s why Jacht also wanted to attack them using the unsavory fact that Vivienne was dating a commoner,” explained Celine nonchalantly as she sat down and took a gulp from her drink.

“There have been a lot of changes within the region lately, the military items market keeps on expanding, and our collaborative business is doing better by the day. If it weren’t for the fact that the benefits from her project with you keep increasing, she would surely have been pulled down from the position of manager a long time ago. Looks like it’s all thanks to you,” said Celine with a laugh.

“T’was just a coincidence.” Garen shrugged and pressed a button, the room door instantly closing automatically. “The auction this time might be slightly troublesome, I only have one and a half billion in mobile assets, so I might not be able to get what I want.”

“I can provide a billion on my side, if that’s not enough, I can use my identity to pay a certain portion in advance. I’m just worried Fila will probably try to make things harder for you!” said Celine in a low voice.

“Yeah, I can’t possibly give up the Ring Light Silver, and Fila probably knows that too. We can’t underestimate his intelligence division.”

Pak pak pak!

Suddenly, a row of blinding white lights was instantly switched on outside, shining down on the main stage.

“The auction has officially begun, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Earth’s Heart Auction Center!” A high man’s voice rose suddenly, his tone as though singing.

Chapter 921: Auction and Ambush 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After that excited announcement, the whole auction was bathed in bright white light, the powerful spotlights all around them lighting up one by one.

Bam!!

A ring of fire abruptly exploded on the very front of the stage, like a rocket shooting into the sky.

The platinum-colored flames fell slowly with time, fading, and then a handsome man, tall and slender, and dressed in white, appeared on the stage without anyone else noticing.

He raised his arms high, and bent his waist, bowing low towards the crowd below him.

“Welcome, everyone, to the auction.”

“I am Earl Platinum. I believe that everyone here understands just how precious time is, so I will not beat around the bush, let us now go to the main topic of the night.” The man snapped his fingers loudly.

Two large men carried a white box from the side onto the stage. The box had deep patterns engraved onto it, and in these path-like craters, there were actually several thin platinum-colored snakes.

The live snakes kept swimming regularly through the pathways, with no intention of escaping the box.

“The first Serpent Crate, Light of Frenya, the mysterious crown originating from Frenya. Apparently, it has magical rays that can prolong one’s youth.”

White smoke sprayed out of the crate slowly, revealing a slightly small platinum crown resting in the middle of black swan down.

“Bidding begins at sixty million. Starting from now!”

“Are you interested?” Garen looked at Celine with a laugh.

“I’m not that kind of idiotic woman who puts everything else aside just to make myself look good all the time,” Celine clicked her tongue, picked up her drink, and took a sip from it. “Rather than using so much money to buy a white elephant like that, I might as well just go for one round of Genetic Amelioration.”

Garen did not comment further, and just turned his attention downward, without making an offer.

The bidding below had already begun, and as expected, all the voices bidding were female. Such an intricate crown could not even be worn out once bought, so he had no idea why these people were trying to buy it.

Soon enough, the crown was successfully sold, and they proceeded to the next Snake Crate.

“The second Snake Crate, Auto-Equip Armor, also known as Mech Armor, it’s a must-have for powerful pilots. Bidding starts at three hundred million.”

This caught Garen’s eye somewhat, but he knew of it as well. Auto-Equip Armor had always been something only Inherited Level pilots could use. He did not even have his own specialized Mech yet, it was still far too early for him.

Soon enough, this thing was bought by a merchant with a large pot belly, evidently not for his own use. It was very likely meant to be a gift.

The third item followed closely after that, and the fourth. They were all just rare gems, nothing else special.

By the sixth item, the box seat opposite theirs finally made a move.

The VIP in the first box seat obtained this Snake Crate, even before the crate was opened, he just bought it for ten times the starting price. No one knew what was inside.

That did cause some ripples through the auction.

The few items after that were all bought away by the VIPs in the box seats, and the prices grew higher and higher as well. A completely average vase was even raised to a terrifying price of one point six billion.

“Maybe some higher-up from some family is here, otherwise they would not have such buying ability,” said Celine with a laugh.

“I hear that some of the family leaders of the smaller families will even come here in person, using all their assets to bid for some things. I never thought that it might very well be true.” Garen shook his head. “The next one is the Ring Light Silver I want.”

“I hope everything goes well, our highest budget is two and a half billion, if we can’t buy it with that much, then we’ll have no chance.” Celine nodded, Ring Light Silver usually would not exceed a hundred million per ton, but now Garen was desperately in need of a large amount of the stuff. If someone interfered with the bidding, it was very likely that the price would increase to a troublesome amount.

“The next Snake Crate is something everyone is familiar with, the one everyone knows as a rare and precious material – Ring Light Silver!!! Ten tons!!”

The host started yelling loudly.

The crate beside him spewed white smoke slowly, and opened up, revealing a clean white bank storage receipt for the Ring Light Silver.

“These ten tons of Ring Light Silver are the greatest essence that we at the auction discovered in some mountains deep with the dangerous radiation zone. They have not been cut, or modified by radiation in any way! Completely original, with no trace of any preservatives guaranteed~! Bidding starts at, five hundred million!!”

“It’s half that of market price, if no one offers for it, the auction would have lost big,” said Celine with a laugh, when she heard the price from below.

“No way, this thing was shipped here especially for customers like us, it’d be weird if there were no offers for it,” Garen laughed, and pressed the panel in front of him lightly.

“One billion.”

A calm voice appeared on the site.

“One billion! Box Number Five offers one billion, is anyone willing to go higher! This is a complete piece of ten-ton Ring Light Silver, once in a hundred years. If it was diluted and used according to standard measurements, it could increase a hundred standard issue Mechs by 0.2 levels!!” roared the host.

“One point one billion!” Someone made an offer.

“One point five billion!” Garen said directly, raising to price to a terrifying extent. It was instantly approaching the highest bidding price yet, of one point six billion.

The place was also starting to grow rowdy, countless gazes focusing on Box Number Five, as though guessing who the person inside could possibly be.

In another box seat opposite them.

Fila and that thin, weak young man were sitting side by side, both of them accompanied by a half-naked beauty, and currently they were looking down at the auction beneath them.

“Remington, that’s Ring Light Silver, if you want to create a powerful, high-quality luxury private battleship for yourself, then Ring Light Silver is more suitable than Dream Gold. They’re both memory metals, but the silver’s memory regeneration abilities are superior to Dream Gold’s. Although it may not be hard enough, you can use it for a long time without having to repair or maintain it too often, so it can save you a lot of effort. Of course, the price is just as high,” suggested Fila with a smile.

“It’s just as high? That’s okay, my principle has always been to buy expensive things, rather than the right things,” said the thin man proudly, his chin raised. “It won’t do if it’s too cheap, that will damage my status and reputation.”

He tapped the panel in front of him.

“Two billion!”

The reporting of the price instant destroyed the previous highest price of one point five billion.

“Box Number Two offers two billion! Two billion!!” The host was getting even more excited, evidently even he had never seen a price as high as twenty billion. It just went up by five hundred million just like that, evidently that person had cash to spare.

Garen’s expression went cold and he stared at Box Number Two opposite him. If he remembered correctly, that was the place Fila had gone in.

“Someone’s playing games.” Beside him, Celine’s expression grew cold as well, and she smiled coldly. “It is Fila, as I thought.”

“It might not be just playing around,” Garen shook his head slightly. “Two point five billion!”

He put down his bid immediately, raising the price to the highest he could take.

There was no way he could gather so much Ring Light Silver on the market, several dozens of kilograms would already be fortunate, so he needed these ten tons of Ring Light Silver!

Rather than increasing the price slowly, he would rather increase it by five hundred million at once, letting the opponent think he still had plenty left in his budget so that they would retreat rather than risk both sides losing out.

But unfortunately, and contrary to Garen’s expectations, the other party raised the bid.

“Three billion!” a calm voice said.

The whole place erupted, and the noise grew louder. Three billion, that price was already far beyond what these ten tons of Right Light Silver should cost. The discussions grew louder and louder, anyone who attended the auction here was definitely rich, but three billion was already more than half of some people’s entire fortunes, so it was completely normal that this would incite a frenzy of discussion.

Inside the box seat, Garen’s expression was dark.

“I can still use five million that my family gave in advance…” Celine said quietly beside him.

Garen raised his hand, telling her that she should stop talking. Then he tapped the panel lightly.

“Three billion… Fila, are you trying to pick a fight?”

“What do you mean, picking a fight? It’s an auction, I’m just bidding like usual, if you don’t have money then scram, don’t embarrass yourself here!” Fila cold laugh came from the other side.

Garen narrowed his eyes. “You must know, that no matter how good something is, you better make sure you’re alive to enjoy it…”

“Are you threatening me?!” Fila’s voice was icy.

The two of them were in direct conflict, their voices clashing through the bidding equipment, as though sparks were actually flying.

The others in the auction hall were all interested as well, it was rare to see a butting of heads like this.

“Nonosiva, you think you’re so f*cking great, don’t you?” Suddenly, a rather feeble voice was broadcasted across the area as well. “No matter how mad you are, you’re still a dog belonging to our Black Flood! What right do you have to be so cocky!”

“And who the hell are you! How dare you speak to me like that?” Garen’s expression was approaching sub-zero.

“The hell are you! Why don’t you run on back and ask your teacher who the hell I am! How dare a dog bark crazily in front of their master, I’ll break your legs, all three of them!” The voice on the other side was growing more and more furious.

“Even your teacher doesn’t dare to talk like that in front of me, who the f*ck do you think you are! Son of a bitch! If we weren’t at this place, you watch out, I’ll squash you as soon as you leave!”

Garen’s expression grew stormier and stormier. These past few years, he kept climbing the ranks, but his abilities did not improve as much. That was already reason for him to be in a bad mood, but now there was such an arrogant piece of trash blocking his way forward.

“I found it!” said Celine suddenly beside him. “The one talking is one of the higher-ups from your Black Flood Party!”

Garen turned off the panel and heard the other side cursing loudly again.

“Who is he?”

“The son of the Black Flood Party’s seventh Divine Wind General, Remington!”

Bam!!

Garen smashed his fist into the armrest, and the armrest made of alloy actually bent under the force.

“Nono!” Celine frowned deeply, shaking her head at him. “Control yourself, there’s a Resonance pilot on the other side! And more than just one! Your senior brother won’t stand out for you either. The Divine Wind Generals are too powerful!”

Garen took a deep breath, right now it was true that he did not have the right to fight this person. Divine Wind Generals, only fighter pilots above Level Six in the Black Flood Party had the right to claim the title of Divine Wind General. It was not just merely a title, you needed extreme power to be able to shoulder it. Even among the Inherited Level pilots, only the ones at the very top had the right to that title.

“The Seventh Divine Wind General, if I’m not mistaken, he should be from the faction opposing ours.” Garen took a deep breath.

“I forfeit this bid,” Garen said softly, pressing the panel.

“Atta boy, a dog should act like a dog! A disobedient dog will be beaten to death by their master,” Remington’s cocky voice came from the opposite box.

“I hope the Seventh Divine Wind General can protect you all forever…” Garen said coldly, and then got up and walked away.

“What a joke, you’re just trash who can’t even reach Resonance Level!”

Garen did not reply to that. If he stayed for any longer, he would just be humiliating himself. He could not bother them, and they stood in the way of what he needed most, so there was no point in staying any longer.

Celine got up as well, and their leaving made the lights in the box go off.

The two of them followed the path and reached the leaping point room. And at the same time, Remington successfully obtained the item he was bidding for.

“The Seventh Divine Wind General has made a move as well, he’s obviously preparing to suppress you.”

“Not necessarily, consider his position, there’s no point to him suppressing a junior like me. He has his own descendants too, wouldn’t he be worried about my teacher’s faction opposing him as well? That will just lead to losses on both sides.” Garen shook his head slightly.

“That’s not for sure either, the Seventh Divine Wind General was always an arrogant one, he never did care about preserving face or the like,” said Celine softly, according to the information she had found.

“What do you plan to do now that you didn’t get the Ring Light Silver you were looking for?”

“Are there any other channels?” asked Garen.

“No, there’s no more Ring Light Silver, you can only a lower level metal to replace it.”

“If I don’t use Ring Light Silver, the Mech will be weaker in functionality, and later I’ll need to upgrade it with different materials. That’s too bad, if I had Ring Light Silver, I wouldn’t need to change materials even after I reach Inherited Level,” sighed Garen.

“What do you plan to do?” asked Celine softly. “Do you want to get someone to intercept and rob them?”

Chapter 922: Auction and Ambush 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“If I made a move now, even an idiot would know I was the one behind it.” Garen was speechless. “Plus there are two Resonance pilots here, if their Mechs are excellent as well, it will be very troublesome. Even I might be no match for them.”

“True, and Fila is here too. His power is near Two Moons Level, so he’s a huge threat as well.” Celine frowned too.

“Unless, I could mobilize large-scale forces to raid them, bring out the brigade. But that may result in many casualties.” Garen took a deep breath. As a Captain in the army who fought alone, he also had an independent squad under his leadership. After two years of selections and training, the members were now all powerful pilots, at least Level Three or above. Some of them were even Level Five like him, and were just slightly weaker in combat power. And there were many more people in the squad than there were when they raided Red-White two years ago. Perhaps it was due to special wartime privileges, but there were more than seventy members in the squad, more than seventy of the strongest students from all the different schools.

After they were brought together by mutual benefit, Garen also successfully built bonds between these pilots, so that they had the same goals in mind, and all swore loyalty to him.

Such a force, driving Mechs to attack a bunch of Resonance pilots with no Mechs, could easily result in a one-sided slaughter as long as they had good battle ethics. Pilots without Mechs could only rely on their Willpower’s attacking skill, but that had too short a range, and faced with the Mech’s complete dominance in all areas, it would be no fight at all.

Of course, the other side was politically powerful as well, but there was one very important point, being that the area closest to this auction was Garen’s territory.

Garen was slightly hesitant as well, wondering if he should go ahead and rob them of the Ring Light Silver. Once he did that, the conflict now would instantly escalate, and he was not mentally prepared to face off against a Divine Wind General yet.

In the two years, his Living Secret Technique, the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, had already reached a very crucial point. It was now over 90% complete, perhaps he could soon break past this level’s extremely slow progress pace.

But according to the latter part of the Living Secret Technique records, the seventh and eighth levels after the sixth all required a lot of time and devouring to advance steadily, so they were not something he could accomplish in a short time. After all, the peak of the eighth level should be the theoretical Army Level power.

According to Garen’s calculations, the Army Level should be equivalent to Inherited Level and above in this world, but he did not know which level within the Inherited system it would reach.

Similarly, it was not that easy to reach Inherited Level. It required a lot of time and an increase in understanding.

“Once I reach the seventh grade, the Living Secret Technique will probably change completely. And I have the ingredients prepared for my Biochemical Pool, and I finally found the most critical one, the Mila Cells. When I match the Biochemical Pool with the Living Secret Technique, I wonder how they will change…”

Garen had already prepared the ingredients for more than two years, but he never found that key item, the Mila Cells.

That was the main reproductive cell in the Biochemical Pool, it constructed the main body. It always came from the middle of some strange rocks that grew in the radiation belt, so it was also known as Stoneheart Flesh. Eating it could greatly strengthen someone’s vitality, prolong their lifespan, and it could only be kept for a very short time, like five days.

That was why Garen could never find suitable Mila Cells.

“Do you want to grab it or not! I can mobilize some of my family’s forces to help as well, we probably can’t stop them from leaving, but if you want to grab that heavy Ring Light Silver, it shouldn’t be a problem,” said Celine softly.

“There’s no rush, once the auction is over, just pay constant attention to their transport route.” A hint of flint flashed through Garen’s eyes. “I’ll go ask my teacher first.”

“Alright.”

There was a fountain of white light spewing from underneath the leaping point and engulfing the two of them. In an instant, the white light vanished, and the two of them disappeared from the leaping point as well.

*****************************

The radiation belt outside the Blackboard Region

On the wide grey-black grassy plains, the sun was setting, the red twilight rays casting a layer of golden-red all over everything.

A black convoy lined up like a long snake, driving out endlessly from the entrance checkpoint into Blackboard, driving out endlessly into the white veil that separated the region from the radiation belt. It was as though they had come out of a foam filter, the many large heavy-duty trucks rumbling along, headed towards the distant grasslands.

The commanding soldier at the checkpoint waited until the last heavy truck had left before he finally put down the automatic wall behind the veil of light slowly, surrounding the whole Blackboard Region once more.

There were many levitating airships on each side of the convoy, and one black-armored guard standing on each airship. They each held long machine guns in their hands, and had curved warswords in their hands. Their left eyes twinkled with a faint red light, as they constantly scanned the movements around them.

There was no cargo inside the hold of one large truck in the middle of the convoy. Instead, it was decorated into a comfortable lounge for resting and chatting. Looking through the cracks in the windows and the curtains now, you could see some people partying, drinking, and singing inside.

Far away from the convoy, there were several small black dots hiding behind the small hill rising from the plains, watching the moving convoy from afar. These small dots were actually several pitch-black tall humanoid Mechs.

Two of the Mechs were hiding behind the hill, and seemed to be the leaders of the lot.

“It’s confirmed, the mission is to kill Fila and all the Mech guards in there. If you can’t do that, destroy the radiation protection, then they’ll all become radiation people,” said the leader coldly.

“Leader, are we really going to do it? The opponents are Resonance pilots at the peak of Full Moon,” the assistant pilot beside him said quietly.

“Riches come with risks, as long as he doesn’t have his Mech, and he’s not Inherited Level, what’s there to be scared of!? And after that we can get a billion in rewards. Once this gig is over, we call go back and live peacefully, we won’t have to live life on the edge anymore,” said the leader calmly. “So even if I know there’s a high chance we can’t make it back, and we’re being used as scouts to test the opponent, I have no other choice.”

He looked at the convoy moving slowly in the distance.

“I’m forty now, my talents have reached their limit. There’s no point in continuing to fight, so I might as well end on a bang, we’ll take this load and call it quits!”

His Mech gave a jolt, and the faint force of a Level Four pilot was released slowly.

Similarly, all the Mechs around him emitted Level Four forces slowly. They were the elite force that Garen had carefully chosen and gathered over the past two years. At first these had all been killer pilots who had committed crimes, but Garen used his position and the wartime bureaucracy to secretly bail them out with money, so that they were now one of his secret assets.

But now, this force was going out as cannon fodder just to test Fila and the others.

“Move out.” A pale blue light appeared slowly on the back of the leader’s Mech.

Similarly, the other Mechs replied dully, all their Mechs lighting up with a faint blue light from the back.

Boom!!

At the same time, a large amount of blue flames sprayed out of the engine exhaust, more than ten Mechs shooting into the air at once. The Level Four forces rumbled towards the black convoy.

Of these, the three elites, the strongest fighters and the leader, were placed in the very middle of the team, heading straight for the car in the middle, the one Fila was on.

“Enemy ambush!!”

As soon as a guard Mech rang the alarm, it was shot directly in the cockpit, and fell on its back.

Most of the guard Mechs were also dispatched with at the first possible moment, but just as these guards were going to fall completely. A powerful Level Five force quickly rushed out of one of the heavy truck holds.

Barroom, the hold was shattered, and there was actually a clean white Mech curled up inside. The Mech’s eyes lit up with a faint green light, and then it suddenly stretched out, shooting out like a bolt of lightning.

“Insects!” Fila’s voice came booming out of the Mech, with extreme arrogance and contempt.

Several high-powered lasers shot the surface of his cockpit, but they were blocked by a layer of transparent light, so he remained completely unharmed.

Backhandedly, he pulled out a large blade that was completely silver and bright.

“Thunder Snake Slash!”

A bolt of blue-purple lightning flashed across the sky above the convoy. At lightning speed, it landed on three of the ambushing Mechs.

Bam bam bam!

The three Mechs burst into fireballs and crashed down at the same time.

“It’s Fila! Damn it! The Mech was hidden in the cargo hold!” When the three of them including the leader saw Fila appear, they were instantly shocked out of their wits, and turned around to run.

On the other side, Fila laughed coldly, swinging his blade and effortless releasing yet another bolt of blue-purple lightning, demolishing several more black Mechs in the ambush.

The Full-Moon Level powerhouse was practically unbeatable. Forget these average Level Four pilots, even those three strongest ones, at the peak of Level Four, could not even take a hit.

He strode towards the three Mechs, chasing them, the blade in his hand crackling like thunder as he slashed a Mech beside him. He was unstoppable!

Just then, other than Fila, two more Resonance Mechs flew out slowly, slaughtering the black Mechs that were here on an ambush.

Fila laughed coldly as he chased down the three strongest Mechs.

“You’re already here, so why would you try to run? Level Four pilot killers, I wonder if Nonosiva will regret it if they were all lost!”

His Mech quickly caught up to the three Mechs at the front.

But just then, a strange force abruptly spread from the three Mechs at the front.

Ba-thump!

Fila’s expression changed slightly, suddenly realizing that the Willpower force fields around the three Mechs ahead had started to distort violently. Their Mechs instantly froze in mid-air, as though they could self-explode at any time.

He quickly stopped his Mech, maintaining his distance. After all, if their Willpower exploded together with their Mechs, the impact would be terrifying. Even as he was now, his Defense Field would be greatly reduced. For the sake of several regular Level Four pilots he could destroy at any time, it was not worth it.

Ba-thump!

There was another muffled sound from three Mechs. That force field was like a heartbeat, but it was far beyond a normal human pulse, as though it was a giant drum, strangely deep and impactful.

“Ah– Aaaaahhhh–!!”

All of a sudden, terrifying screams came from the three Mechs ahead.

As the screams went on, inside the three Mechs, the skin of the three Level Four peak pilots kept rippling and distorting, as though there were countless insects crawling under their skin. Their eyes kept bulging, extremely bloodshot. As the screams continued, hard black scales began to grow all over their bodies slowly. The many scales covered every inch of their body surface.

At the same time, their hearts all beat once, and their skin simply burst open. Countless blue-black slimy tentacles whooshed out of from inside, waving around in the air.

Instantly, the Willpower inside their bodies began to expand and mutate, increasing madly from the peak of Level Four to Level Five… Mid Level Five… Peak Level Five.

And as they continued to mutate, the nature of their Willpower somehow also began to change drastically in a terrifying way.

Their bodies, including their Mechs, all began to emit a deep blue Cold Radiation.

The three Mechs began to slouch slightly, their arms hanging down, and they panted terrifyingly, like wild beasts.

Fila narrowed his eyes, staring at the strange changes occuring in the three Mechs in front of him. He did not believe that these tiny Peak Level Four pilots could harm him through any methods, but the effect of this strange mutation had stunned him slightly as well. From Peak Level Four, they had instantly reached Peak Level Five, this was such a terrifying increase in Willpower. And the three Mechs had even automatically formed a Level Five Willpower Defense Field.

Whoosh… waves of Cold Radiation blew towards him, and even Fila felt his heart grow slightly cold.

“These are just Level Four pilots, too… What if they were Level Five…?” Staring at the three mutated Mechs in front of him, he could not help but feel a chill, deep in his heart.

Chapter 923: Counterattack 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Are mutated measures like these secret methods or medicine?”

A similar thought had crossed Fila’s mind recently. Suddenly, from the bottom of his field of vision, he saw two blue curved lines shooting downwards from mid-air that nearly hit the surface of his Mech Body.

“Screen!!” he growled softly.

The Willpower Defense Field System firmly formed in front of his body and became much more substantial. It blocked both of the blue curved lines that flew towards his face. The lines did not budge against his force field for a few moments but disappeared slowly after that.

Meanwhile, two of the three Bodies in front of him had apparently disappeared without a trace while two shadows appeared beside him on both sides. Both of them held daggers and pierced them into Fila’s waist instantly. Cold blue air wafted out of the sharp blades faintly.

For unknown reasons, the speed of both of these Bodies became abnormally fast. They were now more than one and a half times faster than they were previously. When Fila reacted, the edges of their blades had already pierced through his Willpower Field.

“Roll!!”

A sense of crisis had arrived and he roared frantically as his Willpower Field twisted itself quickly and stopped the two daggers that flew towards him on both sides.

He stretched both of his arms and held the head of one Body with each of them. He smashed them together brutally so that both of the Bodies in front of him collided against one other in the middle.

At this moment, he was overcome with intense feelings of danger suddenly. Fila did not even have enough time to think before he dashed upwards into the sky in an attempt to flee further away from these two Level Five Bodies. However, he was one step too late.

Boom boom!!!

Two loud explosions could be heard suddenly as the fragments of his Willpower rolled away in a frenzy with the flames throughout their surroundings in a range of more than ten meters. As he was unable to escape in time, Fila was violently swept away as well.

The tremendous explosive force of the impact shook Fila’s Willpower Field to the verge of collapse, almost destroying it completely. After all, this was the full strength of the self-explosion of two first-rate Level Five Mech Pilots.

Just when he had almost breathed a sigh of relief, a huge explosion occurred right above his head and suddenly came down.

Fila raised his head and happened to see a crimson red fireball falling from the sky. It was about to fall and collide with his head directly like a fiery red shooting star.

Boom!!

In the sky above the grassy plains, a frontal collision occurred between the red shooting star and the White Body. The Body of Fila’s Mech was completely enveloped by flames, making it impossible for him to see anything clearly during that time.

When both of the Resonance Mechs from the convoy rushed over to assist him immediately, everything had ended already.

Both of them and a few remaining Bodyguard Mechs observed the exploding fireball but none dared to approach it too closely.

“This is the impact of the self-destruction of Level Five Mech Pilots. They knew much earlier that Master Fila would be in the convoy!” said one of the Remington Mech Pilots softly with a pained look on his face.

“Pay attention to your surroundings at all times to prevent any more of the enemy’s sneak attacks!” yelled someone else.

The remaining bodyguards dispersed quickly and stood guard throughout their surroundings.

However, everyone’s attention was still focused on the gigantic red fireball that was suspended in mid-air. If anything happened to Fila, they would be in great danger regardless if they resumed their journey by continuing to go forward or by returning. If their enemy were able to dispatch formations and ambushes like this, it would definitely occur again once it had happened the first time. Without Fila’s support, the ending would be too ghastly to imagine.

The gigantic fireball that had a diameter of over ten meters finally dissipated.

A White Body that was stained with black burn marks appeared slowly. One of its arms was charred black while burning flames continued to dance on the Body. Some sticky-looking substances that were burning fell off its body and burned black holes of different sizes on the grassy plains below. They were clearly burning at frightening temperatures.

“Master Fila!”

“Are you alright? Master!”

Two Resonance Mech Pilots asked loudly.

“I’m fine…” Fila sat inside the cockpit with a slightly fearful look on his face. “When those three Level Five Mech Pilots destroyed themselves simultaneously, their powers were already enough to pierce through my Defense Fields, threatening the cockpit. Fortunately, I was able to block it by sacrificing one of my arms in the end.”

“They are forces that actually dare to oppose our convoy?!” said a flustered voice from the convoy suddenly. “Uncle Fila, how am I going to explain to Father if anything happens to you?”

Fila’s Mech Body raised its hand.

“Don’t worry, it’ll be fine once I return and fix it.” He sat inside the Cockpit with a solemn look on his face.

“Who would be so brave to actually ambush us?!”

“To think that someone would dare to ambush the convoy of Divine Wind Generals! Most people could not even imagine themselves being so brave!”

“But what if it’s someone within the Divine Wind Generals?” sneered Fila while interrupting the conversation between the others.

“Someone within Black Flood Party?” said a Resonance Mech Pilot before becoming silent and not daring to speak anymore. Within a giant like the Black Flood Party, each Divine Wind General was an Inherited Mech Pilot whose powers stretched over the two main territories and were unimaginably strong.

The other voices turned silent at once as well except for Remington who continued to curse.

However, his father did not have particularly many enemies. Nonetheless, one would naturally offend many people while on the path to reaching the level of a Divine Wind General. Most Divine Wind Generals would be unwilling to make their Level Five Mech Pilots kill themselves while ambushing a convoy. Therefore, he would not be able to guess the culprit either.

“Could it be that Nonosiva?” asked Remington angrily.

“It’s unlikely,” Fila shook his head slightly. “It would be impossible for him to gain such strength so quickly. I thought that it was caused by one of his people at first but I’m not so certain about that now. The ability to get three Level Five Mech Pilots to self-destruct immediately is not something that can be done by the average person. Even Divine Wind Generals would be pained by this.”

“Then who is it? If I find out who it is, I’ll be damned if I don’t get Father to slaughter all of them!” said Remington while displaying his own resentment. However, he did not sound truly furious as this matter was not any of his business. The real target of the enemy’s sneak attack was not him but Fila instead. Therefore, he was only anxious in the beginning but had steadied himself after that.

“Could it be him?” Fila narrowed his eyes and his gaze slightly.

****************************

“Failed.”

Garen was not shocked at all when he detected information from his Living Secret Technique that his Distorted Seed had disappeared.

He was currently taking turns with Celine while playing military chess calmly.

Both of them sat upright on the balcony outside Celine’s villa. A gentle breeze blew while soft music played comfortingly.

Celine who was sitting on the opposite side of him moved a chess piece with one hand while supporting her chin with the other as she yawned.

The afternoon sun shined on both of their bodies and made them feel slightly warm.

Garen lifted a chess piece gently and placed it on an empty spot that Celine was not paying attention to.

“Kill steal!”

“Ah, I lost again…” Celine looked on helplessly when her General piece was killed at once. Her hand swiped across the board and scattered the other pieces messily. “I don’t wanna play anymore. I keep losing despite playing for more than ten rounds. It’s meaningless now.”

“Then what do you want to play?” Garen smiled.

“I’ve learned the numbing ability that the bald guy used previously. Why don’t I show you once?” giggled Celine mysteriously at once.

“Are you talking about that Energy Machinist baldy who called himself a magnetic field?” asked Garen.

“Yes, that numbing ability was pretty neat. Although he used a consumable substance, it produced some pretty good effects by being able to paralyze others for two seconds,” Celine nodded. “However, it wasn’t effective enough against me!” she said with a confident look on her face.

“If it wasn’t for me previously, I’m afraid that he would’ve done all he could to molest you, right?” Garen shook his head while smiling.

“Bullshit!” Celine stood up. “I’ve made a huge pile of these toys so why don’t you take one now and try it?!”

Without even thinking, Garen already knew that this girl had definitely used a lot of these to create a resistance drug for herself. She had only come to him now after obtaining complete immunity.

This girl’s had always possessed an abnormally headstrong personality.

“I heard that Fila’s convoy was ambushed.” Garen changed the subject suddenly because he had too many matters to solve and simply did not have time to spend his day playing with Celine everywhere.

“Ambushed? How is he? Is he dead?” Celine became interested suddenly and sat down again.

“Fila is lightly wounded and Remington is fine. Meanwhile, more than half of the regular bodyguards are dead but the powerhouses are fine,” answered Garen matter-of-factly.

“What a shame”, Celine shook her head. Suddenly, she raised her head and glared at Garen again. “It wasn’t caused by someone you sent, right?”

“How would that be possible?!” Garen waved his hands continuously. “The attackers were Level Five Mech Pilots but so am I. Do you think that I’m able to influence such high leveled Mech Pilots? You’d need to know your limits even if you were joking!”

“I know, I know” Celine felt that this was unrealistic as well. “Whatever, it doesn’t matter whether he’s dead or not. Right, what do you plan to do since you don’t have enough Ring Light Silver? Your Appraisal”

“Without sufficient Ring Light Silver, I can only use some Level One items to substitute them this one time. Although its performance will suffer slightly because of this, I will just be careful to select those of best quality,” Garen shook his head. “Although my Appraisal is slightly lower than the other first-rate prodigies, I won’t face any problems achieving Level Five. As long as I reach Level Five and obtain my Exclusive Mech, I will be able to enter the Resonance Degrees. I will need to look at my developments while threading on the next path.”

“That’s true as well. As long as you achieve excellent Appraisal, your personal development will be the only obstacle that limits your advancement. Encounters, luck, and power are things that you cannot lack”, Celine nodded. “How are the preparations of the materials for your biochemical pool?”

“Almost done. I can begin constructing the cultivation immediately. It’s being done at an extremely fast speed and will be formed in two or three more days. Most of my time is being spent on looking for materials”, Garen said with a smile.

Regarding the biochemical pool, he was extremely looking forward to it because he was a Level Two Energy Machinist now.

“What about your Energy Machine Imprint? What have you chosen?” Celine continued to ask.

“I’ve already decided that the first one will be the Investigating Hawk. Its functions are more practical and I will be able to develop and evolve it to Level Two in the future. It’s not bad.”

All Energy Machine Imprints would start at low levels initially. Moreover, once they were determined, they would occupy a location that could form Imprints. For Energy Machinist, it was extremely important they could only produce a control space after every two levels. Therefore, it was an important step to decide which Energy Machine Imprint would be placed into the control space because they would need to pay an extremely heavy price if they wanted to change it in the future.

“There’s no need to rush, I’ll decide later once the biochemical pool is done”, said Garen casually while smiling. He was not anxious at all because he knew that he would be able to take a huge step and advance forward if he found an Energy Machine Imprint that could reproduce his powerful calculation abilities. Compared to most of the other Energy Machinists who did not have Energy Machine Imprints, they would only reach the standard of a Level One Energy Machinist after at least ten years of perseverance and calculation. Meanwhile, after relying on his powerful Intelligence Attribute, he was able to forcibly break through the large gap that seemed like a moat between him and the others within a short span of time. No one knew that he had surpassed these obstacles and obtained his Level Two Energy Machinist status merely within one or two years.

After chatting with Celine for awhile, Garen stood up and excused himself before sitting in the convoy that was surrounded by bodyguards and returning to his own villa.

Throughout the journey, he recalled the battle scenes that were transferred back to him through the Distorted Seed.

Other than the abilities of mutated creatures, he had not expected that the Distorted Seed possessed short-term sensory sharing abilities as well. This allowed him to temporarily witness the battle scenes.

“The three Level Four Mech Pilots that were hosts of the Distorted Seed parasites were actually upgraded to the peak of Level Five immediately. They even possessed radioactive cold air that could increase the energy consumption of their enemies that were attacking the Energy Fields of their Bodies. While battling other Level Five Mech Pilots, their combat abilities were sometimes slightly weaker but the radioactive cold air was able to make up for the difference. As long as they were not fighting exceptional, top-notch Mech Pilot prodigies, most of the other Level Fives would be like this. I really did not expect that the Distorted Seed would give me such great surprises…”

Garen’s mind considered that the results of this ambush were truly unexpected. He did not think that the explosion of the Distorted Seeds would produce such great power. He had only planned to test out an experiment initially but had now discovered that the effects were extraordinarily great.

“Now that the Level Four Mech Pilots in my hands have been used up completely, where else will I be able to find high-level Mech Pilots?” Garen began to ponder slightly.

“High-level Mech Pilots have always been opponents that were drawn over by other forces. If those Mech Pilots had not committed crimes that caused their infamous reputations to be scattered about, which then made other unwilling to hire them, I wouldn’t have been able to entice them either. High-level Mech Pilots… High-level Mech Pilots…”, Garen furrowed his eyebrows and pondered.

Chapter 924: Counterattack 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Looks like I’ll only be able to come up with a solution from prison. Perhaps Professor might have a solution. There would definitely be some pretty talented individuals in the Black Flood Party’s heavy-duty offenders prison.”

While sitting inside the car, Garen began to arrange his next plan carefully.

“If managed to infiltrate the Black Flood Party’s heavy-duty offenders prison and implant my parasites into one or two strong Mech Pilots, although I would be unable to control the life or death of a Mech Pilot that possessed a Distorted Seed at any time, the units that hosted parasites would not to attack me as the main body. On the contrary, once they entered the battlefield, they would only get rid of other creatures of different species than themselves. They would also control the time of the mutated distortions on their own. It’s unlikely that most people would reject these conditions. After all, this would also be an opportunity for them to upgrade their level by a great extent.”

“Additionally other than Mech Pilots, perhaps the other mutated creatures outside the radiation belts would make pretty good parasite hosts as they are already naturally strong, I’m certain that their powers would increase greatly if they were implanted with parasites…”

A plan formed in Garen’s mind slowly.

Although his own powers were not strong as they had reached a standstill, the strength of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique had finally begun to appear, slowly. This conformed to the power levels that were famously associated with Living Secret Techniques.

“I’ll build a biochemical pool now first and attempt to implant parasites into the biochemical creatures. Perhaps there will be somewhat impressive discoveries.”

Ideas floated around in Garen’s mind. He did not know what kind of changes would occur throughout the explosive troops that were formed in the biochemical pools after they fused with the Distorted Seed. According to the theories and inferences, perhaps the Distorted Seed would get rid of the biochemical creatures’ limited numbers as it would be impossible for the biochemical creatures that had fallen into chaos to accept the control of the biochemical pool. Therefore, as long as he had sufficient materials, he would be able to continuously create a limitless pool of explosive soldiers within a short span of time.

“If the theories are proven…” Garen’s mind began to burn with enthusiasm. “The other Energy Machinists have their own control quotas such as the Level Two Energy Machinists being able to control two biochemical creatures. The Energy Machinist’s somewhat impressive Training Methods allow them to increase the limit by one creature while the biochemical pool lets them control another one, which adds up to two creatures in total. If my Distorted Seed works, I will be able to create an endless amount until I have enough of them as long as my Distorted Seeds are sufficient!”

Boom!!!

Suddenly, a burning blue meteor descended from the sky and fell in front of the car that he was sitting inside. It soared towards Garen’s car and flew directly towards it.

“Die!!”

A low voice echoed furiously.

The tremendously terrifying momentum seemed almost physical when its strong pressure collided against Garen’s body brutally.

Bang! Bang! Bang!!

The drivers and bodyguards from the surrounding cars were immediately blasted into pieces of bloody flesh that could be turned into cans of human minced meat. They were unable to endure this tremendous pressure at all.

This strength was not merely gravity or any other kind of Energy Field. Instead, it was purely the stress of extremely strong Willpower!!

Garen felt as if his entire body had sunk into a glue-like swamp as it was absolutely difficult to move. His eyes widened when he heard continuous cracking noises coming from the bones inside his body. The blood and flesh of certain parts of his body had gradually collapsed as well while the cells and organizations kept on breaking down and dying.

Red trails of blood flowed out of his nostrils, ears, and eyes slowly.

As the heavy pressure continued to close in on him, Garen’s vision became a complete blur. He was unable to see anything clearly while his ears were filled with a brief popping noise before he became deaf as well.

“This power…??!”

Beep… Beep… Beep…

A series of hurried alarm noises echoed throughout the car continuously. Strangely enough, the city’s defense installations had not reacted during this surprise attack. However, guarding shields that were used for segregation appeared immediately throughout a large expanse of the surroundings.

A beautiful sky blue Humanoid Mech with a Body that as smooth as a mirror was currently extending its body while flying down slowly from a crackle of blue flames.

He carried a slender spear on his back that had black flames burning faintly at its tip.

The most eye-catching thing about it was the snowy white, silver-rimmed cloak that was hung on the left shoulder of its Body. The word ‘wind’ was written in big letters on the cloak.

The sky colored Body stretched its large handout and attempted to violently grab Garen who was inside the car below.

“You dare!!”

A roar could be heard.

A ray of light that was reflected off the blade shot downwards and pierced through the shield from afar. It hit the large hand of the blue Body violently and forced it to take a few steps backward.

A low voice echoed from afar.

“Seventh! You will suffer the consequences if you dare lay a finger on him today!!”

Another similar dark blue mirror-like Body floated down slowly and appeared in the sky nearby. The same silvery-white cloak hung from its left shoulder with the word ‘wind’ written there in large letters. The difference between it and the Mech Body with the long spear was that there was a slender pitch black thin sword that was as dark as ink which hung from its waist.

“If I find the person who dared to ambush my son, don’t blame me for humiliating you, Six”, huffed the Body with the long spear coldly. He turned around and walked away unhurriedly before his Body sank into an empty space and disappeared without a trace.

The Body with a black sword that remained lowered its head and glanced at Garen whose entire body was covered in blood inside the car.

“Be careful, Seventh will take action immediately with the slightest suspicion. Don’t clash with Remington anymore in the future. He has never needed proof.”

He turned around and slipped into an empty space as well.

Only then did the terrifyingly powerful pressure disappear slowly.

Once that frightening pressure had finally disappeared gradually, only then did Garen heal from that heavy force slowly.

He felt like a heavy-duty truck had run over his entire body continuously. Blood was pouring out of all of his five sensory organs while most of the muscles in his body had torn. Large cracks had of various extents had appeared throughout the bones of his whole body as well. Moreover, most of his internal organs were bleeding.

He opened and closed his mouth in an attempt to speak but the only thing that escaped his throat was a violent tearing pain.

“Divine Wind General…” He closed his eyes and carved this name into his mind firmly.

He had no strength left to resist.

He had never once encountered an enemy that could strip him of all power to resist and this stopped him from being able to move as well.

The terrifyingly oppressive Willpower caused his whole body to become critically injured to the point where he was at the brink of death. Previously, he had tried to think about the strength of the Divine Wind General Level many times. However, he had never expected that the power of the other party would actually reach this degree.

Other than himself, most of the pedestrians in the surroundings of the small town had exploded because of this ominous pressure and none of them had survived.

Within a range and vicinity of over a hundred meters, no one else had survived other than him. The other person’s unscrupulous nature had reached an extent that could not be glossed over at all.

He used his last bits of strength to add one Potential Point to his Vitality. Finally, Garen fell into a coma completely when he was unable to endure it anymore. His body had suffered extremely critical injuries in which the best state of healing was when his Willpower was in a dormant state.

*********************

Within the confusion, Garen felt as if he had heard a noise.

There was nothing but darkness in front of him while his Willpower was slightly blurry as well.

“How much longer will it take for him to wake up?” It sounded like Celine’s voice speaking extremely coldly.

“I’m not sure about the whole situation. However, his injuries are really very serious. A normal person would have died much earlier if they suffered injuries of this degree. I never expected that someone like him who had suffered a terrifying ambush like this would actually survive so tenaciously. Our hospital has only seen a handful of living examples like this,” said another unfamiliar voice. “His vitality is extremely strong. Many times, we only need to guide him faintly for a while before he’s able to heal himself quickly and automatically. This is truly rare!”

“Will he suffer any disabilities?” Celine continued to ask. “He’s already been in a coma for five days!”

“We’ve assembled all of the first-rate medical teams and the treatment plans that they have formulated is definitely the most suitable one for him. Disabilities, perhaps there will be certain effects but these will depend on the condition of his healing in the future.”

“I believe that he’ll be fine.”

“We will do all we can. Sigh”

The sound of a door being opened could be heard.

Garen could feel his Willpower clearing up gradually. Various memories and scenes replayed in his mind again.

“That’s right, I was ambushed…”

The powerful sky blue Body appeared in his mind.

“Divine Wind General…”

When he opened his eyes slowly, Garen could see the white ceiling.

“You’re awake!!” Celine’s face burst into his field of vision immediately. She looked sallow as if she had not rested for a long time. She had dark circles around her eyes and was much thinner than before. When she saw that Garen had awakened, the surprise on her face was very apparent.

“You’ve finally woken up!!” She sighed in relief quickly. “I’ll go look for a doctor!”

“No need.”

Garen opened his mouth and spoke.

“How long have I been unconscious?” He could hear his own voice. It sounded very hoarse like a pair of bellows that were leaking air.

“Five days and five nights. Someone tried to stab you to death and I killed five or six people because of them”, answered Celine softy. “You can rest properly. I’m here, don’t worry.”

Garen nodded. His entire body was heavily injured while both his Willpower and physical body were at the brink of collapsing. There were many people who wanted to take his life, especially those who wanted the Rainbow Stones in his hands to refine their skills and powers. This item and his business had made many people envious for a long time. Garen would never dare to let his guard down in the presence of the other collaborative partners except for Celine who was the only committed individual whom he could trust. After all, he gained profits of at least a few hundred million every year.

“Be careful of the Seventh Divine Wind General because Fila would never let such a rare opportunity go. He will definitely make his move!!” said Garen in a low voice.

“I know”, Celine nodded with a solemn look on her face. “My household’s latest security systems have been installed in every corner of this building. The five different tests will be able to stop the entry and exit of all hidden equipment. The powerhouses from my household are keeping guard outside. What should we do with the people that your Professor sent?”

“Ask them to patrol the periphery temporarily. If Professor’s friends hadn’t come to save me that other day, I would’ve died right there and then”, said Garen coldly. “Don’t worry, I’ll heal in no time. My body will not be a huge obstacle”. However, he was not speaking honestly. He could heal his body with his Potential Points but had no way of healing his Willpower. The Willpower of his Crouched Eagle Talon had suffered serious damages and nearly collapsed. Therefore, it would need at least a few years to heal. Even if he had built his Exclusive Mech perfectly, he would not be able to continue entering and controlling it in his current state. Meanwhile, he only had 37 Potential Points left. Hence, although he could use these Potential Points to quicken the healing process, the speed of his healing would unintentionally reveal his biggest secret. Regardless of anything, he could not control the Exclusive Mech or become a Resonance Mech Pilot at the first instance.

He would either need to delay this for at least a year or proceed with everything in the dark.

“What plans do you have?” asked Celine after being quiet for a while.

“What other plans could I have? My opponent is the Seventh Divine Wind General and I would be fighting overwhelming odds if I were to fight him with my current strength”, answered Garen calmly.

“The Black Flood Party is dominating the Polar Region exclusively and they have the strength of overlords. Forgive me, I have no way of mobilizing my household to confront them directly. However, I can still represent myself!” said Celine softly.

“I know and I don’t blame you. This matter was not an issue that arose when I offended Remington. The main reason is probably the fact that my Professor’s sect over there could not handle them. They merely used this minor issue as an excuse to set out.”

“Your Professor said the same thing. He said that it’s very likely that the other party knows about your talents already. He told you to keep your guard up because the Seventh Wind General has always been thick-skinned. He has never had any emotional burdens even when personally taking action against younger members of his family”, said Celine in an even softer tone.

“Don’t worry, I will make him pay”, Garen took a deep breath and looked at the Attribute Pane at the bottom of his eyes.

Thanks to the Divine Wind General’s contributions, his Hellfrost Peacock Technique that was slightly lacking previously had finally broken through to Level Seven.

The critical injuries that he had sustained this time had failed to achieve their desired effect. Instead, his Living Secret Technique had modified the Vitality of his body completely.

While observing the new changes that had appeared throughout his Living Secret Technique, Garen’s eyes became colder.

‘Secret Technique — Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Living Secret Technique, Level Seven. 0% completion rate of Level Seven.

Natural Ability Obtained — Devoured Energy Field 3 (Devours all living creatures within a certain range to heal itself and condense Distorted Seeds. Its largest diameter is ten meters).

Natural Ability Obtained — Distorted Seed 3 (Creating chaos is the Hellfrost Peacock’s greatest hobby. Increases qualities and upgrades them by three times. Mutated organisms will produce contamination effects. Contaminated organisms will mutate automatically and become secondary distorted organisms. Qualities will increase by 1.5 times.)

Natural Ability Obtained — Cold Chaos 3 (The main body will cause fluctuations of time and space naturally. With the main body as the center, cold air was naturally be released within a surrounding range of 20 meters to form a chaotic low-temperature area where the lowest temperature will be -20 degrees. Simultaneously, there is a small possibility that it will cause chaos within the senses of its enemies, causing them to attack randomly.)

Devour had upgraded the effects of his range. The main improvements could be seen in the Distorted Seed as it was now upgraded to a Level Three Distorted Seed. The mutated qualities had been increased from their initial 1.5 times to their current three times. This was a terrifying extent as once a peak Level Four Mech Pilot’s mutation was increased from its initial 1.5 times and it was strengthened in all aspects, they would automatically become a peak Level Five Mech Pilot. Meanwhile, now that he had been upgraded by three times, he did not know what kind of level he would enter. Moreover, he had gained contamination effects as well which simply turned him into a chaotic powerful killing machine!!

The truly frightening part of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique had started to gradually display itself finally. It was not directed at himself but was a terrifying power that was similar to developing an army!

Chapter 925: Bureau 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was aware that he had been recently oppressed by the Divine Wind General’s terrifying Willpower Energy Field. It caused his entire body to collapse and a lot of internal and external bleeding. His Crouched Eagle Talon that was also a important element of his resistance was immediately destroyed as well, leaving him with only his Level Two NIS Energy Machinist Willpower. Despite being a Level Five Mech Pilot powerhouse earlier, he had completely turned into a normal Level Two Energy Machinist. Moreover, he could not be considered as a true Energy Machinist because he did not have his own Energy Machine Imprint and biochemical pool.

If someone were to ambush him again, a single Willpower attack from a Level Three Mech Pilot was all that was needed to get rid of him immediately. The Willpowers of Energy Machinists were simply not designed for combat.

“Don’t worry, I will arrange everything”, Celine could see the anxiety on Garen’s face. “You just need to rest well!”

“My Willpower, it might be destroyed”, Garen raised his head and glanced at her with a calm look on his face.

“I believe in your talents. Besides that, you’re still young and you’ll be able to get back up sooner or later!” The expression on Celine’s face was slightly pained but she managed to force a smile. “After all, you’re Celine, the combat master!”

It was easy to say but rebuilding Willpower, especially combat Willpower simply needed an extended amount of time. Special cases like these where the foundation was destroyed and needed to be rebuilt needed twice the amount of time taken for normal repairs.

Both Garen and Celine actually understood that although they only spent two to three years studying the practices of the Crouched Eagle Talon in the beginning, this time frame included the fact that they had transferred certain parts of studying other types of Willpower beforehand. It was important to note that Nonosiva had actually spent at least five or six years practicing these things previously. If this increased by twofold, he would need another ten years. Meanwhile, no one could be able to tell how many unknown Mech Pilots would be able to surpass him greatly within these ten years despite not being as good as him in the past.

“Alright, you should just rest well. I’ll go and get more medicine for you”, Celine stood up and ran out of the sick ward as if she was fleeing because she did not know how to console him.

Garen laid on the sickbed alone. He raised his head and looked at the ceiling.

“I must heal my Willpower as soon as possible. Otherwise, I won’t even have the basic ability to protect myself!”

Without any hesitation, he tried manipulating some of his basic Willpower again. He began to follow the trajectory of the Crouched Eagle Talon before sketching the Willpower Imprints on his arms slowly.

Suddenly, there were no signs before a sharp pain surged throughout his arms and pounded against the depths of his brain violently.

Boom!!!

A terrifyingly deafening ramming noise could be heard.

Immediately, Garen felt like two gongs had smashed beside his ears loudly. His ears became deaf for awhile before they were filled with humming noises.

His head became dizzy and his eyes were blinded at once while his mind was hazy. Even his basic Willpower became drowsy immediately after being hit by the impact.

After waiting for half a minute, the noise and tremors gradually disappeared and weakened.

Only then did Garen realize that the powerful sky blue Willpower was entrenched within both of his own arms. They were like two live skinny snakes that had forcibly occupied the spaces that were actually suitable for the engraving of Willpower Imprints.

The deafening noises from before were not caused by other things. Instead, they occurred when those two shrouds of Willpower were attempting to rush into his mind. The crashing noise occurred when they clashed with the Soul Seed’s strong defense.

During this moment, the shroud of Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower that had just condensed had now completely vanished into thin air. This made Garen’s face even more contorted with pain.

“Such venomous measures!” Only then did he understand why the Seventh Divine Wind General had left so easily. As it turned out, his true intentions were actually here!

He discovered suddenly that once he had arrived in this world, he had encountered many obstacles but did not know their true sources.

As his Willpower sank into the surroundings of his Soul Seed, Garen used another the strong detection abilities of another two Soul Seeds to begin sensing the state of his own body again.

Seconds and minutes ticked by and his consciousness could sense that Celine had returned once again. She changed two bottles of energy water with the ones that she was holding. She sat at Garen’s bedside for awhile before leaving temporarily.

Garen fell into a state of semi-deep sleep. He forgot the time and the current condition of his wounds.

He used his entire body and mind to focus on his Soul Seed that was sensing the state of his own body. He felt that his journey ever since he arrived in this world had always been filled with obstacles while the things that he wanted to develop were constantly suffering from damages and obstructions. There was something that was not quite right with this state.

As time continued to pass, Garen could gradually feel that something was abnormal.

Some unknown forces started hovering around his own body. These forces were very strange and could conceal themselves very well. If it was not for the Soul Seeds extremely strange detection abilities that could even sense the abnormalities between worlds, he could not detect the movements of these forces.

“What is this?” Suspicions flashed through Garen’s mind.

These forces seemed somewhat familiar and caused him to vaguely associate it with certain negative memories.

They were the exact same unknown forces that he had sensed the first time he saw Clint and his own younger brother Baylon.

“Could it be something that only the main forces and influencers of the world possess?” Garen recalled Isaros and her sister that he had once met in the previous world who had these same forces wafting around their bodies.

“I definitely did not have these forces around my body in the beginning. I’m certain about that. So when did these things produce themselves then?” faint uncertainties stirred in Garen’s mind. The Soul Seed’s instincts were telling him that the source of all his bad luck stemmed from these strange and nameless forces.

“Everyone who possesses these things are the centers that many other major events revolve around. They have the ability to change the turning points and progress of these major events and can control many aspects of various matters. In other words, they can be temporarily known as the forces of cause and effect.”

This definition was very vivid. Everyone who possessed these forces of cause and effect, from Goth to Isaros and her sister, were key figures who were implicated in a great number of interrelated events.

“I don’t know the main functions of these things or their sources. However, according to my identity, the most likely source is Baylon and my connection with respect to Red Moon.”

Garen analyzed this step by step and felt that it was most likely that these forces of cause and effect stemmed from Baylon, Clint, and Red Moon.

After straightening out some things, he retreated slightly further away from his Soul Seed slowly and allowed his consciousness to return to his body before opening his eyes and noticing that his vision was completely black.

Faint rays of light cascaded inside the window while the curtains were slightly raised by the breeze. Celine was sleeping on a temporary bed on the right side and held the remote control of an alarm device in her hand tightly. Her breathing was even and gentle, giving off the feeling that she would wake up at any moment.

Garen did not know how long she had been keeping guard. However, he saw that her face was extremely sallow while dark eye circles could be seen there clearly. Garen’s heart felt slightly warm. Celine who had already entered Level Four had started to cultivate her Resonance Degrees with the Exclusive Mech that her household had already prepared for her much earlier. Despite being considered as one of the prodigious Mech Pilots, she had actually been willing to quietly guard him for such a long time.

Even though a long duration of time had passed, he had not seen any of the other collaborative partners come over to visit him for awhile. Over there, perhaps the professor had come over before Garen had regained consciousness.

Garen remembered that Celine had mentioned in the beginning that some of Professor’s people were guarding the periphery. His mind settled slightly then.

Once he had composed himself he entered his dreams slowly once again and discovered that his body had actually almost healed completely after lying down for so many days. However, the important part was still the restoration of his Willpower. There was currently no way to reconstruct it fully because it was being obstructed by the two shrouds of sky blue colored Willpower. Without combative Willpower, he would be unable to pilot even basic Level One Mechs.

During the next few days, Garen attempted to use the Living Secret Technique’s Devoured Energy Field to try and devour both of the foreign Willpowers. It was indeed effective but its speed was terribly slow. After focusing and attempting to devour it for an hour, he could only consume less than 1% of the sky blue colored Willpower.

The density and mass of both of these Willpowers were simply insanely high! It was more than a few times stronger than his own initial Level Five Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower. The fact that the Living Secret Technique’s Devour talent could consume it was indeed a miracle.

However, it was extremely exhausting to focus all his efforts into devouring it like this. Garen could only use it continuously for an hour each day.

A few more days passed before Professor Van Doe’s people finally arrived.

The door to the ward was opened slowly before two hefty men in black military coats followed behind the doctor and walked inside.

Both of them had thick eyebrows and big eyes and it looked as if their features were slightly similar.

The man in front glanced at Garen who was on the bed. His eyebrows furrowed slightly suddenly and his gaze fell on Garen’s arms immediately. His facial expressions became somewhat contorted and solemn.

The male doctor changed his drugs quickly and checked the indicated parameters on the examination apparatus at the side. There were no abnormalities. After leaving a few instructions, he exited the ward. The two people who had followed him inside earlier were the only ones who remained there.

Celine had zeroed in on the duo much earlier. She had stood up and was looking at them suspiciously now.

“I’m the biochemist, Bamente.”

The first sentence that came out of the first man’s mouth was enough to shock both Celine and Garen. He glared at Garen who was lying on the sick bed and took a few steps towards him and looked at both of his arms carefully. Next, he removed an exquisite silvery-white badge swiftly. It was a badge that was only given to biochemists.

“Your Professor Van Doe spent a huge sum of money to hire me. I’m here to see if there’s any hope of restoring the Willpower in your body.”

Biochemists!

There were less than a hundred people within the entire Blackboard Region that worked in this rare field. Therefore, the price to hire any one of them would be extraordinarily high. The fact that Professor Van Doe was willing to hire a first-class individual to come and treat him definitely gave Celine and Garen great hope.

“Relax and let me take a look.” Bamente furrowed his eyebrows and held one of Garen’s arms gently. Shrouds of gentle Willpower burrowed into his skin slowly like silk threads before binding the sky blue colored Willpower inside his arms.

Garen adjusted his muscles frantically and tried his best to relax his body.

He could feel that the thread-like Willpower was extremely gentle but tough. If he did not feel it carefully, he would not be able to detect its presence or movements.

“This situation is very troublesome. Two Inherited Willpowers remain inside both of your arms. Whenever the Willpower Training Imprints inside your arms are involved, both of these foreign Willpowers will be activated. They will destroy the new Willpowers that you have recently trained at once”, Bamente’s face was slightly solemn and it was clear that the situation was intractable.

“How do we solve it?” asked Garen softly.

“I have two plans. The first one is that I would perform long-term Willpower surgery on you that will take a month at least. However, I won’t be able to assure you that there won’t be any side effects. The second one is to find another Inherited Mech Pilot of the source with the exact same characteristics to either offset or draw out the remaining bits of this foreign Willpower. You will only be able to rebuild the Willpower Imprints on both of your arms after that,” said Bamente casually.

While speaking, the Willpower threads that were being released from his hands continuously burrowed into Garen’s brain quietly.

Garen knitted his eyebrows and was about to speak. Suddenly, an intense impact force hammered his head brutally at once, striking him to the point where his mind became blurry. The large amounts of thin Willpower threads had suddenly hit the defense that his Soul Seed had formed.

“What are you doing??!!” howled Garen in pain.

“This is an inevitable reactionary procedure. Why are you panicking? Did you think that the remaining Willpower of an Inherited Level Mech Pilot could be dispelled so easily? Idiot!”

He realized that something was wrong when he noticed that the expression on Bamente’s face had not change at all. Instead, a sneer had appeared there faintly.

“You must believe in my treatment procedures! Don’t just complain or I’ll turn around and leave immediately!” he said coldly.

“You!!”

Boom!!

Numerous shrouds of Willpower threads travelled towards the defense area in Garen’s mind and struck it like a large hammer. It hit the Soul Seed’s defenses brutally.

Garen’s entire body trembled. The impact had shaken him to the point where he was unable to speak. Immediately, Bamente Willpower retracted suddenly before surging towards the sky blue colored Willpower in his arms at once.

He exhaled. Meanwhile, Celine who had stood up and was prepared to make a move at any time relaxed when she saw him calm down. She relaxed her tense body slowly.

Just then, Bamente’s Willpower charged into the sky blue colored Willpower suddenly. There was a crashing noise as both of these Willpowers fused into one. They became twice as large as their previous size and transformed into a blue python that sprung itself towards Garen’s brain suddenly!!

Then, a cunning smile finally appeared on the corners of Bamente’s mouth while he stood with his back towards Celine.

Something was not right!!

Fatal life-threatening feelings filled Garen’s mind at once. He focused all of the strength in his body in one step before both of his feet pressed down against Bamente’s lower abdomen in an attempt to kick him away.

“Hold him down!! The remaining Willpower is going out of control! This is a vital period!! Hurry!” Bamente plastered a frantic expression on his face and yelled loudly.

Celine and the other man rushed forward at once and held Garen down quickly.

Chapter 926: Bureau 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s strength became limp and much weaker after being shaken by the impact. It was utterly impossible for him to kick Bamente off completely. It was clear that the other man had undergone genetic strengthening as his vitality was extremely strong. The combined strength of these three people would be enough to press the struggling Garen down firmly.

The sky blue colored Willpower that was twice as strong as his own was finally collected together before it charged towards Garen’s brain immediately.

“Trying to kill me? In your dreams!!” In the depths of Garen’s soul, the ancient Nine-Headed Dragon’s Will roared suddenly and rushed out immediately from the depths behind the two Soul Seeds like a great soul storm that rolled towards the defense in his mind violently.

Roar!!!

Within moments, it seemed like the terrifying roars of invisible beasts inside his mind had shaken the entire hospital room.

There was a brief crashing noise.

The sky blue colored Willpower crashed against the Soul Seed’s defense in his mind violently and broke it to pieces. It collided brutally against the Nine-Headed Dragon’s Will that came rolling out.

Boom!!

It seemed as if Bamente had been hit by a train from the front. His body was sent flying backwards and he crashed against the wall behind the sick bed painfully before releasing loud banging noises. Fresh blood sputtered out of his mouth continuously.

Flashes of gold twinkled in Garen’s eyes before they rolled backwards when he fell unconscious.

The two other people were rendered helpless by the tremendous changes and tremors.

“Doctor! Doctor!!” Celine gritted her teeth and hurriedly pressed the alerting alarm bell in her hand.

Meanwhile, the other man supported Bamente who was still continuously spitting blood.

“I can’t treat his sickness… Go!” Bamente squeezed out his last words before leaning against the other man and leaving the hospital room quickly.

After some frenzied rescuing that occurred soon after, Garen was sent to the emergency room for two whole hours before he was taken back to his hospital room again. After seeing that his complexion had returned to normal, Celine’s breathing became calm again and only then did she allow herself to sigh in relief slowly.

Garen had awakened slowly now as well but his face was unusually contorted.

More than half of his internal injuries that had healed earlier had become even worse now. After this impactful collision, the sky blue colored Willpower dispersed throughout every inch of his body. Shrouds of it now existed within all of his injuries. Other than his head which was protected by the Nine-Headed Dragon’s Will, it was extremely difficult for him to move the other parts of his body.

He only said one sentence when he noticed Celine who was keeping guard outside the emergency room.

“That Bamente tried to kill me!”

Celine’s expression changed immediately. She had realized that something was amiss much earlier. However, since the other person was a biochemist, she assumed that he had certain strange treatment measures that no one knew about. She had been enduring it patiently all this while but once Garen had confirmed it now, she finally discovered that there was something that was actually not right with that person.

“Was it Fila?!”

“It could be a Divine Wind General as well. It’s even likely that it’s someone that I offended in the past,” said Garen calmly. The Nine-Headed Dragon’s Will was purely a soul ability. If the other person’s intentions had not infiltrated his mind, it would not have activated the Nine-Headed Dragon’s instinctive defense consciousness. However, collisions like these caused him to become extremely exhausted.

“There are a lot of people who want me dead.”

Once Garen had returned to his hospital room, he sat down and leaned against the bed with Celine’s support.

Celine’s expression was pained as well. She had not expected an outcome like this either.

“I won’t let anyone come near you!” she said firmly.

“You can’t guard against it forever,” Garen shook his head. “This place isn’t safe anymore. From today onwards, don’t let anyone besides yourself and Professor approach me.”

“Alright,” Celine nodded solemnly.

“I won’t be using these medications either. Get my people to surround this place,” said Garen calmly. “Tell Professor about this information. Perhaps he will have a plan.”

“I’ll make a call immediately,” Celine stood up and said.

*****************

In the surroundings of the hospital in Dawn City where Garen was currently located, within the circles of buildings and streams of people, one could vaguely see a few mysterious people that were dressed in normal clothing who were unconsciously gazing in the direction of the hospital.

Most of these mysterious people had bulges around their waists as if they had stuffed items there.

Inside the hall of a residential building near the hospital.

Two men were standing in front of the window and looking towards the hospital window where Nonosiva was located from afar.

“I was about to make a move when I was shaken and forced backwards by something. It’s very likely that it was the life-saving object that Van Doe had given him,” said the man with the thick eyebrows and big eyes softly while holding the curtains with his right hand. He was the biochemist Bamente who had tried to cure Garen earlier.

“If you were forced to return with serious injuries as well, he will definitely be unable to use that object again. If a Level Five biochemist like yourself was injured by the aftereffects of the tremors, a wounded person like himself probably sustained injuries that are even worse than yours,” said another man, smiling. “Our manpower has been prepared. The military’s garrison has informed us that everything has been arranged in order. Once we’ve received the message from Van Doe’s side, we will move out immediately.”

“Then the little bastard is dead for sure. Five Shining Mechs and more than twenty Level Four Captain Level machine soldiers. Tch tch, they’ve been disguised the acts of normal terrorists. This scale is truly great!” praised Bamente.

“The few Level Four Mech Pilots that Celine assembled will not be able to stand a single blow. However, we should wait awhile before commencing. The follow-up preparations should be completed soon,” said the man softly while smiling.

********************

Blackboard Inner Courtyard

Van Doe put the phone down with a pained look on his face and glared at the blonde man in front of him.

“You’re saying that Nono’s Willpower has collapsed completely?!”

“According to the information that was sent back, that is true,” the man nodded. “Moreover, according to the investigation of the Intelligence Bureau, it’s very likely that Nonosiva possesses the related characteristics of radioactive people.”

“Radioactive people!”

Van Doe glared at the man in front of him firmly before his gaze blinked occasionally.

“Professor, what do we do now?” asked the man quietly.

“Are you saying that his Willpower is completely destroyed? There’s no hope of restoring it?” asked Van Doe softly while lowering his head.

“I’m afraid so. The Seventh Divine Wind General’s Willpower that remained in him will completely absorb the Crouched Eagle Talon’s Willpower that he obtained from training. If he doesn’t get rid of the remaining Willpower first, he will be unable to practice the Crouched Eagle Talon. Moreover, it will be even harder for him improve the skills of the Black Wind. He will either need at least three years to get rid of it or he will need an Inherited Level powerhouse to help him dispel it constantly. Professor, if I may speak frankly, we cannot pay this price for an individual who may only grow into a genius. It’s not worth it.”

The blonde man continued to advise him, “Some compensation resources have been sent over from the Seventh Divine Wind General’s side. We don’t have to intensify the conflict with them because of a future genius anymore.”

He paused before saying, “Nonosiva has become useless.”

After hesitating for a long time, Van Doe exhaled a long breath.

“What a shame… A genius like this…” His eyelids drooped slowly.

The blonde man knew that once these words were said, it meant that his teacher had truly given up on Nonosiva completely.

This powerful genius of humble birth had finally been forced into an abyss after offending too many people that he should not have provoked.

**********************

“What?! The military has instructed the units urgently and transferred them forward to the radiation belt for their missions?! What kind of joke is this?!” Celine could not help but roar angrily while standing in the corridor of the hospital.

They possessed the combat strength of a perfect unit! Their lowest level members would be Level Three Mech Pilots at least. Other than Garen, the highest ones would be peak Level Fours. Did the military actually transfer orders and compel these forces to leave for their mission immediately by assigning them to another place?

Did they actually send them to another place during this key moment when they needed to protect their strength? Could their intentions be any more obvious?!

Unsuppressible rage boiled in Celine’s mind.

“I’m very sorry, this is an order from the headquarters and there’s nothing we can do about it either.” The person in charge at the defense base answered her coldly and briefly before disconnecting the call immediately.

Celine’s face had turned bright red with rage. She dialed the phone number of a close uncle who was the head of their household. Unfortunately, the line could not connect.

“Celine,” a masculine shout echoed behind her.

Celine turned around and saw the captain of her household’s external bodyguard team who was an honest and sedate middle-aged man named Hann.

“What’s the matter, Hann?” Celine tried her best to suppress the negative emotions in her mind. She asked casually, “Didn’t I ask all of you to stand guard outside?”

“I’m very sorry… An order came from the household to tell us that we must return immediately,” said Hann quietly while lowering his head helplessly.

Celine’s pupils contracted.

“Who gave that order?!”

“Your father, Master Cameron…” answered Hann softly.

Bang!

“Damn!!” Celine’s fist smashed against the hospital wall, forming a little hollow pit there.

Her mind was filled with chaos. It was obvious that the other party was gaining momentum by doing all of this. They were stripping them of all their protective layers in preparation for their final move.

“What do we do?!!” Her mind was a disorderly mess. She did not know how to counter her enemy’s moves at all.

From the situation that was revealed from the previous phone call, it seemed as though Nono’s professor might have given up as well. The pressure from the other party resembled a tidal wave that was huge and could oppress others to the point of suffocation.

The staff that were keeping guard outside were mainly the household’s bodyguard units that she had arranged to be placed there. Once they were disabled, the entire hospital would lose all of its defensive strength at once!

“Your father’s intentions were for you to return with him as well.” Hann’s voice echoed over again.

“Get lost!!”

Suddenly, Celine yelled angrily.

“Get lost, all of you!! It won’t make any difference if I guard this place by my damn self!” She was slightly hysterical now. Celine flung the surgical cotton in her hands everywhere and walked briskly before running towards Garen’s hospital room.

She needed transfer Nono and get him out of here immediately!

Bang!

Suddenly, a shadow flashed behind her and hit the back of her neck gently.

“Who?!” Unexpectedly, Celine turned her body and dodged it while her elbow struck behind her quickly. She moved her other hand backwards like a whip rapidly and hit the neck of the oncoming person!

“Twelve Flying Dragon Hand!!”

Through Garen’s guidance, she was able to suddenly use the Twelve Flying Dragon Fist that she had reformed. Her blade-like hand turned into a large cluster of shadows but were continuously dodged by the person behind her immediately.

That person dodged her frantically and finally increased the distance between them suddenly.

“It’s me! Celine!” A low but dignified voice could be heard.

“Uncle?!” Celine was shocked when she noticed the other man’s face suddenly.

Immediately, a strong Willpower assault surged over violently. Celine felt her mind turning black before she became unaware of anything else.

The person who had arrived lifted her on his shoulder and rushed towards Hann and glanced at him coldly.

“Evacuate everyone immediately! This place is extremely dangerous!”

“Yes!” Hann forced a smile.

****************

Inside the hospital ward

Garen lay on the sickbed quietly. Celine had left a long time ago, more than half an hour in fact. These days, she had never left for more than fifteen minutes. However, more than half an hour had already passed…

The entire hospital was completely empty. There were no noises at all as if there were no more human voices left for now. It seemed as though the doctors and nurses that were always walking around had disappeared as well.

“Am I the only one left?”

Garen murmured softly and turned his head to look out of the window. This hospital was once a private hospital while Dawn City was an unassuming small town. It would be too easy if the other party wanted to evacuate the area.

Chapter 927: Desperate Situation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Outside the hospital, within the surroundings of the dark grey blocks, the pedestrians and residents had been evacuated urgently. Only empty neighborhoods and houses remained while the crowds that had been dispersed were held back outside the separation lines. They looked on at the private hospital in the center from afar.

On top of a building, several people who were in charged stood on the edge of the roof, issuing commands while on-site.

One of them wore a white suit and looked as if he had just walked out of a ball. His platinum hair was combed out with a layer of hairspray. When the afternoon sun cascaded on it, layers of light were reflected faintly.

“Logan, how are the arrangements for each aspect?” asked the man quietly.

“Almost done. All of the powerhouses that I arranged have been hidden properly. The Remington household’s forces have been dispersed throughout a range and area of a hundred meters. The three main units of the Third Mechanical Army have complied fully with the first garrison to monitor and control the three aspects of the ground, underground, and sky. A single mosquito would not even be able to escape from here!”

A thin man stood on the side, and reported quietly.

“I just don’t understand why a single heavily wounded and disabled individual would require so much combat manpower? Can’t it be done just by entering and seizing him directly?”

“What you don’t understand is that this isn’t just a regular arresting activity but more of an exhibition of power. Moreover, we still don’t know the exact moves that he’s hiding up his sleeves,” the man shook his head slightly. He reached his hand out and tidied his four strange eyebrows before a smile appeared on his face.

“Anyway, there’s nothing wrong with being slightly more careful.”

He looked down. He saw a large army of black Miniature Mechs, who wore black badges and were dressed in the Remington forces’ military outfits, started to approach the hospital building gradually. They carried large black shields that were big enough to cover their whole bodies while marching forward slowly from all directions.

In the sky, Mech Soldiers from the Third Mechanical Army flew over gradually as well. Although most of them were Level One Mech Soldiers, since this was a small town, it was already quite impressive that they were able to assemble more than ten of these forms of manpower during these critical moments.

The people from the Intelligence Bureau had installed monitors and protective screen measures around the area. They had even installed simple laser interception networks in certain important areas.

Fila had previously held the post of the Commander in Chief of the Third Mechanical Army. Hence, he was able to assemble and loan the strengths of his subordinates currently. He had held the post of the director of the Intelligence Bureau as well. Once again, it was easy for him to obtain his own forces. However, he still refused to let his guard down because he could still remember the ambush that he had encountered in the radiation belt. A pressing feeling continued to stir in his mind because he was uncertain whether Nonosiva had actually planned that raid. After all, an average young person would never be able to grasp mutated skills like that. Yet regardless of whoever was controlling these things, he had no choice but to get rid of this lurking danger as soon as possible because of the arrangement of the crisis that would soon follow.

Although this was seemingly just another encirclement, it was also an opportunity for him to display his own strength.

With a wave of his hand, Fila had finally given the final order to attack.

He had spread an inescapable net, and had laid it out completely.

His style was to stand on the spot while he slaughtering others!

**********************

Bang!

The door to the hospital room was pushed open at once. Following that, a black Miniature Mech soldier charged inside and aimed the barrel of its gun at a patient’s bed precisely.

“No one?!”

“Search!”

A Mech Soldier moved forward and pressed the bedding.

“The temperature is 28.5 degrees and there is still residual heat. According to the calculations of the temperature and the air conditioning, he should have left two minutes ago.”

“Open the residual body heat tracks and trace them.”

There was a brief clapping noise before the entire room immediately became completely bright red under the gaze of the Mech Soldier.

“Nothing! What’s the matter?!” There were no traces of residual body heat inside the room at all.

Suddenly, a bright red shadow flew downwards into its line of sight, and harshly fell on top of the Mech Soldier’s head.

There was a crisp cracking noise before the person’s neck was twisted and broken, killing him in the process.

The red shadow turned a few more times. When the other people were unable to pull the trigger in time, it disappeared moments later within the hospital room.

Bang bang bang bang!

Loud gunshots could be heard inside the hospital room while bullets flew about.

“Jamie!! Oh sh*t!”

Pfoo!

Another red shadow pounced over suddenly, and landed behind the other Mech Soldiers. Both of its arms shot forward. Then like two venomous snakes, it violently bit the back of both their heads.

There were two simultaneous cracking noises but it seemed as though only one was heard.

The armor plates on the back of both of these Mech Soldiers’ heads were pierced through by his bare-hand. He violently stabbed both of his fingers inside them, leaving two bloody holes.

Garen resembled a large bat that soared upwards after biting these two people to death. He then proceeded to hang upside down on the ceiling once again. Strange enough, the back of his body was able to absorb itself onto the ceiling as if he was a wall painting that was hung upside down.

The last remaining Mech Soldier below staggered about in an attempt to escape the room. However, it only managed to run a few steps away before feeling that the bottom of its feet had stiffened.

He lowered his head to look. Only then did it realize that a thick layer of ice had frozen the legs of his Mech without him even noticing. Moreover, this icy layer was spreading at a speed that even the naked eye could see.

He suddenly felt as though he could sense something. He raised his head immediately, and looked at the ceiling but it could only see a red shadow rushing towards his face at the final moment.

Garen used one hand to press onto the Mech Soldier while a gush of frighteningly intense cold air was suddenly released from his entire body.

Ever since his Living Secret Technique had broken through Level Seven, both his Cold Radiation and Cold Chaos abilities were upgraded. He could release extremely cold temperatures of -20 degrees unexpectedly, allowing him to quickly freeze and delay the movements of the Mech Soldiers when his enemies were helplessly panicking. At the same time, although these individuals were initially well-trained combat soldiers, when they were affected by the Cold Chaos’ mental confusion effects, they would become easily spooked and anxious during the state of disorder. This allowed Garen’s surprise attacks to succeed smoothly.

He floated down, and landed gently while his complexion remained pale.

Slaughtering numerous Mech Soldiers in a row by force was not an impressive feat. The troublesome part was having to pierce through the Miniature Mechs that were worn by the Mech Soldiers. Although these things did not have particularly strong defenses, their fingers would suffer great harm if they penetrated it with bare hands.

Garen raised his hand. Solid icicles had frozen both of his forefingers due to the frigid air. Coupled with the quick movements of his hands, he was able to penetrate the Mech Soldier’s armor. However, his palm and wrist had suffered slight fractures because of this.

“There are gunshot noises here! Hurry, hurry!!” Loud yells echoed outside.

Tch!!

The left wall was suddenly penetrated by a ray of red light that was shooting towards Garen’s face. It was an armor-piercing projectile! Like a red line, the miniature armor-piercing projectile directly pierced through multiple layers of walls.

Garen somersaulted, and narrowly dodged the shooting armor-piercing projectile. However, he still felt a violent, burning pain on his face at the same time. A cold sensation that was tinged with burning heat quickly spread from the wound on his face and onto the other parts of his body.

“It’s poisonous!”

He added one Potential Point to his Vitality immediately. His Potential diffused quickly to rapidly suppress the poison from spreading.

Garen dragged the corpse of a random Mech Soldier and violently smashed it against the wall on the opposite side. Next, he rushed out of the hospital room door.

Just as he had exited the room, two shrouds of fiery red fluttering light shot over from the right side of the stairs.

Boom boom!

When both of the intense flames exploded, Garen’s body was sent flying brutally as he was unable to react in time.

Bang bang bang bang!

The Big Mechs outside had started raking the whole area with machine gunfire. Heavy-duty machine guns swept across the hospital in a frenzy.

Bullet holes pierced through the walls. On the white walls, the bullet holes resembled black snakes that were rushing towards Garen.

Garen rolled over again and discovered that his entire body was charred black from the explosions. He had just crawled up before he saw two strings of bullets inching towards him. The corridor of the entire hospital was shot up, and covered in a thousand holes while rays of sunlight cascaded in through the numerous bullet holes on the other side.

The ground of the entire building made violent crashing noises as if it was roaring.

His ears were filled with buzzing noises. Other than the noise of the bombs and machine guns, he could not hear anything else.

Garen stared fixedly at the black chain of bullets that was quickly moving towards him from the bullet holes. He dodged, and crouched down to evade the assault of the bullet chain before a series of noises that came from running Mech Soldiers suddenly echoed from the stairs behind him.

Bang!

He immediately moved, just before a ray of red light pierced through the floorboards below. It formed a pillar of fire that was more than a meter tall when it burst through.

The whole hospital started to burn.

“Arson?” Garen’s face remained indifferent because he was not afraid of death. He could not even clearly remember the number of times he had stared death in the face. Nonetheless, it was not his style to simply die here.

Miniature Mechs were not afraid of the scorching flames at all. It was easy for them to endure high temperatures of a few hundred degrees. However, the same did not apply to Garen because he had a flesh body. It was clear that the other party intended to burn him alive here.

Columns of bursting flame constantly exploded from the ground. Garen continuously dodged the flame pillars on the floorboards. With a few somersaults backward, he bounced towards the stairs at the back. He leaped gently, like a fish that had just jumped out of the surface of the water, before coincidentally landing on the head of a Mech Soldier that had just charged through the stairs. He sandwiched it with both his legs before twisting and breaking his enemy’s neck with a ‘crack’. He pressed downwards with the tip of his toes. Then, he swiftly pulled the trigger on the machine gun in the Mech Soldier’s hand. He supported himself against it and jumped before evading the shooting sweep that followed.

Boom boom boom boom!

After numerous consecutive gunshots, all of the bullets landed accurately on the head of the Mech Soldier upstairs while Garen was somersaulting.

It only took a single encounter for all five of the Mech Soldiers upstairs to be killed.

Without his Willpower, it was impossible for him to confront the enemy directly. He could only rely on his speedy movements to dodge the potential Willpower assaults. Currently, the only thing that he could depend on was his powerful battle skills, and great physical fitness.

While the rest had yet to react, Garen operated a Mech Soldier and ran towards the part of the building with the thickest bearing walls.

While running, he quickly stripped the Mech Soldier of the Miniature Mech that it was wearing and placed it on himself.

These Miniature Mechs were different from the ones in the radiation belt. They were considered as boosting-type Mechs that could be worn separately. They could increase the defense and power of the wearer. They were even fitted externally with certain communication devices that were used for detecting and probing.

Just as he had put it on, Garen could instantly hear noises coming out from the pager inside the Mech continuously.

“Wolf Five, Wolf Five, move forward to the second floor to assist immediately. Use the vertex bomb to destroy the second floor. Try your best to catch him while he’s still alive, if possible!”

Garen did not reply verbally but pretended to pant hoarsely and respond ambiguously instead.

He glanced at the blinking red dot on the board. Those were the numbers, and locations of all the Mech Soldiers.

“Catch me alive? Hehe.” A cold expression appeared on Garen’s face. He knew that it was very likely that the other party was planning to seize him to take the Rainbow Stone techniques that he had obtained.

If they had gotten rid of him on the spot in the beginning, perhaps he would not have an escape route now. However, the order to catch him while he was still alive gave him a lot of empty space to move around.

He moved his hand backward and removed the fixed-point hand grenade from the waist of the Miniature Mech and pressed it against the right wall.

Garen ran forward quickly.

Boom!

Stretches of fiery red flames shot out and exploded behind him. After dodging the flames and explosions, he returned to his previous location at the hole-ridden area. He exchanged the machine gun in his hand for an armor-piercing projectile model. He aimed it precisely at the wall on the other side of the hole-ridden room and shot it directly.

Red lines were shot out.

Boom!

The armor-piercing projectile penetrated the wall and accurately hit the body of another Mech Soldier that had just passed by. Perhaps it had struck the ammunition bundle on its body because suddenly, a large explosion occurred. It sent intense tremors throughout the entire second floor.

“Damn!”

The sound of a cursing man echoed from the pager.

“He’s just an injured cripple!”

The corners of Garen’s mouth curled into a cold-blooded arc.

He rolled across the floor and moved his hand backward to remove another armor-piercing projectile. He aimed it accurately so that it would pierce through the wall before shooting it outside the hospital.

In the sky outside, the Cockpit of a Big Mech was penetrated by that shot. It fell down crookedly, making a crashing noise before turning completely silent.

Garen’s speedy movements allowed him to enter the hospital and get rid of more than ten Mech Soldiers by using armor-piercing projectiles. Occasionally, Garen would replenish the armor-piercing projectiles that he had used. He managed to shoot down five or six Big Mechs outside.

On top of the command building outside.

The expression on Fila’s face remained unchanged as he continued to wave his hand.

“Everyone, withdraw! Abandon the mission to seize him alive, just demolish everything!”

“But…” Beside him, Logan’s eyebrows were knitted together tightly as he attempted to open his mouth to speak.

“Do you still not understand? Within ten minutes, the thirty Miniature Mech Soldiers that entered were completely slaughtered. Five of the Big Mechs outside were killed as well! That Nonosiva is truly not the pushover that we had imagined,” huffed Fila coldly.

“Send the Elite Team forward,” Logan gritted his teeth and said. “That’s a yearly profit of hundreds of millions!” The Mechanical Army that he was part of spent three hundred million a year. If they were able to seize this technique, its effects on the interest of the Mechanical Army would make anyone emotionally affected.

Fila’s mind turned cold. Despite just being relieved of office recently, some of his initial subordinates had stopped listening to his orders already.

“Do as you please. But if something happens, don’t blame me for not reminding you! Besides that, my men won’t leave anyone alive.”

“Commander, I don’t have a choice. Our military allowances have been cut each year. Although this sum of money may be insignificant to you, it’s still a large sum of income for us!” said Logan softly. If it was not for the money, Fila’s instructions would not be able to truly stop him either as he was currently the Commander in Chief.

Fila sighed coldly. He glanced at this man who was previously his groveling subordinate who had now matured into an individual who had dared to look him in the eye.

He turned around because he could not be bothered with looking at him anymore. He stuffed his hand into the pocket of his shirt immediately and walked towards the exit downstairs.

“I hope that you won’t mess it up.” Once they were in this state, there were no survival routes left for a minor force like Nonosiva. He did not have to watch anymore.

“Don’t worry!” A smile appeared on Logan’s face. He rearranged the microphone at the corner of his mouth. “Powerhouse Team, forward! He’s just a lowly piece of garbage with Level One Willpower. If you’re unable to seize him despite that, all of you can just die!”

Chapter 928: Desperate Situation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen shook out the armor-piercing shells from the gun as he leaned against the hospital’s ruined wall on the first floor.

Everyone who had entered the building had already been killed. So, he acted in such a way that made it seem like he was on the verge of dying. He switched off the relay instrument from the Mini Mech. He laid at a side of the ruins while reducing his Mech’s temperature with the Cold Radiation to the point where the body temperature was indistinguishable.

If his opponent primarily used heat to detect any signs of life, then they would not be able to detect him as long as he could blend in with the surrounding temperature.

He would have a chance to survive as long as the opponent intends to capture him alive.

Garen’s highly intense spirit and continuous actions had made him extremely tired as he had exhausted a huge amount of spiritual energy.

His eyelids became heavier over time. He felt as if it was difficult to keep his eyes open, that they could shut down at any time and never open again.

The hospital was in a disastrous state – corpses, fiery fires, bullets, and debris of Mechs could be seen everywhere. A document room, nearby the hospital, was broken as the documents inside were slowly burning. The plastics which were sandwiched in between the papers were slowly turning black, giving off viscous smoke.

The hospital was filled with smoke. It was so bad that one would not be able to see their fingers if they reached their hands out. Crackles were occasionally heard from the wooden furniture that was burning at high temperature.

The power to annihilate dozens of Miniaturized Mech alone was Garen’s raw strength. Without including his unique ability, the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, it was about three times more than a typical person. Ultimately, Garen’s unrivaled prowess in martial arts had made him a classical killing machine, so much so that even the military specialist powerhouses were no match for him.

Boom.

The wall on the first floor was punched through, and the stone debris flew about in the air as multiple human figures slowly walked in.

The man who was at the front reached out his right hand, as if he was grasping onto something.

“Sun Finger Ring.”

A circular golden halo appeared underneath his feet and spread out across the floor. Similar to the ripples spreading about on the surface of the water, the halo would automatically reflect once it reached the wall or any obstacles. After a few seconds, the whole area, including the ceiling was filled with these golden ripples.

Garen was stunned. It was impossible for him to avoid it as he could only see the golden ripples bouncing about on his body.

At the same time, he sensed that these people’s eyes were on him.

“I’ve been discovered!!”

He was startled as their first reaction was to shoot at him with their guns instead. He immediately rolled to the side and jumped up with his legs.

“Hand of Void!”

The other girl shouted.

A powerful strength enveloped Garen as if an elusive huge hand had captured him while he was in the mid-air.

However, the Hand of Void was immediately neutralized with a sea of Cold Radiation. Garen then leaped into the Hospital’s kitchen to hide and no noise was heard after that.

The leader turned his body and the armor-piercing bullets burst opened the left side of the wall. To these group of powerhouses, avoiding these bullets was something very common to them. They wouldn’t be injured unless the path of the bullet was extremely curved or a refraction bullet was used.

“I can’t locate him with my Sun Finger Ring. You guys shall move accordingly,” The leader said calmly.

“Well, duh?” The black-shirted girl behind him scoffed. Then she walked into the hole in the wall, and stared at the viscous smoke inside with a frown.

“Wind of Void!”

Invisible strong wind emerged as she raised both of her hands up, forming a small gray tornado inside the hospital, carrying away all the combustion in the oxygen.

The fiery fire distinguished at the speed that was visible to the naked eye. Though very quickly, all the smoke was gathered by the tornado, and was sent away through the hole in the wall. Immediately after, it exploded, and the smoke slowly floated upwards.

In a split second, the huge fire in the whole hospital was distinguished.

“I expect nothing less from a Level Five Resonance Powerhouse. To possess Resonance of this level is simply amazing to witness,” The lead man shrugged and he wasn’t angry at all.

The black-shirted woman walked into the kitchen without any sense of fear. She didn’t seem to care about any sort of ambush, whether it was guns or explosives.

Another four people from the powerhouse group entered the area. They were all criminals who had been sentenced to death but was kept alive by the military. They were equally assigned among the military groups as an ultimate weapon. Majority of them were Level Five Powerhouses, and the minority of them were Resonance Pilots. Since their Exclusives Mechs were destroyed, they could only release a set of simple Willpower techniques. However, under their overpoweringly strong Willpower, these techniques were strong enough to bend reality itself.

“Be careful. This kid was once a topnotch Level Five Pilot as well.” Seeing how the woman ignored him, he quickly followed up as well.

Both of them walked together as they entered the kitchen on the first floor.

The kitchen was huge. It was a place for the nurses, doctors, and patients to eat.

White cloths that were half burnt were hung in there. However, no one was sure what their purpose was.

“Those words you said back in Tienye Canyon? What did you mean?” The man walked to the woman’s side and whispered into her ears.

“It is however you would want to interpret it,” the woman said coldly.

“That incident isn’t my fault. I can’t do anything if you insist on pushing the blame on me. However, can you please understand the whole situation?” The man said helplessly.

“What situation? Haven’t you already done it?” The woman stared at him coldly.

“I have said that it’s a misunderstanding…” His expression changed before he could finish speaking, while he grabbed onto the girl’s shoulder.

Boom!

Suddenly, a human figure raised from the curtain, and rushed towards the woman.

At the same time, the Cold Radiation was cast upon the both of them, hitting them hard as they were about to activate their Willpower abilities.

Boom!

The man took a few steps back once he was hit. Whereas the girl was kicked in the abdomen by Garen.

“Void!!”

As she screamed, a powerful Willpower was released from the woman’s body.

The invisible force spread outwards, with the woman as the epicenter. The rubbles, Miniature Mech, and even the corpses on the ground were sent flying everywhere. All the cloth in the kitchen were torn apart. In the howling wind, Garen’s body flew out as if he was hit by a train.

He spat out a huge amount of blood from his mouth.

Garen felt that most of his bones were broken. Along with this hit, his injured body suffered even more damage. He had been relying on an exhausting huge amount of Potential Points to forcingly suppress his injury since Potential Points could be used to increase the regeneration process. However, it was being restrained by the Divine Wind General’s residual Willpower, resulting in a very slow regeneration.

To make his injury worse, he was now hit by such a powerful Willpower.

Garen laid on the ground; he was unable to move. His skin was cracked and not a single part of him looked unharmed. He had literally become a blood man, drenched in blood from head to toe, and was on his last breath. He was on the verge of unconsciousness as he couldn’t control the inner injury of his body. The Potential Points were unable to recover the injury caused by two heavy attacks.

“That’s a close one. Is this guy really a Level One trash?!” The two had just calmed down from the shock of the sudden ambush.

The duo walked towards Garen’s side, and kicked his head.

“He’s almost dead,” The woman frowned. Although she was kicked in the abdomen, she didn’t suffer many injuries as she had a strong body and managed to released her Willpower in time. She seemed fine, excluding her pale face. “How should we deal with him?”

“Bring him out of this place. The interrogator would make him spill out whatever we need to know.” The man shrugged as he looked at the corpses and Miniature Mech around the area. “To be honest, I’m really interested in how this guy has managed to kill so many people.”

He walked towards the corpse, and flipped it with his leg as he tried to find the lethal wound.

Suddenly, he gasped softly.

There was no sign of wound from the corpse. What made it even stranger was that the corpse seemed like an empty shell. Other than the layer of skin, the internal organs seemed to have been sucked dry. It was like a predator spider that used a poison to melt the internal organs of its prey. After the prey died, it would then slowly suck it dry, leaving behind a layer of empty shell.

The man suddenly shivered. He had never seen such an assassination technique before.

“Let’s move out quickly,” The woman said softly from behind.

“Alright.” The man turned around. However, his pupil shrunk as a sharp dagger was pierced through his heart without mercy.

Crack!

The dagger twisted deeper into the wound.

The attacker was the woman. Her appearance was rather bizarre, with red eyes and her skin covered in a layer of light grey transparent scale. She looked rather cold yet explosive, as if she was a volcano that was on the verge of explosion.

“Snow…”

The man tried his best to reach out his hand, trying to touch the woman’s face. However, the gaze in his eyes dimmed down as the dagger that had pierced his heart twisted once more.

Thump.

He fell to his face.

Roar!

The woman who had been mutated with the Distorted Seed started to cry in agony; tears flowed out of her eyes. However, as her body mutated further on, she was gradually covered in a thicker grey scale.

Crack!

A long and sharp tail emerged out from her back – a part of her new mutated body.

Under the effect of the Distorted Seed, the powerful Half Moon Grade Willpower quickly evolved. It became one time… Two times… Three times more powerful!!

In that instant, the woman’s strength tripled, and her body size increased tremendously. A third grey-white eye started appearing on her forehead.

“Go… Kill them all! Kill everything that you can see…”

Garen laughed mercilessly as he laid on the ground.

One could only wonder how powerful a Half Moon Grade Powerhouse could be under the parasitic effect of the Distorted Seed? He was eager to know as well.

In an instant, the woman disappeared. It wasn’t just her Willpowered that had become stronger. Her physical attributes had tripled as well.

This was where the Hellfrost Peacock Technique shone the most. Its main prowess didn’t come from its host. Instead, it is to create chaos and control beings via the Distorted Seed. Once it is planted on a powerful being, it would increase their strength further to create chaos, killing everything in sight.

After the mutated woman monster rushed out of the room, the sound of Mech exploding was instantly heard.

The screams of fear and panic could be heard everywhere.

“What is that!?””It’s a monster! Fire!!”

Roar!

The woman would occasionally scream at the top of her lungs.

Garen didn’t know how powerful a Half Moon Grade Powerhouse was with their strength tripled. However, he knew that this was the best time for him to escape as the chaos would soon be under controlled. Even if a mutated monster had the strength of an Inherited Level, a powerful Pilot would be able to handle it. Without intelligence and wisdom, it would still be a monster without intelligence no matter how powerful it was. Its only purpose was to create chaos.

He then wore the equipment that belonged to the corpses that he had sucked dry with Hellfrost Peacock’s blue strands and walked out of the hospital, acting as a Mech that was on the verge of dying.

It was already a mess when he walked out. The team that had surrounded the area was gone. What was left was just a pile of corpses. After the woman had mutated, the true power of the Willpower of Void was no longer when it was applied on a Mech. She was already a killer machine with her enhanced physical characteristics. Within half a minute, she had managed to annihilate everything outside. The Void of Winds was everywhere, tearing the Mechs apart.

The Miniature Mechs survivors on the ground who tried to get up from the puddle of blood immediately dropped back down to the ground again as they were shot by Garen.

After a few shots, Garen then added two Potential Points into his Vitality to counter the residual Willpower on his body. Following that, his body’s injury started to recover slowly, in which he was able to recover a little bit of energy eventually.

With the gun at his crutch, Garen walked towards a broken Big Mech with a limp. It was completely broken from the explosions and no part of it was perfect. It was fated to be sent to the garbage station.

Garen circled the Mech for a few rounds as he couldn’t fight against the tiredness in him. He then opened the Mech’s empty homing missile compartment located at the right leg as if it was a normal thing to do. He then jumped into it, covered it up, and fell into deep sleep.

Chapter 929: Hope 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Heh… here here. Yes! Throw it over here.”

A few tow truck drivers were maneuvering their vehicles as they tried to throw the Mech’s arm into the pile of garbage mountain.

At the edge of the garbage mountain just outside the Dawn City, tow trucks were transferring the remains from the horrible incident in the city to the garbage mountain.

It formed mountains of garbages that were waiting to be burnt.

The black tow truck pulled a Mech that was beyond repair, and threw it into the pile of rubbish. Then, it turned around and left the area. The whole area was now quiet.

Although this area is just on the edge of the region radioactive belt, it was already considered as within the radioactive belt. Before the garbage was burnt off, these garbage mountains were the main income of the radioactive people. In order to occupy these garbage mountains, many small-scale attacks had emerged in the radioactive people’s town that was nearby this area. In the end, a small town called Lion had successfully obtained the ownership in this area.

The morning sky gradually turned into an evening sky. from the horizon, a convoy drove by the radioactive people slowly came into view. As the radiation was at the lowest during evening hours, it was the time where the radioactive people were the most active.

The convoy was greyish-black, and it mainly consisted of motorbikes and trucks. Most of the radioactive people wore leather shirts, leather pants, and a pair of windproof glasses. They were tall and muscular, carrying guns and bullets on their back.

“Look kids! It’s the latest Mech from the region! Hahaha! We finally have something to work with!” The bald, and muscular leader laughed happily. He looked ecstatic as he looked at the newly formed garbage mountain.

“I hope there’s a well-conditioned life support system since the one we had was broken beyond repair!” A red-haired ponytail woman said with a grass stick in her mouth.

“Big Sis’s habit of sleeping naked still hasn’t changed at all! Haha!” The man in the convoy teased.

“Come after me if you have the balls!” The red-haired woman pointed a middle finger towards her back. “You’re trash if you’re just all talks!”

“I don’t think the person who dares to go after you have yet to be born!” The crowd in the convoy laughed as if they weren’t fazed at all.

“Tsk!”

The woman looked at the pile of garbages that was far away as she scanned through the eye-catching remains of the Mechs. “It looks like something big had happened in the region. These were all military grade Mechs and they’re destroyed to this state.”

Baldy nodded in agreement.

“It looks like they were destroyed by some strong torsion, and shear stress instead of firearms.”

Soon, the convoy arrived at the foot of the garbage mountains. All of them got down of the car, and wore their Half Mechanical Arms that could boost their strength. They then proceed to disassemble the Mechs for useful materials and parts.

The red-haired woman operated the mechanical arm without any expression. Then, she naturally disassembled the parts. Her movements and techniques were so natural that it would put the mechanical experts from the region to shame. This amazing skill of hers was trained in the radiation belt since she was young. These pair of mechanical arms could not only be used to tear the Mech apart, it could be used to tear a person apart too!

Her name was East Perrin. She’s the leader of Leo City, largest within the Dawn City. On the other hand, Baldy was her assistant. Regardless if it was physical or intellectual attributes, no radiation people could hope to match them if they did not undergo education or training.

East Perrin tore down the parts naturally as she observed the others’ actions. Occasionally, she would comment on her underling’s techniques. This sight was incredibly rare among the radiation people. Compared to the other cities, Leo City was one of the extreme minority of the radiation people who teamed up, and worked alongside each other. Although their quantity wasn’t large, they were extremely united. More so, they enjoyed everything together, including having a feast. It could be considered a miracle in the deserted radiation where food was more valuable than gold.

All these were made possible because of East Perrin’s leadership.

As East Perrin was tearing down the Mechs and instructing her underling, her hand suddenly jolted as if she had encountered a part that couldn’t be torn apart.

She regained her focus, and looked at the item in front of her. It was thick, big, and completely black like a dirty black wooden pile. There was even a thin slit where missiles would fire out from.

“Part of the leg?”

East Perrin popped her hands out from the mechanical arms, and touched the item with her bare hands. A sudden sensation of frost radiated from the part and into her bone, causing her to sneeze loudly.

“How could it be this cold?” A hint of excitement started to show on her face. She had been disassembling Mech’s parts for quite a long time now. Occasionally, she would encounter a unique and powerful weapon that was similar to the Quick Frost Bomb. Perhaps this would be one of those Quick Frost Bomb that was yet to be discovered.

After pondering for a while, she attempted to cut away the Mech’s leg through the small gap in the missile’s chamber. Unfortunately, the small gap was frozen with an incredibly tough ice, and she was unable to cut it away.

She then decided to carry the whole part up before she threw it into the truck behind her.

“This is mine and no one can touch this! It may be very dangerous!” She ordered. After that, she continued to search through among the trash.

It only took them awhile to search through everything, and the convoy left the area afterwards.

Approximately an hour later, a fleet of black soldiers flew out from the region, to the pile of garbages to conduct a thorough research.

“I’ve said this before, who do you think would know when this pile of garbages was disposed here? How is it possible for someone to hide inside the remains of a Mech. These were garbages that were about to be burnt to crisps,” A soldier complained frustratingly from within.

“Let’s not care about it that much and follow the orders,” Another soldier said softly. “This is Lord Biochemist’s order. We’re fine as long as Lord Fila doesn’t find out.”

“I understand.”

The group of people then took out the Biochemist’s life detector, and started scanning the surrounding.

Only a small portion of the remains of the Mech was taken away earlier by the convoy. As the majority of the parts were still here, and the damage done to the Mechs were extremely severe, no one could determine which parts were taken away.

“Say, why do you think Lord Biochemist is so concerned about a wounded man?”

“Who knows. I heard that this patient has a strong physical characteristic that was similar to a radiation people. So his corpse has a high research value.”

The group of people scanned the area as they discussed. However, they didn’t manage to find anything, so they had no choice but to go back empty-handed.

Far away inside an invisible flying ship.

Bamente, the Biochemist frowned as he stared in that direction.

“Perhaps I have guessed wrongly? Is that mutant really Nonosiva?”

He lowered his head as he looked at the genetic report, recalling that a merely wounded soldier could push him, who possessed a Level Five Willpower away with that mysterious strength… He was getting excited as his instinct told him that if he was able to find the source of this strength, it would lead him to a path of unrivaled strength.

He had already known that something was off during the test. Although he suspected that there could be someone hiding inside the remains of the Mech, he didn’t voice out. Instead, he told someone to transport the debris to this location. Unfortunately, Fila wasted his time by asking a few questions, causing him not to be the first one to reach the area.

After the scanning team had left the area, he got down from the flying ship personally with his scanning equipment. He then scanned the whole area on his own.

Again, he didn’t find anything.

“Looks like that mutant was really a mutated Nonosiva…” He gave a sigh of relief as he looked extremely disappointed. “What a waste… That man is nowhere to be found. Once the gene has decayed, the information within the gene would become a mess. It would be as difficult as finding liquid substance inside a pile of ashes if I want to obtain anything useful from it.”

Feeling extremely disappointed, he turned around, headed back to the invisible ship, and left the area.

***************

“What? He’s nowhere to be found?!” Fila frowned as he stared at the underling who reported the situation.

“Rumor has it that he became that overpowered mutated monster. Although we didn’t find any genetic link from that monster, the only explanation is that Nonosiva has turned into that wild monster that destroyed the whole team,” The underling replied softly.

Inside the office, Fila threw the pen in his hand into the pen holder as he opened the document in front of him. He then fiddled with his hair using his fingers.

“Then, what happened to that monster?”

“It was severely injured by the Black-Clothed General who was guarding the area, and escaped into the radiation belt. Since half of its body was torn apart, it might not live for long,” The underling immediately replied. “According to the Lord Black-Clothed General, that monster shows no sign of intelligence. He only knows how to create chaos. It would kill anything on sight, and does not care for anything else. Sometimes, it would even try to eat the corpse.”

“According to the genetic scientists’ report that was submitted later, the monster’s strength has a limit. Its strength relies on a large scale, one-time use of burning his body’s potential to unleash his true strength. It’s equivalent to burning its own life force. According to the intensity, it can only live for four days at most before its genes are destroyed. With that, it would die.”

He continued speaking.

“We’ve obtained a huge amount of cards that stored the Universal Units from Nonosiva’s house. We also found a contract agreement to purchase the Rainbow Stones, and Refined Fuel Powder. In addition to that, we also found some good antiques and a captain-ranked model Mech in his garage.”

“What about the incomplete Exclusive Mech from the White Dragon’s Base?” Fila was most concerned about this as the cheapest Exclusive Mech was still much more expensive than a typical Mech. It was the main item of value.

“It was obtained by the Black Flood Party when they intercepted our men outside of the house,” The underling said helplessly.

“Whatever. This incident ends here. A crippled will be of no threat to us even if he survives.” Fila gestured his hand to tell the underling to leave the room.

After the underling left, he sat back in his seat, and looked at the document that was half organized. After that, he took out a projector and a laptop, in which the former projected out a holographic keyboard as he typed swiftly on it.

Soon, he entered a colorful pornographic website. As he clicked swiftly, seemingly at random, the webpage suddenly turned black, revealing a cold and pale old man with white hair.

“The plan is almost done and according to schedule. All we need is your order,” Fila said respectfully.

“All the penetrations are completed?” The old man asked in a deep tone.

Chapter 930: Hope 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I’ve put in ten days of effort, and I have figured out its overall movement and tracking. I’ve just sorted them out a moment ago.” Fila picked up the normal-looking document as he answered.

Within this period of time, his main job was to handle these large-scale movements. He had spent countless of days and nights on it. He even read half of the report regarding Nonosiva’s encirclement and suppression that he devised himself before going back to work.

“Ice Dragon, Dark Light, Thorn, and I have finished our deployment and can proceed with the killing at a moment’s notice,” Fila answered as he nodded his head.

“Be wary of their actions. That man is notorious for his arbitrary,” The old man warned.

“We will. Obtaining intel is my specialty. Don’t worry about it,” Fila replied with confidence.

“Good.” The old white haired man nodded his head before he disappeared from the monitor and the pornographic website turned back on.

Fila closed the website, and started checking every step of the movement that had been arranged. No mistakes were tolerable in this plan as this had been planned for so many years, just waiting for this moment.

****************

Universal Calendar Year 11527, 25th August.

A huge incident had startled the whole region.

Peace had been around for many years as war had reached a stalemate. The talented First Seat of Blackboard Region, Black Star Diofie had challenged Maria Region’s top powerhouse, Suanna. Both of them had agreed to fight to death at the Mars Canyon located in the dangerous radiation belt.

The terrifying power of Inherited Level had doubled the size of the Mars Canyon. What made everyone surprised was that both Black Star Diofie and Suanna had disappeared; they were nowhere to be found. Even the investigation team couldn’t find any trace of them at all.

Both Blackboard and Maria Region were angered as they, both powerful regions, couldn’t sustain a loss that involved their First Seat geniuses.

Both parties had voiced out. They blamed the each other’s party and that was the mastermind behind this conspiracy. One would need to have an extraordinary power in order to make an Inherited Level powerhouse disappear.

The frictions between two regions grew stronger as the frequency of conflict between Black Star and Suanna’s soldiers kept rising. Both regions had increased the number of soldiers standing by at the border, causing the whole situation rather anxious.

Under this circumstances, Blackboard Region’s new generation was promoted. Medero, Karfi, and Narissis were all promoted to Inherited Level, becoming the new pillars of the Blackboard Region.

It had been two months since Nonosiva was surrounded, and his parents had received notice that he had become a traitor to the country. All of his property and resources under his name were confiscated.

The Nonosiva family’s heavenly days were now thrown into an endless abyss…

***************

Outside of Blackboard Region was Leo City in the radiation belt.

The city looked extremely strange as huge black stones were everywhere, and people were living in these weirdly shaped stones. They had used a special instrument to dig into these stones. It was a house that could provide them with warmth and coolness during winter and summer. Some stones were half buried underground, which could be used as a basement.

The largest black stone inside had been carved into Leo City’s emblem, the lion.

It was also where the leader East Perrin lived in.

It was early in the morning as the hunter and Acquisition Team exited the city through the metal gate via motorcycles and trucks at great speed.

Every day, they went to the radioactive pond nearby to hunt for mutated fish — it was the main source of food for these radiation people. They would occasionally gather some good tasting fruit. Although it had its illusive side effect, the entertainments in the city were just playing chess, cards, and nothing else.

The Acquisition Team would head out to the energy harvesters which they had set beforehand. These harvesters were able to absorb light and wind energy to store it in an empty energy battery. It could then be reused as an energy source. At the same time, it functioned as the patrol team, patrolling around the territory.

With Leo City as the epicenter, their territory spanned about twenty kilometers square wide.

East Perrin stood by the window on the second floor of her house as she looked at the fleet leaving, she sighed at them. Her red hair was messy and she was only wearing a thin layer of white, half-transparent pajama. There was a lion-shaped scar on her shoulder that was given to her by radiation. She also had a black lion tattoo on her body, which was also the origin of the city’s name.

It seemed like East Perrin didn’t sleep well last night as she yawned and went back into her bedroom.

Her bedroom was different from a typical girl’s bedroom. Inside this medium sized room, excluding the bed, it was filled with oil stains, parts, mechanical equipment, and a messy instrument that was half assembled.

The whole room smelled rather strong and pleasing as it was a combination of her body odor and the smell of the oils.

East Perrin’s parents were both radiation people. though she had never entered the region before. She had heard stories of the inner region ever since she was young, and that was why she had decided to find a location near the region as a territory.

With her powerful strength and her mechanical knowledge, she had gathered a group of people. At the same time, she built herself a water purifier with the parts obtained from the garbage pile.

This water purifier was named as Eve by everyone. It would be able to purify radioactive water down to 10%, which was considered a good technology in the radiation belt.

With her mechanical expertise, she had built a powerful self-defense system for the city. She even trained a group of maintenance members who were good in these techniques.

Hence, Leo City was born.

“It has been so many years…” East Perrin grabbed onto her hair as she picked up a mirror, staring at an elegant female face. Though what she saw was a tired looking face instead of the awkward and wild look that her underlings always saw.

She was only nineteen, but she had learned how to be independent in the radiation belt since she was five. She had killed thirty-two people when she was almost raped at ten. By the age of thirteen, she followed a Pilot who was up to no good, yet she ran away from him after obtaining a technique from him. By the age of sixteen, she had already killed hundreds of people with her own hands.

In the radiation belt, one could not survive without being cruel. That was the truth.

“This kind of lifestyle is truly boring…” East Perrin shook her head as she tried to throw out the useless dilemma in her mind.

She then casually picked up an electromagnetic detecting instrument and walked to the corner of the room where the Mech’s leg was placed — the one that she took away the last time. Almost two meters of the thigh part of the body was black, and it gave off a natural cold and frosty radiation. This had only gradually changed within this period of time, and that made East Perrin very curious.

She had used many ways to try to open the missile chamber that was located in the Mech’s leg but it was to no avail. Even the with the strength of the larger cutting machine, it was unable to cut it open.

The hardness of this part had far surpassed any standard hardness scale.

She picked up the instrument and started to analyze the electromagnetic sensitivity in different areas of the part. Through the sensitivity result, she could combine it with other analysis to determine the weakest point in the part. She would then work her way up from that part, in order to save her time.

However, through her continuous research, she had found a strange regularity inside the frozen part.

Once, when she had accidentally spilled over the Life Support’s nutritional liquid onto the part, she surprisingly found a response from the radioactive instrument.

She had realized that the intensity of radiation on the surface of that part had a slight increased by 0.1 degrees.

“A response towards nutrients, eh?” She stood up and stroked her chin. “Let’s see how much of a reaction can you give off today!”

She then picked up a bottle of an overly concentrated, lower grade nutritional liquid which even the radiation people did not dare to ingest. She then proceeded tp opened the bottle cap. The greyish-white bottle contained the thick viscous nutritional liquid that resembled milk. It was so thick that it dripped out in a clump, and fell onto the center of the Mech’s leg.

A strange phenomenon occurred.

The surface of the part faintly glowed with a tinge of blue. However, the blue stood out more especially on the surrounding area where the nutritional liquid was dropped on.

East Perrin crouched down and got closer to the part. She could clearly see that the surface of the part was giving off a faint frosty-white air while it absorbed the nutritional liquid on the surface like a cotton.

The highly concentrated nutritional liquid was considered toxic towards the radiation people. However, the part wasn’t affected by the slightest. This made East Perrin extremely amazed.

Beep beep…

The radiation instrument beside her started beeping.

She reached out her hand and picked it up to see that the reading had increased once more.

“Its radioactive measurement has increased fifteen times more than the initial value. However, what’s strange is that this cold radiation seems to radiate half a meter out of its surrounding. Hehe…” East Perrin couldn’t comprehend such a phenomenon.

As she looked at thigh part that was quickly absorbing all the nutritional liquid, she suddenly had a wild idea.

She took a glance at the big bottle of nutritional liquid in her hand.

“Since you like this so much, let’s see how much can you absorb then!”

Out of curiosity, she opened the bottle and poured everything onto the leg.

Silently, the nutritional liquid kept flowing out of the bottle, but the moment the liquid came into contact with the part, the Mech’s part had absorbed all of them clean.

After that, East Perrin had lost interest in this item. She left for her bedroom after recording down the radiation reading. There were a lot of daily activities she had to deal with within the territory so she couldn’t neglect her duties by just focusing on her interest.

Within the pitch black space inside the Mech’s part where she couldn’t see.

Garen was in a fetal position inside the part. Due to his injury, it made his body become as dry as a corpse. However, blue thin lines were madly crawling out from his body and connected themselves to the inner wall of the Mech’s leg as it kept absorbing the radioactive nutrients from the outside.

Along with the absorbed nutrients, Garen’s body gradually started to wake up from deep hibernation.

The potential points and the residual inherited blue colored Willpower were still battling against each other within his body. On the other hand, the Living Secret Technique was slowly absorbing the nutritional liquid, growing stronger to the point where his body was finally recovering at a snail’s pace.

At first, Garen was on the verge of dying. Though after absorbing the nutritional liquid, he was finally able to restore his strength.

Chapter 931: Awaken 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A distance away from Leo City, an abandoned highway among the remote hills.

At this moment, a team of men in short braids, riding on red motorcycles was hollering. They were making weird sounds as they whipped the metal chains in the air, constantly forming shadows hovering above their heads.

“Woo!”

“We discovered a new town, hahaha!!”

“Seems like we now have new food!”

“Eat! Eat! Eat!” Someone yelled.

On the leading motorcycle, there was a man with the longest whip in his hands. His eyes were slightly swollen, his skin a pasty white. The weird thing was that the braid behind him was different from the others. His black whip seemed to be moving faintly like a living creature, slowly crawling about his neck.

“It’s been five days since we have eaten, I’m so hungry…” The leading man muttered.

A passerby on a motorcycle slowly moved in the direction of the small town in front, and the town nearby just happened to be the rival of Leo City — Vulture City.

The leader of the town was a strong, conceited man with a good hand in heavy artillery skills.

“The hog we captured just yesterday had said, there are still five towns ahead in front of this region. Most of them survive by relying on garbage rummaging. The town was pretty big, about two-three hundred population. Seems like we will be able to eat some good food!” A motorcycle at the edge picked up its speed, laughing and exchanged smiles with the leader of the group.

“Take care of the town first!” The Chief raised his right arm up. His fingers were as red as blood, sharp and slender, just like five razor-sharp miniature daggers.

“Forward!” He suddenly shouted. It was followed by a strong enormous sound wave that erupted from his throat. The entire surface of the road shook ferociously.

A small town in the distance, under the morning sun at the observatory, a sentinel quickly rang the electronic alarm.

The continuous beeping sound of the alarm spread in all directions.

The collection team and the hunting team who were still out working around the area speedily returned.

The town was a mess. The leader was a brawny man with short hair, who was swiftly making his way up to the observatory. He took the electronic binoculars and looked towards the side.

“It’s the hunters…” The brawny man muttered.

“Hunters?!! Don’t they just roam around the northeast area? Why would they suddenly come here!” The deputy, who was by the edge, jumped in shock and hurriedly asked.

“Maybe something happened there, perhaps some other reasons. These monsters were prowling around the area. It’s no surprise that they made it here,” the brawny man flung the binoculars to the deputy. “See for yourself.”

He turned to glance at the dozen of young adults who had begun with manpower preparations for the upcoming battle.

“Prepare for battle!”

“Huo!”

The people below raised their firearms, and weapons one by one in response.

“Boss, we’ve never battled the hunters. Should we go seek backup from the other towns?” The deputy started to feel anxious.

“What are you afraid of? I’m here!” The brawn man cast a glance of annoyance towards him.

Hunters, a unique race of the radiation belt, are classified as the humans who were infected by the radiation disease. They practice cannibalism; they are brutal, temperamental, and powerful. However, most of their character had been affected by their instinctive desire to eat. Therefore, their characteristics are a mess – they only know how to attack with instinct. As for slightly complicated logical operations, they have trouble understanding and carrying out simple actions.

The radiation belt had the highest number of hunters. People who were driven out of the region after being infected by the radiation disease were everywhere. Eventually, they became hunters. This ratio would constitute up to 60%, and as for the rest, they were either dead or objects of exploitations. It would be relatively rare, especially for a normal human, to have the ability to survive.

The most barbarous thing was that hunters do not have a long lifeline. They only have just about five to six years. In spite of that, their fecundity was extremely frightening. Comparable to spiders, hunters are able to give birth to five or six, seven or eight, even at least ten children at once. Not only that, once someone became a hunter, their body would carry a forceful virus which would be sufficient to infect a normal radioactive person to become the same kind of low-class hunter. This was the most horrible part.

Fecundity, coupled with the pollution, was a major key to hunters being able to survive in this era of science and technology.

In fact, they were the highest population in the radiation belt. Normally, radioactive people would build up many defense systems to not only resist the threat of ubiquitous mutated insects but also to guard against them.

Boom!

A deafening sound of explosion blasted, severely hitting the army of hunters not far away.

The huge impact force of the explosion overturned the abandoned road, ripping off the cement road mercilessly. Blocks of cement hit the hunters on their head but only left minor wounds before it bounced away weakly.

Few of the hunters taking the lead were sporting a bloody face. Wiping their face grimly, they let out a higher-pitched howl. Even their glares toward the town in the distance became more murderous.

“Kill!”

“Eat!”

The group of people growled. Some of them only knew a few simple word pronunciations.

The entire team was about twenty people. With that, the army formed into the shape of two serpents, and they dashed towards the small town at full speed.

With a ‘bang’, another long-ranged explosion landed, breaking the ground. A hunter was hit by the pieces of rocks and his body burst open on the spot. A mixture of flesh and blood splashed in all directions; the battle had officially begun.

*******************

Leo Town.

East Perrin looked down at the sand model before her.

The two deputies were crouching by her side, sharing the same frown while staring at the sand model.

The three of them were the strongest in the entire Leo Town. Both deputies were Level Two Willpower Masters whereas East Perrin was a Level Three Master. That was also one of the vital reason to why she became the leader of Leo Town.

“Adger who was on patrol duty earlier came over to report that he had spotted sight of hunters roaming about in the Northeast side. I didn’t believe it until Xiao Dong, who just came by, reporting that they have gotten complete pictures of hunters rushing in the direction of Vulture Town. They were almost caught by the hunters too. Imagine if they had been discovered by these monsters, these kids would definitely not be able to make it back!” The deputy, Caster said solemnly.

“How many were there roughly?” East Perrin placed her index finger in her mouth and began biting them slowly.

“Looking at the picture, there should be at least twenty of them,” Caster replied.

The other deputy, Mellon was a much older man with a beard that had faint white glows from within.

“I had once encountered a hunter in a small town somewhere in the East. They may be mad, but they have a strong physique. Some of the stronger ones are even good enough to fight against the mutated beasts, though their lifeline is pretty short. The worst thing is, hunters are cannibals so there will simply be no negotiations. They only kill!”

“What about their fighting power?” Caster asked.

“It’s tough, but as long as two Level Two hunters don’t show up at the same time, the others should not be a major difficulty. They’re afraid of firearms, so just take note of the number. It is mainly those Level Two or above hunters who would have the Hardened Skin Ability. Other than explosions, there’s no other way that you can defeat them!” Mellon shrugged reluctantly, “Thinking back to that year when the hunters attacked the town, I still shudder with fear.”

“What do you guys think? Will the Vulture Town be able to hold them down?” East Perrin whispered.

“I don’t know…” Mellon shook his head, “If there are no Level Two hunters, they should be alright. However, if there is… I’m afraid we must be prepared to face a vast amount of hunters. Their rate of pollution is pretty quick…”

What Mellon said sent chills down East Perrin’s, and Caster’s spines.

“Hopefully the Vulture Town is able to hold them down!” East Perrin stood up, “Immediately release the surveillance drones over Vulture Town. Energy consumption doesn’t matter. This is not the time to save money!”

“Alright, I shall start arranging everything,” Mellon nodded.

“Don’t forget to check the weapons storage — how many energy batteries do we still have, how much stock for bullets do we still have. Send a few people from the processing workshop.”

“The processing workshop has only one automatic bullet production line. Sending people over won’t increase production, because only two thousand bullets can be produced within a day. On the other hand, energy batteries are better stocked in comparison. I’m just worried that the ray gun isn’t strong enough…” Mellon let out a wry smile.

“We can’t possibly expect everyone to step up with a blade and fight, right?” East Perrin was getting slightly irritated.

“What about the other towns?” Caster asked quietly, “If we really can’t do it, why not retreat?”

“Retreat?” East Perrin was also considering this dilemma. With Mellon, the old encyclopedia by her side, they had a clear understanding of the hunters’ strength and what the hunters were capable of. However, if there were even just two Level Two hunters among the twenty other hunters, they were all in deep trouble. In reality, Level Two hunters were the equivalent of two heavily-armed standard Mechs. Even though this was just a theoretical comparison, a Level Two Pilot would definitely be stronger than a Level Two hunter.

While the three of them were hesitating, a pager rang from Caster’s waist.

“Uncle Caster! A hunter just turned up!!” Noises could be heard from the other side.

“A lot of… A lot!!””Run! Back to town!”

“Oh my God! There must be at least fifty or sixty of them!!”

Voices were mixed together, and the three of them were seemingly frowning more and more.

“What is going on there? Talk!” Caster yelled.

“They’re everywhere in this town! The town has been surrounded! The whole town has been surrounded! Oh my God!” The one holding onto the pager replied loudly.

The trio swiftly ran out of the room and approached the observatory to look towards the distance.

Just one glance and the trio was completely shocked.

The town was packed with hunters everywhere. Their eyes were swollen, skin a shade of ghastly pale white, black hair with short braids at the back. Each of them was agile and seemed healthy. Some of them even had their disgusting saliva drooling from their mouths.

From all corners of Leo Town, the collection team and the hunting team had returned. About thirty of them poured into the town and instantly, the construction of Leo Town’s war fortress was resumed.

Steel gates were fiercely dropped down against the ground.

Soon, the entire town formed a cylindrical dark gray fortress. The fences and gates were made from a thick layer of alloy that was as thick as a palm. Above the fence stood thirty young men who were holding their weapons, looking downwards.

A lot of them shared a look of nervous, but most of them had a natural expression. Although they had never come into contact with the hunters, they had experienced a lot of battles, and they were confident in each other.

The three leaders were calm and confident too, standing on the observatory with composure. This motivated them and brought them the confidence to fight.

“Attack!” East Perrin raised her arm, shouting into the megaphone handed by the deputy.

Bang bang bang!

A series of gunshots began.

A few hunters were knocked onto the ground, blood oozing out of their heads.

These hunters did not seem to have a leader, but neither did they seem hungry. They were just wandering around dazed. At this moment, forced by the sound of gunshots, they stopped in their tracks, surveying the whole town.

Woo!

Suddenly, a dramatic high-pitched whistling sound could be heard from the distance. It seemed as if a hunter was howling.

“It’s a Level Two hunter!!” Mellon’s expression paled immediately.

East Perrin and Caster also felt that the whole situation had just gotten even more complicated.

“What do we do?!” Caster looked at East Perrin.

“What’s the speed for hunters?” East Perrin asked in a low tone.

“Really fast, we probably can’t outrun them,” Mellon shook his head.

Chapter 932: Awaken 2

“Then let’s prepare ourselves fully, see if they dare to come through!” There was a look of determination on East Perrin’s face. “We have firepower and defense, our food supply can probably last us for two weeks. I don’t believe they would be able to stick around that long!”

Both deputies nodded in agreement, and left to quickly survey the surroundings of the town in case there were loopholes in their defense system.

The defense team was divided into two groups of fifteen men each; one will patrol whereas the other returned to rest.

Soon, the predators which were gathering outside head towards the direction of the sounds. Not much longer, they were moving as fast as the vehicles, vanishing upon the horizon.

The people in town let out a sigh of relief.

However, through her binoculars, East Pirren could see that there were still predators far in the surroundings and still keeping their eyes on this town.

She then understood better. “We’ve been marked,” she thought to herself. The predators may not be smart, but their sense of logic was still there and was sufficient enough to make simple plans and strategies.

She has witnessed a predator’s speed. If they were to leave this town, it would not take long for the predators to catch up. Without any defense, they would not even have much resistance power to fight back.

“Guess we will just have to stand strong then.” A sense of danger lurked in her mind.

However, she was not aware that not only this area was compromised. In fact, as long as there was a crack on the ground in the radiation belt, large pack of predators will enter non-stop through the crack.

They will kill anybody on sight, and destroy any towns they see! They are like wild dogs, generally breaking out into the open once every century but this time it happened earlier and nobody expected it.

Only the radiation belt will experience this kind of catastrophe. The other territories raised up their own isolation shields, completely cutting off all contact from the radiation belt. The territories looked as if they were islands amongst the sea with their white lights, the Blackboard region’s outpost were also disengaged and commanded to return to the region.

The territories were strong but they did not expand much, allowing the radioactive people to enjoy and dig out the many minerals around the region and used it to deal business with people from the region. Because of this, they could only maintain their territory and strength this much during the predator wave. It is not that they did not want to expand, but the general folks within the territory had no idea how the predator wave will actually add on to the horror and stress if they do expand.

The entire surface of the mother planet, all the territories including Central Academy, were just like a cluster of stars distributed randomly at the center of the four cardinal points around the area, were all surrounded by the predators.

On the other hand, the stronghold of the radiation belt was that everyone was mostly holed up. Such a predator wave would last a day and only withdraw during nightfall.

Just like that every day. Even if it’s just half a day would give the radioactive people hope.

*******************

Nightfall came quietly.

Even though it was quiet for the whole day, East Perrin was exhausted from the intense pent-up feelings.

She needs to be at the forefront constantly, to provide support, to calm everyone down and to avoid chaos in town. Being the strongest radioactive person in town, if she herself were to fall, the whole town will surely collapse as well.

Back in her bedroom, she glanced at the parts of the thigh unit at the corner of the room. Its upper clasp held a bottle of nutrient solution which was already completely absorbed, leaving just a gray crust covering the surface of the component. That was the residue of the nutrient solution.

“You really did finish it?” East Perrin walked over in surprise and picked up the bottle. Looking at the bottle, it really was empty.

“Anyways, this highly radioactive nutrient solution was previously used for gardening purposes, we have plenty of it. It will be good to see how much exactly you can absorb!” East Perrin walked out of the bedroom and ordered her people to send over another dozen bottles of unwanted nutrient solution.

She poured all of the nutrients onto the part.

The surface of the part was covered with a clear, blue shade of the nutrient solution, and it was being absorbed at a speed that the naked eye could observe.

“Gee…” East Perrin’s curiosity got stronger. Amongst the many kinds of mutated creatures she had seen since she was young, she had never seen such an abnormal transformation.

And it was inside the unit where she could not see.

Garen’s curled up body had recovered to his usual size. His eyes flickered slightly and he seemed to be regaining his conscious.

The strange thing was, the two marks of Energy Machinists which were floating behind him started to glow. The Energy Machinist Key on Garen’s body which was not broken also seemed to be vibrating slowly.

‘Verifying Level Two energy machinist qualification, are you able to participate in the special ability space market in the vicinity?’

A subtle sense of Willpower force asked Garen.

“Energy Machinist… market?” Garen asked in a daze.

“… Participate.”

‘Confirmation is complete. Commencing separation of Willpower, entering the special ability space…’

Waking up and opening his eyes, Garen glanced around the surrounding darkness. Within seconds, he felt as if he had entered a rainbow-like cylindrical tunnel, flying upwards swiftly.

Not long after, the end of the tunnel appeared in a form of glowing, white light.

Flying out from the cylindrical tunnel, Garen covered both of his eyes instinctively to let it slowly adjust to the sudden brightness.

He was at the plaza which he visited last time. But this plaza seemed to be slightly different.

Its ground was made of white jade, a water fountain with a levitating leaping dolphin was right in the middle, as if Anti-gravity Skills was used.

There were not many shops surrounding the square, just five or six. Maybe that was why the plaza seemed relatively small.

“Garen!!”

Suddenly, a woman’s voice arose from a distance.

Garen lifted his head and looked over just to see a haggard Celine running over quickly. They were not surrounded by many people, at most about twenty or thirty people.

A few energy machinists were squatting by the stalls communicating with the stall owners in silence. Some were standing and asking questions as if investigating something.

There were also a few who were standing together and exchanging whispers. Celine walked over swiftly without attracting attention, and pulled Garen aside towards a corner.

“Relax, only you can hear my voice!” Celine said loudly. Her face was filled with joy. “I knew you were alive!”

“I also thought I will die.” Garen shook his head. “Such bad luck, both factions somehow dragged me into their battle. I guess destruction pursues the great.”

“Destruction pursues the great? Nice saying,” Celine nodded in agreement, her eyes were slightly red.

“I’ve been here waiting for you for almost ten days. There is a predator wave, the special ability space is now the only medium to communicate and trade items. Furthermore, all territories in the area are completely out of touch, hence the influence is really small. Even if you are a wanted fugitive, nobody here would care. Heinous energy machinists here are also treated equally, so as long as you don’t disobey the law set by the Federation of Energy Machinists, everything from the outside world no longer matters.”

“That’s great then!” Garen sighed in relief. Thinking back what happened this time around, he did not expect Professor Van Doe to give up on him. On the other hand, their opponent the Divine Wind would definitely not allow the Van Doe faction to have another prodigy, hence seized the opportunity. In the end, the slightly weaker Van Doe side had to retreat.

A prodigy who was dead or crippled would just be a dead waste, that was perhaps the main reason why Van Doe gave up at the end.

“Where are you now? If you need help you had better be quick, I’m at the Polar Region already. The protection shield is not closed completely. Have you escaped the territory?” Celine asked quickly.

“How do you know!?” Garen asked in shock.

“The energy machinist’s key in your body has a weak signal over here. Besides me, nobody knows you entered this area or crossed over to the special ability space, so I can roughly sense your presence,” Celine responded instantly. She looked left and right nervously.

“Listen, I can’t do much about most of your things. I tried my best with your Exclusive Mech but still wasn’t able to get it back from Fila. I have already hid some of the leftover Mastery Energy Ores earlier. As for the materials for your biochemical pool, I only managed to hide the Mila Cells. The other rare materials that you’ve been collecting this past two years had been taken by Professor Van Doe’s men. If you still want your Mila Cells, I can immediately send it over before the predators break into air territory.”

“Van Doe took them?” Garen was stunned.

“You don’t believe me?” A look of sarcasm flashed in Celine’s face.

“When you were at your worst, your professor sent men to your place right away and rummaged the whole place just to find information on how you process the Rainbow Stone. Unfortunately, they came up with nothing. He thought he was secretive enough to hide his tracks well but what he didn’t know was that I had people at your place at all times to keep a lookout.”

Garen remained silent.

“Now that we’re under their watch, I don’t have time. Other than your family, the men sent by your professor wanted me to surrender your skills information too. Hehe.” Celine snickered.

“There has been zero news from Fila’s side but as for your professor, he’s been sending men every day to keep a lookout on me. What happened to your family was also his doing, Fila doesn’t even bother meddling with your family.”

Garen pondered for a while and asked.

“What happened to my family?”

“They were detained. Your sister was captured and sent to Van Doe, God knows what he did to her. I rushed over immediately to bring her out but I think she was drugged as she was heavily disoriented, answering every question I asked. As for your parents…their company was shut down and they have disappeared, but don’t worry, I won’t let anything happen to them!!” Celine said firmly in a low voice.

Garen took a deep breath. Even though he had no feelings attachment towards this dimension’s Nonosiva family, but he was still the reason they were facing such disasters.

“Thank you.” He patted Celine’s shoulder firmly.

“What are you planning to do?” Celine asked warily, “Please don’t do anything impulsive! You can’t win them!”

“Don’t worry, I might not be able to make it as a Pilot but I still am an energy machinist.” He had a cold glare in his eyes.

The Seventh Divine Wind General, Van Doe, Fila. Truth be said, he did not blame the Divine Wind General or Fila. As the enemy, using tactics to fight back was normal.

But what was saddening was that as his own professor, Van Doe did not give him the education and knowledge he needed. Everything he knew about the Black Wind was already something given that people of the Black Flood Party knew already. In the end, he became the sacrifice of a battle between two factions, he became the interest of a trade. The one who gained the most in the end, was still Professor Van Doe himself.

Chapter 933: Siege 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In reality, all Van doe did was utilized a little energy to activate the Inherited Level to protect him. Even if his prodigy disciple was killed by hostile enemies, the Black Flood Party would compensate and maintained the balance needed but he was certain that this was not what he will only be getting. Compared to parts of the harvest, Van Doe had already gotten more than enough but he was still greedy and continued to do evil.

“I will return sooner or later…don’t worry,” Garen muttered. As the top Martial Arts Master, there was no way he would give up this easily because of one obstacle.

“When do you want the Mila Cells? Just set a venue and I will arrange aircrafts to send it over,” Celine said softly.

Garen understood how sticky the situation was. The other materials needed for the Biochemical Pool could be found easily in the radiation belt, except for Mila Cells which were considered a scarce mineral and not easy to be found.

“I’m outside the radiation belt, but am not sure exactly where. I actually just woke up from my coma.”

“I can send the cells to your area using aerial drones. I will give you a cipher to receive the signals. Once the drones reach your area, you can use it to open it and retrieve the stuffs. If you don’t use the cipher, it will self-destruct.” Celine took out a small, black metal that resembled a matchbox.

“This is an automatic signal transmitter that will help the drone to locate your Energy Machinist Key’s signal. Once you’ve retrieve the cells, destroy the transmitter immediately. You must remember this! Be careful!”

“Yes, I understand!”

Garen know that Celine is most probably the only support he still had within the Blackboard territory. They share a relationship which seemed like master and apprentice, but also good friends at the same time. The pressure that they both faced now was something unimaginable to the ordinary.

He patted Celine’s shoulder. “You have to be careful too!”

“Don’t worry, I’ll be fine!” Celine smiled, but it seemed somewhat strained. “Alright, I should leave now before they discover my tracks and send out Energy Machinists after me. Remember, the cipher code is…take care.”

“Okay.”

Garen’s heart emptied a little as Celine gradually fade out of view. He felt as if he was the only one left in the world.

He suddenly thought of Clint, Baylon and the mysterious Red Moon. Perhaps they have already officially embarked on a path of their own.

Looking around, the Energy Machinists around him were communicating wordlessly with the people, but something seemed different from the last time.

Moreover, the appearances of these Energy Machinists did not seemed as clean and neat as the people in the territories, but more like the radioactive people in the radiation belt.

“Is it possible that radioactive people are able to become Energy Machinists?” Garen had this dubious thought in mind.

He walked into a random shop to look around.

Inside, rows of counters showed that they were no different from an ordinary store. Several customers were wandering inside leisurely, some of them were bargaining with the pretty sales lady.

Nobody noticed Garen when he walked in.

He glanced casually at the items behind the glass counter.

Navy blue roots, crimson red stones, and a writhing, black, half-grass-half-insect. There were also broken pieces of metal nameplates, and things that looked like fossils of living creatures’ fingerprints.

Even the names on it were strange.

Tears of the Sun, Wind Gauntlets, Freezing Stone, Beautiful Roots, Crab Legs.

“Excuse me, is there anything you need?” Someone came over and ask.

Garen looked up and saw a young, beautiful sales girl.

“This is my first time entering the special ability space, may I know what’s the currency used here?”

“We use Spar Stones, a type of energy stone. To be exact, it’s Energy Crystals. Spar Stone is actually a universal currency, and one of it can be exchanged for 100,000 Mother Planet Universal Units,” The friendly sales clerk replied.

“You’re an Energy Machinist too?” Garen was slightly curious. According to Celine, one can directly bring out the physical objects here, which made him even more curious about this special ability space. However if one can actually do that, the cost of it would definitely be high. Otherwise, Celine would not have risked the danger and sent the drones over, but came over herself to trade directly.

“Sorry, our sales clerks are not Energy Machinists. We are just ordinary people hired by the Federation of Energy Machinists,” The sales clerk answered patiently, and shook her head with a smile.

“How do I earn Spar Stones then?” Garen asked.

“Spar Stones can be earned through the sales of patented techniques, completion of delegated tasks, jobs at stores and much more other ways. If you possess of good materials, those can also be sold to gain interest, but it’d better be the top materials because it is slightly difficult to bring physical objects into the special ability space. It comes with a high price, one kilogram of physical object will cost at least 200, 000 Crystals.” The sales clerk explained in a hushed tone.

“200,000 Crystals for just one kilogram…” Garen finally understood why Celine would choose such a risky method to transport the Milar Cells. “Can I trade in my Universal Units for Spar Stones?”

“Sorry, Spar Stones can be exchanged for Universal Units but it is impossible for the other way around.” The sales clerk smiled, “Do you need anything else?”

She could already tell that the young man in front of her was a rookie without an instructor.

Every year, the ability market would encounter many such rookies. Unlike the other sales clerk, she did not discriminate against the rookies. After all, they were not even comparable to Energy Machinists and had no way to achieve that level. What qualifications do they have to discriminate others? So even if the other person had no intentions of purchasing, she would still be happy to answer all sort of questions to clear their confusion.

“Sea Sand, what are you doing there? We have customers waiting for you at the reception!” A girl’s cry came from the inside of the shop.

The sales lady in front of Garen immediately responded.

“Coming.”

“If you still need anything, please wait for a bit and I will be right back to answer your questions.

Please excuse me,” Sea Sand smiled at Garen apologetically.

“It’s alright, you go get busy.” Garen knew he was now penniless, to be actually served by someone even just for a bit was not bad already.

“Sea Sand!” The voice urged again.

Sea Sand gave a small bow towards Garen before quickly dashing back into the store.

Her friendly service left a good impression with Garen.

He turned around in the store, once again approaching the counter by the door and discovered Mila Cells there.

‘Mila Cells: The fundamental cell needed in building an Energy Machinist’s Biochemical Pool. Highly corrosive, radiation resistant, Level Five hardness, with automatic repairing function. Priced at 4,999 Crystals.’

The small pellets of Mila Cells seemed like a blob of grey brain mass, still slightly squirming. It looked disgusting.

However, Garen knew that if it is provided with sufficient nutrients and organic matter, a pool-sized mold of a Biochemical Pool would be able to form within just a matter of one hour’s time.

“5,000 Crystals…in order to bring out the special ability space, I’d need another 200,000 Crystals…this is definitely something not an ordinary person can afford,” Garen shook his head while he exited the shop.

He turned around to look at the shop’s name: Come Again.

“This name is actually easy to remember.”

He strolled around the square when he realized that an Energy Machinist stood in front of the dolphin water fountain in the middle of the plaza, and pressed his palm on it. He could not tell what the person was doing.

He waited for the Energy Machinist to release his hand, opened his eyes and left before he followed suit. He held his hand out similarly and place his palm on the dolphin.

An icy smooth rush spread within him, and a melodious, electronic female sound rang in his head.

“Welcome to the teleport system, please select your destination.”

A sheet of translucent panel instantly bounced in front of Garen, on the surface of the panel were each delivery points.

Above the surface was simply just a model of the Mother Planet, points of lights shone like the stars indicating the choices of destination.

Garen’s sight fell on one of the points and the edge of the corresponding light immediately emerged into sight with price, the name of location and specialty.

The planet was turning slowly, there were three large spots which were most attractive, looking as if the moon was surrounded by various shining, bright stars.

The first one was Polar City, located in the vast ocean.

The second one was Blue Sky, it seemed that the town itself was always moving.

The third one was Nagadako Town, which was the brightest spot among the three. At the side of the display, it was introduced as the Alliance City Center of the Mother Planet.

Garen casually looked around, the cheapest teleport point cost at least five to 600 Crystals, if he were to teleport to any of the three huge towns far away, it would cost up to 10,000!

“Everything needs money…” Garen left the dolphin and recited exit thrice in his head. All at once, he felt his surroundings glow in colors of the rainbow and he was back to the tunnel which he came from in the first place.

When the dizziness faded, he opened both eyes.

He was back within the missile compartment of the thigh unit.

Slightly moving his body, he slowly withdrew his natural Cold Radiation and started controlling the frost which was slowly spreading, accelerating the melting process.

A thick layer of ice had already formed within the internal part of the thigh unit, gradually melting rapidly as the time increased.

As time passed, Garen finally saw the opening of the frozen part melt away.

He reached out his hand to push and all of a sudden, he was sprung out of the unit as silent as a raccoon.

He was unsure about the situation outside so he got into an alert posture in the first place.

However, just seconds after exiting the thigh unit, Garen sensed something was wrong.

In the large bed beside him, a naked, slim girl was asleep comfortably. The bedroom seemed to belong to the girl, the door and windows were tightly locked.

When he sprung out, he coincidentally landed at the side of the girl’s bed.

The girl’s skin was fair, and seemed to glow like ivory under the moonlight. She slept like a starfish, and she did not even use a blanket. She seemed like she was muttering something while sound asleep, her long slender legs twitching occasionally, even her toes would move from time to time.

“Where is this?” Garen moved his sight away from the girl and glanced around. Walking towards the curtains, he gently lifted the curtain and looked out to see the unique architectural wasteland style that only belonged to no other than the radiation belt.

Grey, dilapidated, but strong and ferocious at the same time, just like a beast drifting off to slumber.

Just as he released the curtain, he sensed a breeze from his back. Lightly tapping with the back of his hand, Garen dodged to his side and avoided the blow from the back.

At the same time, his finger tapped on the abdomen of the person behind him.

Crack!

Chapter 934: Siege 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The attacker bended her waist slightly, held back the pain, and swung a powerful kick at Garen’s head.

Bang!

Raising his arm to to grab the attacking leg, Garen realized that the attacker was the girl who was supposedly sound asleep just now.

One of her legs was now locked on Garen’s neck. With only one leg standing, she could not use much energy to attack, what more to hide her private area which was now pulled open and clearly seen by Garen. She was not even trying to cover it. She suddenly produced a black dagger in hand and stabbed it at Garen’s waist ferociously.

“Let go!”

Garen grabbed her wrist accurately, and with a twist, took down her dagger.

“Who are you?!” The girl glared at Garen coldly. She tried hard to wriggle her legs to close them but could not exert energy to do so.

“Were you the one who rescued me?” Garen motioned towards the thigh unit with his chin.

“You were the one inside?” The girl seemed surprised, then noticed that the both of them were in an inappropriate position and that his eyes were directed at her private parts.

“Are you having a good look?” Her face turned cold once again.

“That is none of my business,” Garen let go of her and took a step towards the side. There was a glimpse of smile in his eyes.

With a cold face, she put on her pajamas.

“Why were you hiding inside?”

“Take a guess.” Garen found a chair to sit down. “This is the radiation belt, right?”

“You’re from the territory?” The girl understood him. If he was a radioactive person, he would not have asked within or outside the domain because radioactive people were not allowed into the domain.

“I’m Garen,” Garen leaned back in the chair and introduced himself. “Your place seems troubled.”

“I’m East Perrin, and this is Leo Town, a small town in the radiation belt near Blackboard Region for radioactive people. If you are from the domain, you should’ve heard about the predators’ wave then?” East Perrin explained swiftly.

“I don’t care who you are, where you are from, and what your background is. Our biggest trouble now is that the predators will be attacking soon. If we don’t have a solution to that, we will all die here! So do you have any ideas or strategies? If you don’t, I believe you should help contribute and see how to help us defeat the predator wave.”

Garen may have showed up in an odd way, but she had no time to find out who he was – not during a dangerous period like this, anybody who popped out will surely be food to the predators and won’t be able to escape. An extra pair of hands means one more share of strength.

“Well, you sure are straightforward. Predator wave, huh?” Garen came across it from the academy Inner Courtyard’s library. If it was not for his elite rank in the Inner Courtyard, he would not even had a chance to read about the predator wave.

Predators were extreme mutated humans. They looked like normal human beings on the outside, but they in fact had already detached from the general human species and became a completely different species of their own.

The predators were extremely atrocious. Long-range attack meant nothing to them as they have hard and tough skins which greatly deflect the force of ray guns and other long-ranged firearms. Only short-ranged attacks and explosives would inflict the biggest harm on them.

These were private and confidential information stored in the library, not to be leaked to others.

“Aren’t you worried that I’m a bad person?” Garen regarded the girl standing in front of him with respect. She was charmingly bold.

“I don’t care if you’re a bad person or one of the good guys, as long as you’re human, you’re going to die when the predators come attacking.” East Perrin started to suit up and put on her full armor.

“If we go according to rules, I should have you locked up and keep you under surveillance for a period of time. However, we do not have sufficient manpower now. So if you don’t want to die, you better come with us and help to defend.”

Garen laughed.

“Do you think I’m joking?” East Perrien glared at him coldly. “Follow me.”

She quickly unlocked the door and walked out.

Garen followed her out of the bedroom. It was an an ordinary second-floor corridor with iron railings. Down the stairs on the left, ten or so men were squatting in the open space. They looked tired and drained. An elderly with a white-gray beard came over and looked at Garen.

“Perrin, who is he?”

“An unlucky bastard who was seeking refuge in the Mech’s missile compartment,” East Perrin replied casually. “What’s the situation now?”

“Most of the predators have moved to Vulture Town. I tried using my wireless signal to contact the people there but there was no response, most probably…” Malone muttered.

“Damn it!”

East Perrin frowned.

“If we go on like this, we will die from being siege alive!”

Listening to their conversation, Garen observed that the men around did not look happy when they saw him walking out from East Perrin’s room..

He did not mind, though. His powers have yet to be regenerated. If East Perrin were to attack him with Willpower force, he would be dead meat; but it was pretty obvious that this girl did not know any Willpower techniques.

After all, these techniques were exceptionally rare to achieve within the domain.

Without any Willpower force techniques and based on his current physique, if he was up against these people who just throw punches and kicks, it would simply be a unilateral massacre.

“You guys do now that the predators are less active at night?” Garen could not bear the pointless discussion going on beside him and decided to butt in.

“At night?” East Perrin was stunned for a moment. “How do you know?”

“Me? I was a former top student after all.” Garen smiled. “Let’s go, we’ll have a look at the situation from above the wall first.”

East Perrin glanced at Malone, and he nodded giving his consent.

“Alright.”

East Perrin and Garen casually greeted the others who were resting before she led him to the interior wall’s ladder to climb up the ten-meter high black iron enclosure.

Garen assumed that the predator wave just started and would not be much of a problem. They could leverage nighttime to rest and defend again during the daytime.

However when they reached the top and he had a good look at the surroundings through the infrared binoculars, he was instantly speechless.

“How can there be so many of them!!?” His face fell all of a sudden.

Standing beside him, Malone and East Perrin were devastated once again. They thought that as someone from the domain, Garen would be knowledgeable and would be able to come up with some sort of strategy. They both had their hopes high, but it seemed like their only glimmer of hope has also vanished.

Garen was astonished. The predators’ shadows could be seen everywhere. Huddling close and tight together, there could be more than hundreds of them. They do not even know if there were any Level Two or even higher level predators among the crowd.

He was only left with Level One Willpower, and his Energy Machinist Willpower was not fit for battle. He had only his martial arts skills but that will not help much. The defense set up by the predators was not something he could easily defeat as well; the most he could was to kill ten of them but the others would just swarm up and he would be screwed for sure.

“This is troublesome…” Setting down the binoculars, Garen looked grim.

“You’re from the domain, do you have any ideas? If it’s troublesome, that means there’s still hope!” East Perrin’s eyes flashed as she asked quickly.

“I do have an idea, but it all depends on when will the predators attacking and how long are your people able to delay the attack,” Garen replied lightly.

If only he was alone, it would be much easier. He could just simply pop a Distortion Seed in and he would stand a chance to escape already. However, one of the biggest disadvantages of consuming the Distortion Seed was that it is uncontrollable. Besides the host’s body, the parasites would madly attack any other living creatures around until the host finishes all potential and the genes crash.

In other words, once he relies on the Distortion Seed, he might kill everyone around him, including East Perrin who saved his life. That was something he did not wish to happen.

Furthermore, if there were higher ranked predators with extraordinary speed and power around, using the Distortion Seed will not help much as well.

“Then tell us, what should we do!?” East Perrin asked immediately.

“Just drag the time, all I need is time!” Garen recalled some strategies from an Energy Machinist recording. If there was a Biochemical Pool, he could actually process his own cannon fodder. In addition to the Distortion Seed, he can produce longer lasting cannon fodders that would not easily crumble so fast. With that, he would be able to increase their defense system immensely. The dead bodies of the predators could also be used to process new materials for the cannon fodder too.

“How long, exactly?” East Perrin asked in a hushed tone.

“I don’t know, but I’m waiting as well. At least we still have a glimmer of hope, right?” Looking at the distance, Garen replied softly.

Malone and East Perrin were silent.

He was right, this was better than no hope at all.

“I’ll go calm everyone down,” She turned and went down the ladder.

With the predator siege for the past few days, the people were frightened. They did not know how long would the predators stay, but their food supplies could only last for just a week. If they were still under siege after a week, nothing mattered anymore because they were going to starve to death.

Malone remained above the wall, staring at Garen.

“Young man, we are now in the same boat, none of us can escape. Even if we are able to hold our defense, what about our food?”

“What do your people eat before this?” Garen asked.

“Mutated fish from the radiation lake.”

“The predators can be eaten also…” Garen said lightly.

Malone shuddered. He felt a chill rising up behind his back. This was something said by one who have never eaten it before.

Staring at Garen’s back, his guts told him that the future of Leo Town will change because of this young man.

Malone turned around and left.

Garen continued to stay up and looked around when all of a sudden, sounds of panic could be heard from below.

“Caster! Caster has escaped!”

Somebody was yelling. It sounded like chaos below.

One of the gates opened and a motorcycle rushed out in full speed. Its engine was roaring and ejecting blue flames similar to those by a Mech.

“Damn it! He took the only power furnace we have!”

“That was the only power furnace in the processing workshop!! If we don’t have weapons we’re screwed! Damn you, Caster!!!”

“Half of the drinks are gone! Even the food!” One by one, the voices were getting louder.

Garen looked at the motorcycle charging ahead as fast as lightning towards the North where the number of predators were the least.

“An escapee? If there’s a first there’s going to be a second…” Garen murmured.

Below, East Perrin and Malone were both staring grimly at the motorcycle rushing across the distance through the embrasure.

As one of the three leaders of the town, Caster had the nerve to run away himself. Not only did he dare to bring along almost half of the town’s food supplies, he even took the only power furnace in town that was used to produce firepower.

“Without the power furnace, we won’t even have our production line anymore!” Malone said solemnly.

East Perrin bit her lips but remained silent, her nails digging into her palms hard. The small glimmer of hope they originally had moments ago just became a little smaller…

Chapter 937: Plight 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I didn’t have a teacher. It was all self-taught and it took me six years,” Garen used the previous story again.

“Self-taught?! Is that possible?!” Lan was so shocked that her eyes widened. “I have tried many times and I couldn’t do it! I haven’t even passed Level One now…” She was saddened. “It’s been seven years… Grandpa taught me since I was young.”

“Er…” Garen didn’t know what to say.

They walked slowly along the counter.

“Brother Garen, you can pick whatever you like. Our business has been getting worse and worse after Grandpa fell ill. After selling off the previous stocks, senior brother and sister had to do some not-so-good quality imprints themselves and sell them to support the shop.”

She whispered. There was no one in the store anymore. The last customer who was only having a look around had also left. The soft lights that were dim reflected the silent surrounding. Only Lan’s voice echoed a little.

Garen nodded silently and listened to Lan’s introduction while scanning the few kinds of Energy Machine Imprint on the counter.

“All the imprints uses basic Level One imprint as the main body. The seniors are all Level Three Energy Machinists. They have insufficient computing power to process Level Two Energy Machine Imprint. The Energy Machine Imprint is divided into two parts, computation and production. The computation part is the main body, which had to be purchased from the Federation. It is the part that is responsible for the calculation and increasing the Energy Machinist’s computing power. The production part is what you just saw. It is responsible for controlling and guiding the production of cannon fodder in the Biochemical Pool. The processing part that we are in charge of is the second block,” Lan introduced, slowly moving forward.

“In other words, we purchase semi-finished products and then process them into finished products before selling them, right?” Garen asked.

“That is the case. However, all the main bodies of Level One imprints are similar and the computing power is increased by a factor of three. The key lies in the second block of the processing of the Production Mod. If an ordinary imprint main body met a powerhouse who could process it into a decent Production Mod, for instance, the powerful cannon fodder such as the demon worm, then there will be a leap in price,” Lan said with some envy.

“That’s how it is…” Garen nodded to express understanding. Although he did not want to decide on his first imprint this rashly, there was no other way. The situation now was critical and time did not allow him to carefully make a choice.

His sight swept across the counter and landed directly on the Wild Wolf.

“That one then. Wild Wolf Imprint.”

He pointed to the Energy Machine Imprint on the counter and said.

“Are you sure you want that?” Lan asked.

“Yup, I’ll have that.” Garen nodded.

“The Wild Wolf is fast in speed, has sharp claws and is capable of night vision, but its defense is not good. This imprint is a proud work done by senior brother. I will give you the best one. The wastage rate is only five percent. It is one of senior brother’s proudest work,” Lan deftly retrieved a gray shimmering soft object from a small cabinet under the counter.

All the Energy Machine Imprints were like different colors of cotton candy, soft and without shape.

“Are all Energy Machine Imprints like this?” Garen asked curiously.

“Of course not. This is only a Level One Energy Machine Imprint and it generally can be used by Level One Energy Machinist. There are also Energy Machine Imprints used by Level Two Energy Machinists, or Level Three, Four, Five. When you have money later on, you can equip yourself with a Level Two Energy Machine Imprint once you reach Level Three. Remember, it is very hard to change this stuff once it is fixed. Like primitive cells, once you have already developed them into a piece of beef, if you want to change it into a bovine bone later on, it will be very difficult,” Lan exclaimed.

“I understand,” Garen nodded.

“Looks like you really don’t know anything,” Lan shook her finger and said, “well, this is for you,” she handed the imprint and put it into Garen’s raised hand.

“Eat it. When you go back and retrofit, it will be painful. Just endure it and it will be fine. It generally lasts for an hour. Remember to pay attention to safety. This is the time when an Energy Machinist is most vulnerable. Regardless of how powerful an Energy Machinist is, it’s all the same.”

“Got it.”

Garen nodded solemnly.

After an indistinct twist of color, Garen suddenly returned to his room.

He raised his hand and saw that he was holding a clump of shimmering gray cotton.

“This is the Wild Wolf Imprint?” He did not hesitate and stuffed it into his mouth.

What was strange was that when that thing touched the mouth, it immediately whooshed inside, as if it was a living thing. It slipped down the throat like liquid and it was cold, like gulping a bowl of ice water.

Garen barely swallowed and felt a tumble in his stomach.

The Willpower behind his head slowly vibrated, as if there was something cold that was radiating out a lot of silk tentacles, slowly wrapping around the two imprints at the back of his brain.

With a whirring sound, a sudden huge shock rushed into his brain and Garen felt a cramp in his stomach, like the churning of rivers and seas. He felt like vomiting. Feeling nausea, he began to burp and continuously spurt out unpleasant gas.

White spots appeared before his eyes as if someone was using their fingers to firmly press on his eyes. He saw many white spots dispersing non-stop.

He leaned forward and suppressed the pain as he walked to the room’s single-seated sofa and sat down, taking a deep breath.

Although this kind of nausea and pain was unbearable, it was nothing to Garen. The pain of reworking his heart was much stronger than this. After a slight adjustment, he was able to stay calm and move about freely. However, the faint beads of sweat on his forehead showed that he was not in a good condition at this time.

After adapting to this severe pain, Garen headed to the side of the window. The sky had already lit up and it seemed to be early in the morning.

Weird sound like the howling of wolves could be faintly heard outside in a distance, but this surrounding terrain could not possibly have wolves. Even if there were, they would have been annihilated by the radiation people. The only possibility was the Predators.

“It’s about to begin…” Garen murmured. Looking at the horizon where the sky was in the distance, he hoped everything would be well.

Even though he was in the room, he could feel the tremendous pressure from the people walking around on the outside.

Anxious, uneasy and forcing themselves to calm down, that kind of repression.

This was the entire mien of the thirty or forty people in the whole of Leo City.

Through the window, Garen saw someone holding a sharp metal spear and was swinging it around non-stop. There were some who were constantly rubbing their hands, sitting on the steps of the doorway and mumbling about something with their heads down.

The howling sounds came from outside, but no one lifted their heads to take a look. The whole city was increasingly quiet. No one spoke. Occasionally, one could hear the cries of babies. However, even the children who were a few years old were seriously doing what they could to help, whereas, the adults were constantly adjusting their physical status so that they could remain at their peak at all times.

Letting down the curtains, Garen knew he could do nothing now. The Wild Wolf Imprint seemed to be transforming the two Willpower imprints at the back of his head. This transformation was very rapid and precise. Many times, it would also extract some subtle substances from his own body to include in the transformation. This was also the key reason as to why the human body felt severe pain.

Garen looked up at the time, 6:21.

The wall clock ticked, its sound crisp and rhythmical.

He sat down, slowly relaxed his body and carefully observed the transformation of this Willpower Imprint. But unfortunately, such transformation was too rapid and the degree of sophistication far exceeded his imagination. Just watching for a few minutes, his conscious was a little blurred and his energy was over-exhausted. He could only stop.

Sitting quietly on the sofa, the sofa cushion under his buttocks was soft and firm. It was a leather surface and there seemed to be metal springs inside of it. It was bouncy when one sat down on it.

Minutes and seconds ticked by.

The sky was getting brighter outside.

Someone started to call on the men guarding the wall to prepare for a change of shift. Three rounds of shifts, this was previously arranged by Garen.

The footsteps of the guards who passed through the room were sparse. The people who came down were breathing deeply. No one spoke. There were only heavy breaths.

Garen looked up and glanced at the time, 6:44.

It had been twenty-three minutes.

The pain in his body continued and the intensity was increasing. He endured it, quietly sitting on the sofa and waited for everything to past.

6:51.

There were subtle noises coming from the outside and there was the sound of gunfire. Hurried footsteps swept past the room and it seemed that someone was running to the wall.

“It’s alright. Just a few Predators who had been singled out rushed over and was gotten rid of,” said a voice. Then everything went quiet again.

6:59.

There was a knock on the door and then came the voice of East Perrin from the outside.

“Are you there? It’s going to be daylight soon.”

“Don’t worry. There’s no need to rush,” Garen sat on the couch with his eyes closed. His sweat ran down his forehead towards the edge of his cheeks and dripped on his clothes. The clothes he wore were still the plain clothes from the inner region. There was blood, engine oil and black soot on it. The outfit looked like a painter’s work suit. Besides the long sleeves and long pants, it was hard to spot any pattern or color. There were smudges all over.

Hearing Garen’s answer, East Perrin was silent and went away again.

7:12.

Gunshots were heard outside once more. This time, it was no ordinary gunfire, but a clutter of noises.

In the midst of the mess, there was the voice of people cursing and occasionally, someone screaming.

“It had really begun…” Garen opened his eyes, but he could do nothing except for moving about freely.

Boom boom boom!!

East Perrin knocked at the door again.

“A group of Predators came from the outside but have been repulsed by us. I suspect they are just testing our forces. A few brothers have died.”

“Help me prepare some basic materials,” Garen raised his voice. “The root of Loquat leaves and Dragon-beard Grass. The higher the radiation, the better they are; more than 20 grams each. The blood and brain of radiation beasts, higher grade would be even better. If not, general ones would do as well. The more, the better. Also, Tomb-branches and Winter Flowers…”

He casually named a series of things, all which were common materials in the radiation belt. These things more or less had radiation. Many of them were used as substitutes for the Nutritional Liquid to create the Biochemical Pool. Garen had no other way. Although these alternatives might be less effective and might affect the strength of the final bred-creatures, there was no other way. Just create some first and see how it goes later on.

Chapter 938: Plight 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

With enough Nutritional Liquid, this was the basis of everything.

“I remember them,” outside of the door, East Perrin repeated what Garen had asked for. Her memory was not bad and she could remember everything just by hearing once. Soon, she left and seemed to be going somewhere to find the materials.

However, as noises arose from the outside, Garen knew that he was wrong. Voices of exclamations were faintly heard.

“Chief has gone out!!”

“Why is she when it’s so dangerous!?”

“Get back! Big sister!”

People shouted again and again but no response was heard from East Perrin.

Within ten minutes, she had returned.

“Thank God!”

“Chief, you can never run a risk again! You are our only hope!”

“Chief…!””Chief…”

Flustered voices followed, with the voice of East Perrin constantly apologizing.

Garen looked up, and suddenly, all the pain in his body disappeared without a trace as if it had never emerged before.

Time, 7:22.

“Finally it has ended…” Garen let out a sigh of relief and wiped his sweat with both hands. He felt that there was a difference in the two imprints behind him.

He found a mirror and looked at himself. Under the control of his Willpower, a greatly altered Willpower imprint gradually appeared.

The original two imprints had now become a larger single unit. The original diamond shape had also turned into the form of a tiny wild wolf with a black body and green eyes. It didn’t look too bad, even a bit ferocious.

“This is Energy Machine Imprint?” Garen tried again to calculate the stereoscopic computational model for the advancing of Level Three Energy Machinist. Sure enough, it was no ordinary task. It was almost incomparable to the previous straining effort.

“If there was enough time, I need five days to break through to Energy Machinist Level Three!” He made a simple calculation of the progress in his mind.

“Sure enough, having three times more the computing power is different.”

“The materials have been found!” The voice of East Perrin came from outside of the door, calm and exhausted.

Garen stood up and walked over to open the door. He looked at East Perrin, her hair scattered over her forehead. This agile and brave woman still had a straight face on. There was a thin trace of blood on her cheek. Clearly, the trip was not entirely smooth.

The tight gray dress she wore was snagged and had several holes. Blood marks were vaguely visible on the skin.

“Take me there,” Garen exclaimed.

*****************

On the edge of the processing workshop at the rear of Leo City, a square pit was dug out in an open space. It was piled with a variety of messy materials, including roots, flowers, bloody flesh and bones.

Garen and East Perrin stood alone in front of the pit.

“What do you want to do?” East Perrin asked Garen. “Everything has been found for you.”

“There is still a lacking of one last thing,” Garen said plainly.

“Still lacking!?” East Perrin’s eyes widened. “Few of my brothers are dead because of these things, I myself almost died outside. Now you tell me that there is still something lacking?!”

“What’s lacking cannot be found by you,” Garen said plainly. “We’re all in the same boat together now. If you die and I’ll also die. What’s there to be desperate about?”

East Perrin wiped her face.

“Alright, I’ll calm down. Now there are a few waves of small-scale attacks out there. The number is about a dozen. But when I went out and looked through the telescope, Vulture City has basically been digested. The Predators inside seems to have begun to shift out and head over here. We don’t have much time.”

“How much longer? An estimation?” Garen asked.

“No more than three days. Although the number of Predators has increased, their speed has also reduced. It takes five days to walk over here from Vulture City. Since the speed of the Predators are fast, it should take them about three days to journey here. The discrepancy would not be huge,” East Perrin answered in a low voice.

“Just wait for it. There will be hope,” Garen jumped down and began to pick up a piece of material by hand. Traces of Cold Radiation flashed in his hand from time to time, freezing the better part of the material to prevent it from deteriorating.

East Perrin did not know what to do and could only watch from the edge.

“Prepare a room for me, a bigger one,” Garen ordered.

“Alright.”

Minutes and seconds ticked by and it was time for breakfast. Radiation people were accustomed to eating two meals a day, one about nine in the morning and another at six in the evening. However now, when the few women who were in-charged of meals served some food to eat, not many people had the appetite. There were children silently helping to refill the food and water.

Garen directly consumed the highly irradiated Nutritional Liquid. With a grab, blue threads emerged from his palm and directly absorbed the Nutritional Liquid, leaving only useless impurities behind.

Time passed quickly and noon soon arrived. Garen looked up to the sky from time to time as he was waiting for the drone sent out by Celine. If his luck was alright, perhaps with the distance from Polar Region to here, it would reach today.

East Perrin had already gone to defense. Now the atmosphere in the town was somewhat in despair. Without her taking command in the city, it was very likely that something catastrophic would happen.

Garen stayed here alone and quietly worked on the material in his hands.

Two large basins were placed beside each other and the parts he had dealt with were placed in them.

The Predators were gradually approaching. There were definitely Level Two Predators in the vast army. When Garen saw the end of Caster who had tried to escape, he knew that he had hit jackpot. A one in a million Level Two Predator was actually present here.

According to the data records, Level Two Predators could produce a Willpower Field-liked Mind Force, which could produce a substantial effect. This was the scene that everyone saw at that time. Caster was crushed by an invisible force and died without leaving a complete corpse behind.

“Now that there is Energy Machine Imprint and most of the materials are available, the only thing that is lacking is the Biochemical Pool…” Garen lifted up his head and looked at the gray-blue sky.

This was the fifteenth time he had looked to the sky today.

This time, the margin of the endless sky finally did not disappoint him. A blue dot was flying at high speed toward this side. Its outline looked like a drone.

Garen’s face finally showed a smile. If it came any later, he probably would have to consider expanding one Soul Seed to reincarnate…

He quickly jumped out of the pit and ran to look for East Perrin to have her tell everyone not to shoot down the drone in the sky.

At this moment, as soon he ran out from the rear of the city, he realized that something was amiss.

There was no one in the houses of the city. Everyone seemed to be concentrated at the front and vague screams could be heard from that side.

From far, East Perrin saw Garen ran out.

“Be careful! There are Predators that have sneaked in! They are invisible!” She yelled.

Invisible Predators!!

Garen was surprised. This was a rare species among the Predators! How could there be any here?

He suddenly felt a deep chill coming behind him.

He spun around, gave a sidekick, and released cold air!

Three fluent and continuous moves emerged instantly.

Garen felt as is he had kicked something hard. With a loud boom, a large amount of cold air quickly covered the entire body of that object which he had kicked. The hoarfrost completely revealed its form.

This humanoid creature was kicked right in the head. It stumbled out a few steps, drowsily fell to the ground, and was swamped by the subsequent white air, directly freezing into a large piece of ice.

Garen looked at his trousers. There was blood on it. With his physical fitness, he was actually at a disadvantage in the direct confrontation just now. Moreover, he felt some pain in his bones where there were probably some fractures.

“This is the Invisible Predator?”

He took a close look at this thing. It had the same shape of a human but without hands. There were two stout, octopus-like tentacles at that place of its arms.

East Perrin also brought some people as she rushed over here. When she saw the ice on the ground, she sucked in a breath of cold air.

“This is the guy who had killed eight of my brothers and sisters!” She raised her hand and shot the ice to pieces.

Krak!

The whole piece of ice shattered into glass-like pieces.

Garen glanced behind East Perrin. There were only more than a dozen people left. It seemed that these were the remaining manpower of the entire city. There were also a few children and women who were covered in blood.

“What about the rest?”

“All dead…” East Perrin replied in a low voice. There was also blood on her face and it was unclear whether it was hers or someone else’s.

“We have no idea when the Invisible Predator sneaked in. When we realized it, it had already killed half of the logistics personnel. It also killed a few men who had gone over to help,” the old man Malone said palely.

At this time, the drone flew down from the sky and descended towards Garen.

Someone raised their gun and aimed it at the drone out of conditioned reflex.

“Don’t shoot!” Garen quickly shouted.

This made everyone loosen up a little. They watched Garen reach out his hands to grab the small drone and took down a small fist-sized black box from it.

“Take care,” he whispered the cipher to the black box.

Pap. The box opened automatically. The cover rose slowly, revealing a round thing wrapped in white silk.

Garen took out this thing and left the rest of it with East Perrin.

“This stuff can be used as an investigating drone.”

“What is that?!” East Perrin looked at the ball in his hand.

“This is hope!”

Garen answered without looking back and hurriedly ran towards the rear of the city.

Following the path between the houses in the city, he went straight back to the side of the pit. Garen lifted the material basin that he managed and walked into a large, empty stone house on the right.

This stone house just so happened to have a basement. It was the residence left by a man who had died in battle. He had no wife and children, so this place was assigned to Garen as a laboratory house.

Uncovering the fist-size thing in his hand, it was a black stone.

Garen gripped the stone with both of his hands and applied force to both sides of it.

Krak!

The stone was divided into two in a crisp sound and a piece of pale yellow soft meat fell out. It was caught by Garen.

“This is it! Mila Cells, Stoneheart Flesh… The main part of the Biochemical Pool!!” Garen knew that in the present plight, there finally was hope…

Chapter 939: Hope 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Stoneheart Flesh in his hand was like a soft and warm cotton.

Garen held it and smelled a faint scent that seemed to be coming from his arm, not from the air but really from his arm.

This feeling was very strange. As if the palm of his hand had become a nose, he even felt as though there was something soft lightly touching the tip of his nose.

He walked to the center of the basement and set aside the Stoneheart Flesh. He then picked up the shovel in the basement and began to dig into the ground.

This was the interior of the stone house, so the excavated ground was also part of the entire stone.

Garen dug a small pit and stopped. He then picked up the Stoneheart Flesh beside him and put it in as if sowing a seed. After placing the Stoneheart Flesh, he took out a black spray that had a few small black fruits on it and gently crushed the small fruits.

A few drops of black juice slowly dribbled down his fingers and onto the surface of the Stoneheart Flesh.

Hiss…

A clear white steam rose, along with a pungent scent.

Suddenly, the Stoneheart Flesh began to wriggle slowly like a viscous liquid. It began to spread around, covering a large surrounding area.

In less than a few minutes, a large piece of pale yellow fleshy membrane was formed and it covered the ground. It was still moving.

Garen stood by the side and waited quietly.

As time passed, the fleshy membrane on the ground gradually became darker in color, slightly grayish.

Sssrraaak…

A hole gradually cracked in the center of the fleshy membrane and it seemed to be emitting steam.

Garen’s gaze was fixed on the spot where the crack was. In it was darkness and nothing could be seen.

As time went on, the rift increasingly got bigger and wider.

The entire rift gradually formed a round crater with a diameter of about two or three meters and the color of the entire fleshy membrane gradually turned black. It was no longer wriggling but was becoming more rigid and solidified.

Garen once again took out the two half-shell of the Stoneheart Flesh, gently chipped off some powder, and sprinkled it evenly on the four corners of the fleshy membrane that had turned into a black flesh-pool.

The flesh-pool, which was still moving slightly, instantly became still and was even more condensed and solid.

“Done… my Biochemical Pool,” Garen was relieved. Finally, following the records of the Energy Machinist training method, his first Biochemical Pool had succeeded. Although the whole process was very simple, he had been constantly worried. After all, this thing was the key to whether he could survive this crisis.

Quickly taking the well-mixed Nutritional Liquid for the Biochemical Pool, he slowly poured it down the edge of the Biochemical Pool. Several kinds of well-mixed biochemical fluids quickly mixed together. Garen then squatted down and slowly released his Energy Machinist Willpower.

The Energy Machine Imprint at the back of his head suddenly disappeared. They disintegrated into countless transparent silk strands and densely pierced into the edge of the Biochemical Pool. They were like needles, swimming and quivering between the flesh and blood of the Biochemical Pool, forming many vein-like bulging things.

A virtual screen was faintly displayed before Garen’s eyes.

‘Wild Wolf Imprint is ready. Please name your Biochemical Pool.’ This text message appeared on the light screen.

“Just call Wild Wolf No. 1.” Garen took a random name for easy memory.

‘Wild Wolf No.1 has been completed. The biochemical fluid in Biochemical Pool is filled. The analysis level is Level One basic level and can cultivate fifteen Level One creatures. After that, it needs to be refilled.’

The light screen showed the information and data of the Biochemical Pool.

‘Please insert the basic organization.’

Garen stood up but his body’s Energy Machine Imprint remained in the Biochemical Pool. He went out to move the pre-prepared flesh and blood of mutated beast into the black Biochemical Pool.

Splash.

The mutated beast that looked like a wild boar was directly submerged in the biochemical fluid and soon, it melted like a candle.

A series of tiny bubbles constantly emerged from the Biochemical Pool, accompanied by strange gurgling sounds.

‘Basic organization had been acquired complete. Begin to create wild wolf units?’ The light screen informed again.

Garen answered yes with his consciousness.

The light screen suddenly disappeared. This was a virtual screen that was presented in front of an Energy Machinist through the direct connection of Willpower. Others could not see it except for the Energy Machinist themselves. This also ensured the high degree of mystery and safety level of an Energy Machinist.

With the feedback through his Willpower, Garen could control the progress of the Biochemical Pool anytime. It could be stopped and restarted at any time.

In accordance with the standard of an Energy Machinist’s number of control, him being a Level Two Energy Machinist could only control one imprint. In other words, he could control only one cannon fodder. If there was an experimental platform, he could then create an elite unit, which was the elite version of cannon fodder. However, the experimental platform was not something that he could obtain now. It required a lot of materials and high technical requirements. Generally, only very wealthy Energy Machinists would dare to build an experimental platform while still at a low level because they could use space tools to bring it alongside with them.

Simply put, what low-end Energy Machinists did was actually the work of ancient Modulation Engineers. Theirs was a purely biochemical route. This was because the elite version of biochemical machinery was the patent of the experimental platform, the general Energy Machinists would not even think about it if they had not reached a high level.

In addition, this profession itself demanded crazy computing power. The untalented person at most would be a low-level Energy Machinist for his whole life. If one could become a Level Three or Four Energy Machinist, one would be considered not bad. What more those high levels of Level Five, Inheriting Level and above.

Most of the general Energy Machinists in the market reached their limit at Level Three. This was because the entry requirement for Energy Machinists was too high and more time would be needed as the level increased. Therefore, without talent, it would take a lot of time to accumulate practices. This had also caused a lot of Energy Machinists to reach the stage of Level Three and Four only when they were at seventy or eighty years old. Level Four was the limit that most people could achieve.

However, Garen was different. He had potential points that could increase intelligence and computing power. Even with his current computing power talent, he was at the top level, a standard genius amongst the general Energy Machinists. One had to know that the profession of Energy Machinist could only be undertaken by people who were computing genius and of super scholar level, whereas, the geniuses of Energy Machinists would truly be the top prodigies among the average people.

A series of situational information flashed through Garen’s thoughts but his eyes were focused on the changes in the Biochemical Pool. The milk-like colored biochemical fluid that was poured in had now begun to tumble. The body of the mutated beast that had just been thrown in had completely dissolved and now, small algae-like floaters began to appear on the surface of the liquid. With the passage of time, this kind of floating object was also increasing.

In the basement, a faint stench began to develop slowly. It was a bit like the smell of mutton and was also somewhat like the smell of fish.

Garen did not have any changes in his facial expression. He just quietly stared at the biochemical fluid in the Biochemical Pool and waited for the result. At the same time, he also had to carefully calculate how much time it took to cultivate one time. After all, the conditions here were not of standard conditions. The biochemical fluid was made using many substitutes, the cultivating environment was also not maintained with the optimum temperature and humidity radiation instruments and so on. In such an environment, the general data on the record had lost its meaning and so, the calculation time for the actual operation of the unit was required.

*********************

In a distance from Leo City, large groups of Predators slowly gathered towards this side. Their numbers totaled tens of thousands.

The Predators that first appeared were now riding motorcycles at the rear end. It was as if they were monitoring and were constantly making an unintelligible roaring sound.

The speed of the entire Predator group was not fast, but their number was packed and the entire grassland horizon seemed to be completely occupied. The number of over ten thousand simply made them looked vast and enormous.

Vulture City had become history. It had been completely destroyed behind the Predator group. There was no living person, bones and rotting flesh were everywhere. Skulls and limbs that were not gnawed finished were scattered on the ground.

On the walls, ground, and gates were dried blackened blood spots. Two lengths of human intestines were used as ropes to secure the door knockers on the main gate. To make the rope, countless people’s intestines were taken to be twisted into the thickness of a small arm. It looked tough and had turned black.

Caw, caw!!

A flock of scavenger crows flew down. They were flapping their wings and jumping here and there from time to time, competing for carrion.

“Charge!!”

The Level Two Predator leader in the Predator group roared.

“Hiss!!”

All the Predators lifted their heads and yelled as if they were responding to the leader’s call.

From the sky, it could be clearly seen that at this time, more and more Predators were gradually encircling Leo City as the center point from all directions. Not only Leo City, but the remaining towns were also like standalone islands teetering in the vast sea.

*************************

“Managed to contact the people of Doe City?” East Perrin stared at the communication staff who was running over here and asked.

“No… The signal disturbance was too much. We couldn’t hear any sound at all.” The communication staff was trained by Malone. Although his skill was still satisfactory, due to the lack of good equipment, he could only reply the Chief helplessly.

“Could it be that Doe City has boded ill?” East Perrin mumbled.

“Don’t worry that much. We will hold out as long as we can,” Malone whispered from the side. “That Garen still has not come out?”

“Still in the basement. Don’t know what he’s doing,” East Perrin shook her head. “I have placed some people nearby him. As soon as he comes out, we will know.”

“You can’t pin your hopes on him alone,” Malone said in a low voice.

“Do we still have a choice?” East Perrin gave a wry smile. “If it wasn’t for not having any other way, who would pin their hopes on someone whom they had not known for a long time?”

“How about digging a tunnel?” Malone suggested.

“We don’t have the energy and time. And if what you say is true, that the Predators originally came out from the crevices in the ground, then digging tunnels would likely be even worse,” East Perrin replied helplessly.

Chapter 940: Hope 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

East Perrin looked at the sparse figures of Predators who were watching her from afar and sighed. She looked back at the people left on defense duties on the wall. There were only a dozen or so left and all of them were haggard and listless. They had eaten and drank to their heart’s content, consuming the original portion of those who were dead. Since they were about to die now and might not live till tomorrow, it was completely meaningless to save on food.

“If another Invisible Predator like the previous one comes, just a few more of them and everyone will die,” Malone tiredly remarked on one side.

East Perrin nodded and stopped talking. She was already extremely tired.

If it were not for the little hope on Garen’s side, she might not have been able to hold out and just wanted to give up on her fate.

Looking back at the direction of the stone house where Garen was at, East Perrin renewed her perseverance.

“Never give up until the end.”

She recalled her mother’s last words. This was also the law of survival she had been depending on all the while in the radiation belt.

*****************************

Basement

After one hour…

Garen carefully watched the bloody creature that was taking shape in the Biochemical Pool. It was a one point six meter wolf dog-like animal. It seemed to have only the torso and the limbs had not fully developed. There was also no skin and the whole body was bloody, like a wild dog that was just skinned.

But what impressed Garen the most was that pair of eyes, dark green, giving people goosebumps.

He looked up at the timetable he had brought in.

“It’s been an hour. The theoretical time has been reached, but it has not yet been completed. Maybe the cultivation environment is not ideal, the quality of the biochemical fluid is insufficient, and other reasons also lead to that.”

He murmured the calculating of time.

The color of the biochemical fluid seemed to be slightly lighter at this time, not as rich as it was at the beginning.

He continued to wait and did not shift his gaze away from the Biochemical Pool for a moment.

He watched the wild wolf’s limbs began to lengthen and develop fully. Then it was the tail and afterward, black skin gradually covered all over it.

Awoooo!

A black wild wolf slowly crawled out of the edge of the Biochemical Pool. When it shook its whole body, thick black hairs quickly grew. It crouched in front of Garen.

It was an hour and a half from the time he had put in the material to begin cultivating.

Garen walked over to it, ignoring the biochemical fluid that was still on the wild wolf, and reached out to gently stroke the head of the wolf.

The wild wolf was half a man’s height in its squatting position, the same level as Garen’s chest. As its head was being stroked, it also made a deep sound. There was no resistance at all.

Garen observed the wolf carefully. This guy looked no different from a normal wild wolf, except that its claws were sharper, its physique was stronger, and it looked like its combat power was not bad.

One could comprehend with a little imagination. If it were really an ordinary wild wolf, it would be impossible to get a rating of Level One combat power. After all, the Level One standard was based on the standard of a Level One pilot operating a Mech.

“Next is the most critical step…” Garen also began to feel nervous.

Although the wild wolf was only an ordinary Level One basic cannon fodder, the combat power was similar to that of a Level One Mech soldier, only slightly weaker than it. In fact, two wolves could barely confront a single Mech soldier. But if adding in the Distorted Seed…

Garen’s outstretched palm slowly cracked open a mouth-like gap and a large number of blue silk threads swarmed out of it. In the center of the silk threads, a twisted and wriggling clump of blue flesh slowly wormed out. When stroking the wolf’s head, it silently touched the space on top of the head between its ears.

Ssss…

The Distorted Seed drilled in as if it was virtual and penetrated directly through the wild wolf’s skull.

Wooo!!

The wild wolf instantly froze. Its eyes bulged slightly as the glittering green eyes began to fill with red blood traces. Its whole body also started to swell up slowly. Its claws continued to lengthen, growing thicker and harder. Its back was vaguely arched with two strong muscles while its ears grew furrier and a little longer.

The entire body length extended to nearly two meters.

“The unit that had Distorted Seed attached to it will have their original quality increased by three times. I wonder how the wild wolf’s strength will be after this increment…” Garen looked at the transformed wolf. “From now on, all these upgraded units will be called Big Wild Wolf.”

He named it simply.

“Squat down!”

He ordered.

The Big Wild Wolf immediately squatted down and was very obedient. Obviously, the Distorted Seed did not affect the control center in its brain. That was the most critical core for Energy Machinists to control the cannon fodder units, same as what was deduced by Garen before.

The Big Wild Wolf gained a powerful growth from the Distorted Seed and had perfectly acquired the Energy Machinist’s brain control.

“The trouble now is that the Distorted Seed is not limited by its quantity and as many as possible can be developed, but there is a problem in controlling it. On the contrary, the quantity of the Energy Machinist’s cannon fodder units is limited but there is no problem in controlling it.”

“Quantity and control. How to get the best balance between them both…?” Garen was brooding.

If he abandoned control, he could create an unlimited number of Big Wild Wolves as long as there were materials and biochemical fluid. He would be completely unrestricted by the upper limit number of control imposed on the Energy Machinist.

However, if he wanted absolute control, then the number would naturally not go up because his current Energy Machine Imprint could only control one Big Wild Wolf. The characteristic of an Energy Machinist was that with the advancement of every two levels, the upper limit number of control would increase by one.

In other words, Level Two could control one, Level Four could control two, Inheriting Level Six could control three, progressing as such. Of course, because of the huge limit of the number, most people would choose to continuously strengthen the unit creature of their control. They would enhance it as much as possible and take the elite route.

In fact, there were also Energy Machinists who took the group fight route, but the individual strength of the cannon fodder would not be worth mentioning. This was also a very cost-effective way to burn money and was not subjected to the environment.

The way of the group route was to separately implant control chips for each cannon fodder unit. The advantage of doing so was that it would not completely burden the Energy Machine Imprint. The disadvantage was that it would lose the increment brought about by the Energy Machine Imprint.

This was because every level of the Energy Machine training method would upgrade one’s control unit.

Just like Garen’s NIS training method, each level could increase the speed and basic defense of his control unit by 0.5 level. This way, compared to the ordinary cannon fodder wild wolf, the wild wolf controlled by Garen could now have one level of advancement in speed and basic defense. The combat power would have increased a lot.

Of course, if this kind of wild wolf made by the same Level Two Energy Machinist was encountered, then it would naturally be about the same.

“Quantity… What I need now is the number that I can control…” Garen stared at the Big Wild Wolf and was deep in thought.

He used to be the top biochemistry master in Totem World and had a world of sedimentation and knowledge of civilization for the cultivation of biological genes. He had more different development ideas than the scientists in this world.

“The limitation of quantity is in the upper limit control of the training method. So if I want to increase the number, I will have to either increase the level of training method or weaken the training method Willpower required by one creature. If controlling one creature would need one unit of Willpower, then if I could reduce it to 0.5 a unit, I would be able to control two creatures.”

Garen found the source.

“Then where is the key module where the Energy Machine Imprint controls the wild wolf?”

His consciousness went deep into the Energy Machine Imprint and began to trace the extremely complex structure to find the relevant module.

The Energy Machine Imprint was like a sophisticated manufactured quantum computer. There actually were traces that could be followed and the division of work in each major modules was clear.

Garen quickly found the module from the records of the Energy Machinist training method.

The Energy Machine Imprint was divided into two parts, the computing part and the production part. The Control Mod was part of the production part. It was a very compact black box-like encryption block. Many thin lines were stretched out from the inside and were gently waving like tentacles. They were releasing an inexplicable fluctuating signal. This seemed to be the source for controlling the Big Wild Wolf.

“The controlling of the wild wolf doesn’t seem to be done through wireless signals?” Garen analyzed carefully and experimented several times before coming to the conclusion. “Instead, the built-in structure of the wild wolf’s brain was implanted in advance so that it will instinctively view me as its master and intuitively obey my commands. At the same time, it seemed that a linguistic system has been implanted in it. Are these cannon fodders capable of comprehending simple command language?”

Garen reached a somewhat ridiculous conclusion, but in line with logic, this conclusion was indeed highly reliable.

“Can I transfer over here some of the techniques used to control the Silver Totems back then?” Garen began to ponder. The Silver Totems had given him a lot of help at the beginning. Despite its insignificant role in the later period, it did give a huge boost due to the early accumulation.

The current Energy Machinists were somewhat like controlling the Silver Totems at that time and both had somewhat similar effects.

“Back then, Black Sky’s crystal ball’s derivator was the core used to control the Silver Totems. The principle of that thing was to use a kind of ore called Resonance Stone to control remotely, which was not much limited by quantity. If I can find something resembling Resonance Stone as an alternative, maybe I can overcome this limitation.”

Garen’s heart moved as he seemed to find a breakthrough.

The Silver Totems in Totem World used the means of resonance to perform complex control.

The resonance of Resonance Stone actually only had a few simple combinations, but the people of Black sky used these combinations as basic units, like how computers used 0s and 1s to combine a myriad of different kinds of software. They also used this kind of combinations to construct an extremely complex crystal ball derivation to achieve the goal of controlling Silver Totems using resonance.

Garen had studied this skill back then. Adding on the information obtained from the help of that female in-house staff of Black Sky, he had done a thorough research on it. It was originally thought that he would not be using it in the future but he did not expect to be able to actually use it again here.

“In this world, although the research on resonance is not in-depth, many of the materials that can generate resonance are available.” A variety of materials that Garen had seen before on the computer instantly flashed through Garen’s mind. Most of which were plants and part of them were marine life.

He went out, picked up all the remaining unused materials and began to search through them.

Although the plants that could generate resonance were very rare, many plants in effect had such phenomena. Fortunately, there were many such plants in the radiation belt. Through resonance, these plants transmitted basic information including environmental information, survival suitability, and so on, in order to choose the optimum living environment.

Chapter 941: Big Wild Wolf 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He flipped through it and searched for a while. This thing was rather common in this world, the scientific developments meant that the research about the inner workings of practically anything was frankly shocking. Naturally, this world also had Resonance research, but it was not nearly so advanced as to use Resonance to make algorithms, because physicists now were already researching the even more advanced photonic computers. These used pure light as the main care of the computer’s calculations, so compared to quantum computers, these photonic computers functioned on a completely different principle.

Quantum computers had the advantage in solving complicated problems with more variables, as well as in modular computing. By calculating according to quantum modules as the singular unit, it actually also involved some separate principles in Resonance regarding quantum interference. But it was not as advanced as how the Totem World utilized Resonance.

Photonic computers had the advantage in traditional computing basics, as they could greatly increase the computing speed, reduce the usage of energy, and worked at far faster speeds than before. They could compute many operations at the same time, and were very good at correcting mistakes as well. Even if there were some small mistakes in the process, these would not affect the final result. With a higher-level aim in mind, the physicists naturally would not bring their attention back to Resonance research, with its vague future.

Even though Resonance research had many benefits for long distance communication, this long distance communications had long ago been realized through material-energy conversion, so there was even less need for this research. They could convert material directly into energy, and could thus leap across long distances, reaching their destinations directly, before turning back to material. It was far superior to backward technology such as Resonance.

Garen broke out of his thoughts, and carefully picked out an egg-like stone with red fire patterns from a pile of materials. The stone was very small, just about the size of a fingernail, and seemed to be the egg of some insect.

Garen shook the egg slightly, and tapped it onto his fist lightly.

A crack immediately appeared on the stone.

“This is it, the Resonance substitute, the hardened rhizome of a plant.”

Garen was more than just a martial artist, he was also a powerful scientist, and experimenter.

Using Resonance skills to create a core, and controlling multiple cannon fodder creatures at the same time, only he would dare think of something like that, and under these circumstances where they had no high-tech gadgets as well.

“This is not a project I can complete in a couple of days…” Garen put the rhizome aside, and suddenly woke up from his experimenting fever. “In that case, I can analyze and distinguish the signal coming from the Energy Machine Imprint, then I can reduce it. It should be okay if there is just a small portion of the control signals released, right? Although this will influence the Big Wild Wolf’s logical thinking skills, it will also greatly increase the number I can control.”

Garen had once gotten an Energy Machinist, or rather, an ancient Modulation Engineer’s training method from the Honorable Noble, it was called Glowing Radiance.

There were some explanations and information about this in that book.

“Reduce the control power on one single unit, spread it up, and do your best to increase the number…”

Garen’s will entered his Energy Machine Imprint, and started to analyze the functions and principles behind each signal.

It was as though many tentacles bounced out of the Energy Machine Imprint, and each tentacle was a different color. When the cannon fodder creatures saw each type of tentacle appear, they would perform the corresponding action as though they had received orders. This was a secretive manipulation skill using light to differentiate the functions.

Of course, that was just a simile, the actual process was a lot more complicated than that.

But to Garen as he was now, with the help of the Energy Machine Imprint, his computing skills were already thrice the original value, and his computing skills were already far, far more advanced than regular Energy Machinists. Once they were tripled, that speed was beyond the human imagination.

Within two short hours, Garen had completely analyzed all of the complicated signals, splitting them into many parts. The main control Willpower only used up one-tenth of the Energy Machine Imprint’s Control Mod, and most of the remaining controlling aspects were mostly some free, meaningless controls. Stuff like controlling their eating, excreting, sleeping, or even the playing or healing they would have as pets, Garen was totally capable of using the Distorted Seed’s innate ability to replace these, and it made them even stronger.

He directly turned off some useless parts, and only maintained the basic main controls, some basic commands such as attack, stop, move freely, rest, and so on. This also saved up on a lot of the Control Mod’s operations.

After he used his Willpower to trim the Energy Machine Imprint again, Garen instantly felt his control of the Big Wild Wolf fade considerably.

“Sit!”

Garen barked at the Big Wild Wolf softly.

There was no response. The thing continued to stand there, occasionally sticking out its tongue, looking really dumb as it stared at Garen.

“Rest!”

Garen tried again.

This time, there was a response.

The Big Wild Wolf walked around in a circle and then found a spot that looked very comfortable to lie down, its whole body relaxing, and quickly entering rest mode.

“As I thought, the controls were greatly reduced and lightened. Maybe I can try to control several, in that case.”

Garen brought his gaze back to the BiochEnergy Machine Imprintcal Pool.

Suddenly, there was a slight tremor from outside.

“Something happened again?” Garen gave the Big Wild Wolf an order to follow him, and the man and wolf ran out of the basement, looking at the large gate in the distant wall ahead, where someone seemed to be yelling loudly.

The two people on the right who seemed to be keeping watch over Garen’s basement burst into a sprint, running towards the city wall.

“What happened!?” asked Garen, rushing over and grabbing one of them.

That person was first given a shock by the large wolf, and then he raised his gun to shoot it, but Garen immediately pressed his arm down.

“That’s my pet! Tell me, quick, what happened?”

“It’s the Invisible Predators, they’ve come in again!” The man could not break free from Garen’s arm, and his face turned red. “Let go of me! I need to save them!” he yelled.

“Do you want to save them, or do you want to die?” said Garen coldly.

He turned around to look at the Big Wild Wolf behind him, using his Willpower to code it as No 1 quickly.

“Follow him, and attack these creatures.”

Garen directly gave it an image of the Predators using his Willpower, and that included Invisible Predators.

The Big Wild Wolf howled softly in reply, and followed behind that man.

Only then did Garen let go of the man, letting him run away. At the same time, Garen moved towards the direction of the gate and the wall, constantly vigilant of the surroundings, in case someone mistakenly shot at the Big Wild Wolf.

Leo City initially had thirty-four villagers, but now there were only seven or eight left. With East Perrin and Malone, they had exactly ten, and their manpower looked sparse standing on the wall. It was extremely empty, and they were far too small compared to the city that could take several hundred residents.

Right now, they stood on the wall by the main gate, spread out and vigilant of the situation beneath them as they held their guns, but there was despair in most of their eyes.

Ten of them was not enough to guard all the checkpoints on the wall. If they guarded the front, the back would be left wide open.

When Garen brought two people and a Big Wild Wolf to them, they were all slightly dazed.

The Big Wild Wolf followed closely beside Garen. Its body looked to be almost two meters, its appearance ferocious, similar to other mutated beasts, and it did not attack anyone at all. But no one could remember if anyone reared such a fierce dog in the town.

Only Malone and East Perrin showed a glimmer of hope. East Perrin got off the wall of her own accord, and greeted Garen.

“This is the hope you mentioned?” she asked quietly.

“Yes.” Garen nodded. “There will be more than one, and it can replace the dead men to patrol the town. It’s very fast too, and can be maintained for a long time. One of these would be equal to at least two people.”

Joy flashed through East Perrin’s eyes.

“How many more can you make?”

“Depends on the time and materials,” replied Garen softly.

East Perrin nodded, and quickly ran to explain the Big Wild Wolf to the others. She did not say much, she just told them that this big thing would help protect the town. Although the townspeople were wondering where it came from, this was not the time to sweat the small stuff.

And Malone seemed to have an inkling of a guess, in his seventy or eighty years of life, he had indeed seen something similar.

He approached Garen, and while East Perrin was on the other side introducing the Big Wild Wolf, he asked Garen quietly.

“Energy Machinist?”

Garen paused, and then smiled.

“You know too?”

“I saw one when I was young, it’s a very impressive profession, most people can’t even meet them.” Malone nodded.

Just when everyone seemed to have a glimmer of hope.

Suddenly the Big Wild Wolf abruptly pounced at an empty space to the right, its sharp teeth and claws slicing through the wind, as it clawed at the air.

There was a tear, and something seemed to get caught, instantly torn in half by the sharp claws.

“Invisible Predators!!” someone gasped.

Only then did the rest realize that the thing pressed under the Big Wild Wolf’s paw was an Invisible Predator that had snuck in. Its invisibility had been torn apart, and it showed itself, the Big Wild Wolf chomping down on its corpse’s flesh and blood.

It never occurred to Garen that the Big Wild Wolf might actually eat the Invisible Predator’s corpse directly.

This was an unexpected change, but he sensed it carefully and found that the Big Wild Wolf’s genetic structure seemed to be even more stable after eating, echoing back a signal that lasted even longer. So he made no attempt to stop it.

“There seem to be some accidental changes that I can’t control.” Garen carefully observed the way the Big Wild Wolf ate the Invisible Predator, to see if there were any signs of it being infected by the radiation disease on the Invisible Predator.

It seemed to be due to the Distorted Seed, but the Big Wild Wolf seemed completely unaffected. It ate up most of the corpse in a few large bites, and even crunched up the bone, chewing it and swallowing down, without wasting anything.

“Kill them freely, but do not leave this area.” Garen gave the Big Wild Wolf the order to only hunt the Invisible Predators within the town, and then to rest once it was tired.

He watched as the Big Wild Wolf made a few large leaps, quickly vanishing behind a stone house in the town.

Rip!

There was another low scream, and yet another Invisible Predator bit the dust.

While it sent a chill down the spines of the survivors, they also felt a long-lost sense of security.

Chapter 942: Big Wild Wolf 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“With this big guy, we can finally relax a little,” murmured Malone softly.

“Yeah, it can find the Predators through their scent, and it can see in the dark as well. It’s quick, and can patrol the whole town once in a few minutes.” Garen nodded.

Right now, although the Predator Army would arrive within a day, and there was heavy pressure weighing down on all of them, they still felt a deep spring of hope at seeing this powerful living tank join their side, killing the Predators they could not see everywhere.

No one said anything, the survivors just stared at Garen quietly, deep hope in their eyes. They just knew that Garen was someone from the regions that their leader had brought back, and nothing else. But right now, in their darkest hour, Garen stood out and gave them all some hope.

“Why didn’t you bring it out sooner!!?” Suddenly, an angry voice came from the crowd.

A young man with a scar on his forehead stared at Garen, his face scarlet.

“If you had taken it out sooner, we wouldn’t have had to lose so many people! If you had taken it out sooner, would we still be in this situation right now?!” The young man rushed out and swung a fist at Garen.

“It’s all your fault!! We’re in this state because of you!!”

He howled, his fist aimed for Garen as he shouted.

Garen reached out a hand and caught his fist.

“Fool. If I really could take it out sooner, would you need to run out here and tell me?!” Garen said icily. “If it weren’t for the fact that your leader saved me, I couldn’t be bothered with your lives. What does it matter to me if you live or die??” he said directly, without hiding.

“You!! Listen to that! Listen! What monstrous crap is he spouting?!” the young man roared angrily.

But no one responded, the others, including his companions, just looked at him coldly. No one in the radiation belt was foolish, no one knew what this young man wanted to accomplish by running out here, maybe he just needed somewhere to vent. But no one was going to join in on his madness.

“Barr, your older sister and father were killed by the Invisible Predators, this has nothing to do with Mr Garen. Just as he said, if Leader hadn’t saved him, he would not bother with our lives at all. And Mr Garen was working his head off just now, we all know it. That large hound didn’t appear before, and now it’s here, everyone can imagine what happened in between,” said a slightly older middle-aged lady softly, stepping out. “If Mr Garen could have brought it out earlier, he would have. There were more of us before, and add that to the hound’s power, it would naturally be easier to defend and survive. But he didn’t take it out, so what does that mean? Are you implying Mr Garen has no intention to survive?!”

The more she said, the stricter she sounded, her eyes staring at the young man, Barr. The latter’s sorrow and fury slowly quieted down, to be replaced with deep shame.

“Alright, we only have this few people left in Leo City, but we’ve weathered even tougher times before,” said East Perrin loudly, walking out of the crowd. While the Predators were not here yet, and it was relatively quiet around them, she needed to unify everyone as best as she could.

“Do you still remember the attack of the Mutated Earth Demons? How many did we lose then? In the end we only had fifteen left, but we rebuilt the town anyway.”

“Yeah, the new ones all died, we’re just left with the old hands now…” someone added.

The others all nodded.

East Perrin looked around her and said calmly.

“So, now that Mr Garen has given us hope, from now on, we all obey Mr Garen’s orders. We might still get through this yet!”

She had passed on the authority, even if there was not much authority left in a town of ten people, this was her way of making her attitude clear.

Nobody had any objections, so the decision passed easily, everyone knew that Garen was their only hope. Everyone else was pessimistic and had sunk into despair, but this person who appeared mysteriously was different. Evidently, he had some confidence in himself.

Under Garen’s calm, quiet leadership, everyone, including East Perrin, perked up, their spirits picking up again.

Rip!

There was the sound of the Big Wild Wolf killing Predators again in the distance, it had evidently killed off another Invisible Predator.

This allowed the hope to grow in everyone’s hearts.

If there were a few more of these Big Wild Wolves…

“From now on, everyone must listen to what Mr Garen says. My position as leader will officially be passed on to him. No objections?” said East Perrin loudly.

No one spoke, they all gave their silent agreement.

“Now, what do you have in mind, Garen?” Just then, Malone spoke, looking at Garen.

“The Big Wild Wolf will patrol and kill any Predators that might have entered the town, you guys just have to guard the walls. Await my further orders!” Garen nodded calmly, and turned around to walk towards the Biochemical Pool behind the town.

“There’s still a day before the Predator Army arrives, we need to gather up as much strength as we can.”

“Okay!”

That wave of chaos calmed down just like that, and Garen also became the leader of Leo Town in name. Although everyone still followed East Perrin’s lead, this would also slowly change and solidify with time.

Returning to the basement, Garen poured the second batch of materials into the Biochemical Pool again, and then he crouched down, his hand pressed against the side of the pool.

Instantly, a large number of Willpower threads from the Energy Machine Imprint shot out, rushing into the middle of the Biochemical Pool like a vast web of blood capillaries.

Big Wild Wolf production, round two, begin!

The second round of production took up to two whole hours.

Garen also edited the control methods the same way, and then gave it orders, sending it to the wall to help the others patrol. The Big Wild Wolf, strengthened by the Distorted Seed, was way stronger than the cannon fodder from before. With their vitality tripled, and with their innate fighting power, forget wolves, even humans could become overpowered killing machines.

Garen did not know just how strong the Big Wild Wolf could be after strengthening, but it was undeniably much, much more powerful than a Level One Predator.

Outside.

When the second Big Wild Wolf appeared, everyone let out a suppressed cheer.

That huge ferocious body, long, sharp claws, and fangs, those powerful muscles and features, these all represented safety in the eyes of the residents.

As soon as this parasite of the Distorted Seed that Garen named the Big Wild Wolf appeared, everyone seemed to look a little more relaxed than before.

It was time for their afternoon meal again, and the five people left on the wall scattered to keep watch, working together with the Big Wild Wolf to maintain vigilance. Under Garen’s orders, the others sat down to eat.

East Perrin followed the Predator-hunting Big Wild Wolf through the town, and found a hole in the wall that the Predators were using to enter the town. After she got some people to fill it in, there was no longer a hidden threat to their safety. Now that it was freed, that Big Wild Wolf was also ordered by Garen to patrol the wall, as an extra measure of security.

Malone and the others who had come down from the wall lowered their heads and kept drinking their meat soup, eating a mixed-flour pancake with dried vegetables. They would occasionally raise their heads to see the two Big Wild Wolves patrolling the wall and howling sometimes, and a sense of safety rose uncontrollably in their hearts.

“It sure feels good to have such powerful pets defending the town…”

That middle-aged woman who had berated the young man, Barr, sighed now.

“Yeah, thank goodness for Mr Garen’s help…” Malone smiled, and glanced at the others, who were either crouching or sitting down. Although it was quieter in the town now, it was already not as despairing and depressing as before.

“I think Mr Garen is a powerful Energy Machinist, I’ve seen such powerhouses before when I was young, they are head and shoulders above everyone else, even the lord pilots don’t dare to offend them,” said Malone softly.

“Energy Machinists, huh…” The middle-aged woman seemed a little dreamy. “Mr Garen is still so young…”

“If I could become an Energy Machinist too…” said a little boy beside them with clenched teeth and fist, he and the other little girl were the only two adolescents that had survived out of all the children in the town.

Soon enough, another two hours had passed, and another Big Wild Wolf, almost two meters in size, ran out of the basement behind the town.

As soon as this big guy came out of the basement, it went straight behind the town and climbed a wall there, starting to guard the back of the town.

Around the wall, the three Big Wild Wolves would occasionally pause, and occasionally they would run again. They were much faster than the average person and could recover from just a short break. They instantly brought a profound sense of safety to the townspeople.

It slowly grew darker, and everyone split up into groups. Five would continue standing guard, while the other five stayed back and rested to recover their energy. Add that to the three Big Wild Wolves, and it looked like they had more than enough manpower.

Malone brought two people to the water purifier to collect drinking water, while also checking on their battery collector. Although it took a long time to collect batteries in the town, it was still better than nothing.

They were busy, so after East Perrin arranged the defenses, she went to the basement to await Garen’s orders.

At seven o’clock in the night.

Another Big Wild Wolf ran out of the basement, this was the fourth one.

The four large beasts, each about two meters in size, ran all around the town’s defense wall, running and pausing at breaks, each of them guarding one side with the discipline of an army.

For a town that could take several hundred people like this, that was not particularly stringent, but the Big Wild Wolves were surprisingly fast, dashing here and there, flashing past a dozen meters in the blink of an eye.

At night, just as the townspeople were changing shifts, the two who had not completely gotten off the wall started yelling suddenly and loudly.

“The Predators are coming!!”

That voice was like dynamite, instantly waking everyone up.

Everyone picked up their weapons and rushed up the wall, getting ready to defend their home at any moment.

There were only six able-bodied left in the town who could hold their guns, putting aside the two children and the elderly Malone, as well as East Perrin, the leader, which meant that only six people could actually fight.

But add that to the four Big Wild Wolves, and that meant there were actually ten people.

Malone used the moonlight to look down from above, sprawled on the wall.

He saw more than ten Predators rushing at them on their hands and legs. Their eyes glowed red, and they had actually chosen night time, the time that Predators detested the most, to attack.

Chapter 943: Skill 1

Translator:EndlessFantasy Translation

Editor:EndlessFantasy Translation

"Fire!!" The middle-aged woman yelled the command.

Ra-ta-ta-ta…

The smattering of gunshots was heard, and four Predators collapsed, but ten more continued to rush madly.

They were extremely fast, each of them panting in a low voice, and soon they reached the bottom of the wall, climbing up it with their hands and feet.

And the Predators that had been shot earlier also got up again somehow, they only seemed to be slightly injured, so they rushed towards the wall again, casting despair on the townspeople. There was another hail of gunshots.

This time, the Predators did not even bother collapsing, they just took it in stride and continued advancing. Be it laser pistols or bullet ones, they were pathetically ineffective.

Just then, another Big Wild Wolf rushed out of the basement behind, this was the fifth one. At the same time, East Perrin arrived with Garen's order.

"Retreat, everyone, leave them to the Big Wild Wolves!"

Although some were reluctant, and some hesitated, but seeing as the Predators had already begun to climb the wall, the six of them quickly got off. They had gotten halfway down the stairs when they heard the low roars of the Big Wild Wolves behind them, as well as the screams of the Predators.

The Big Wild Wolves were like wolves in a flock of sheep, as long as their claws or teeth touched a Predator, they would tear out a long and terrible gash.

They ran around the wall at high speeds, hunting any Predators that would dare to climb up.

One Big Wild Wolf was pouncing at a Predator that had just gotten up, but before the latter could even react, the Big Wild Wolf had already reached out its claws and yanked the Predator onto the floor with a crash. It bent its head and bit, biting off half of the Predator's head, chewing it roughly, and then swallowing.

Another Big Wild Wolf faced off against three Predators that had climbed up together, tearing off half of the two Predators' heads with one paw each. At the same time, however, the last Predator scratched its neck fiercely with a claw, leaving a long blood-red gash.

The Big Wild Wolf turned around and jumped away, and then it suddenly lashed out with its hind leg, sending that final Predator flying high and away from the wall. It crashed onto a stone in the distance, and was instantly doomed. Its back had been completely smashed.

Within thirty seconds, by the time the last Predator was torn apart by the wolves and taken away in two separate halves, everyone, including East Perrin, was feeling slightly dazed.

They had guessed that these Big Wild Wolves would be very powerful, but they never thought they would be this powerful.

The fourteen Predators were all completely wiped out by these five Big Wild Wolves, and now, even their corpses were not spared, devoured completely.

As all of this happened in front of their eyes, all they could feel was a deep sense of safety!!

"We might be able to survive!!" murmured Malone softly.

No one argued, everyone felt the same way just then.

**********************

In the basement, Garen was constantly observing the five Big Wild Wolves that he had released.

He noticed that by eating, these Big Wild Wolves seemed to have obtained a large boost to their survival times. Apparently the Distorted Seed could use food consumption to stabilize their disintegrating genetic strains, this was something he had never noticed.

Normally, even those cannon fodder units that became parasites would not survive for longer than three hours. But he noticed that, after every time they ate and completely regained their energy, they could extend this survival time. One meal could extend their survival time by five hours, the second time they ate after that, it would increase by another ten hours.

He realized that the source of this was most likely the Distorted Seed he had released.

"Looks like the Distorted Seed still has many skills that I have yet to discover…" He recalled the information and records about the Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

There was not much there about Distorted Seeds, but indeed, if the Distorted Seed's parasites could only last for a short time, then wouldn't the Hellfrost Peacock Technique have to constantly repeat the parasitism? That way, how many times would parasitism have to occur before they could reach a considerable number in order to create chaos?

Such a power was completely unrealistic.

Garen vaguely understood now, maybe creatures with the Distorted Seed embedded in them could use large amounts of food consumption to assure their own survival.

"That way, if the woman I planted one on last time was lucky, she might still be alive now…" Garen remembered that Level Five Half-Moon powerhouse woman that he had planted a parasite on in order to escape.

"My hypothesis from before is wrong as well, a unit that releases explosive power after being given a Distorted Seed parasite can theoretically continue to exist infinitely. There is no time limit," Garen muttered.

He sensed the Energy Machine Imprint Control Mod he had, there were already five simplified Big Wild Wolves, and he could control five more, that was his current limit.

Unless his Energy Machinist level could increase, and his Willpower could make a leap forward as well, otherwise the most he could control right now was ten Big Wild Wolves.

"With my computing power, if I can delay it for a little longer, I should be perfectly capable of entering the third Energy Machinist level within a short time, and the upper limit will increase then as well. When necessary, I'll just have to reduce the defense area." Garen counted inwardly, ten Big Wild Wolves were already a very considerable fighting force.

According to the previous battle, one Big Wild Wolf was equivalent to at least five Predators, then ten Big Wild Wolves would be equal in power to fifty Predators. In a head-on battle, he might not be able to beat the hundreds of thousands of Predators, but if it was just defending a small area… That should be no problem.

"But just defending like this won't work either, we need to change to a place that's easier to defend. This town is surrounded by plains, the area that we need to defend is far too large, it won't work at all." Garen started to consider moving bases.

"We'll put that aside for now, it's extremely hard to find a more suitable defense point in the plains. First, let's try to use the Resonance Skill from the Totem World, if it works, then we can pit them against each other and break the production limit, and mass-produce these Big Wild Wolves."

Garen began to use the Energy Machine Imprint's computing power to calculate the likelihood of this plan.

The Energy Machine Imprint was just like a computer processor installed into his brain, it was extremely useful and convenient. Now that the Biochemical Pool was ready as well, Garen had some foundations to carry out his research and experiments too.

He continued to raise more Big Wild Wolves, but at the same time, he began his research on how to use Resonation Skills to perform simple manipulation. Thankfully, he had ready-made information and a large amount of experimental data from the Totem World for reference. All Garen had to do was test the accuracy of the data, and then create a set of simple controllers that used Resonation at their core, to solve the whole problem.

Time flew by.

Even though he had a lot of information from the Totem World to refer to, Garen still came across a lot of trouble in his bid to recreate the Crystal Derivator.

The quantity limit was very hard to remove, he had already tried all he could to save up on the more unimportant aspects of Willpower control, but he still came to a dead-end. The most important problem was materials, what materials he had to use to reach the effect he wanted, and what transmission medium the resonation code required.

There were none of the experimental prerequisites he needed here, Garen had nothing at all on hand right now.

After laboring around for some time, Garen put down the work in his hands and asked East Perrin, who was outside, to not let anyone in. He released the sixth Big Wild Wolf that he had created, and locked the door to the basement from inside. Picking up the key, he began to enter the special ability space.

If he stayed away from it any longer, he would probably be considered as having broken the contract, he had no intention of never being able to enter the special ability space again.

***************

"Hey, Garen, you're finally here." Inside the shop, Lan's face puffed up as soon as she saw Garen. "You kept us waiting so long, and you really cut it close…"

Garen laughed rather sheepishly, after living for so long, it was his first time being told off by someone who was younger than him.

"Where's Mincar? I'll go help right now."

"How's your Energy Machine Imprint? You got accustomed to the fusion?" Lan asked, concerned.

"No problem. I tried using it a few times, it's very effective," replied Garen with a smile.

"Mincar's inside, Senior Sister has gone to join the Energy Machinist Creation Contest, so he's the only one holding up in there. I can't do anything either. Please, help out my senior brother," said Lan softly.

"Sure, I will." Garen nodded, and pulled aside the shop's hoardings to walk inside. He followed the small corridor, turning to the left, and soon enough, he arrived at the experiment lab.

"I'm here." He knocked the door.

"Come in."

It was Mincar's voice.

Garen pushed the door open, and saw that his hands were pressed against a large floating sphere, his eyes closed slightly. There seemed to be a mound of red cotton candy growing inside the sphere, but Garen did not know what kind of Energy Machine Imprint he was creating.

"What do you want me to do?" asked Garen. It was his first time, so he did not know how to step in.

"Within a week, it's enough if you can independently create a passable Level One basic Energy Machine Imprint," Mincar said calmly, opening his eyes. "You can try using a smaller Cultivation Sphere, smaller Cultivation Spheres mean that the Energy Machine Imprints it cultivates are simpler, but conversely, they are larger in size."

"Oh, okay." Garen walked up to one of the Cultivation Sphere, and he started to listen to Mincar's explanation about how to lead his Willpower into the Cultivation Sphere, how to control it finely, and how to perform the intricate etchings to form the production part of the Energy Machine Imprint.

First, he had to try to understand the thing he wanted to cultivate, what imprint it was, or what kind of creature Energy Machine Imprint it was, for example. If you wanted to study the Saber-Toothed Tiger's Energy Machine Imprint, then you would need to be absolutely familiar with the Saber-Toothed Tiger's genetic make-up, using the cooperation between your own Energy Machine Imprint and your brain to grasp it completely. That way, when creating the Energy Machine Imprint, you would know precisely well how to create and Saber-Toothed Tiger and what it required. Hence, the process would be unnaturally clear to you.

"Actually, our understanding of many creatures' genetics has been analyzed to an unbelievable degree, so we just need to recall the parts of the genetic chain that we need. At the same time, we must remember how they are combined, what sort of environment or conditions are required for successful cultivation and so on. In the production process, we should find a type of cannon fodder that's more useful, and produce that."

Mincar continued to explain, "You can't just judge based on how powerful they are, you need to look at the larger picture, For example, the Saber-Toothed Tiger originally had a genetic aura ability called King's Majesty, this is the reason certain creatures would naturally feel fear upon seeing it. But this ability is completely useless against stronger opponents, and it requires many materials to make, so we need to get rid of it."

Chapter 944: Skill 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Mincar took his hand off the sphere in front of him and put it down, looking at Garen.

“We need to find a way, a way to create cannon fodder that’s strong enough but using the least resources, or a way that’s useful enough. The one you’ve chosen now is a Pet Lion’s sphere, as a Pet Lion, it’s usually reared by humans as pets. It doesn’t need sharp teeth and claws with blood grooves, and it looks sweet and adorable on the outside as well. It has a gentle disposition, as well as a pretty and majestic appearance. Of course, this would be different for those people who like ferocious beasts.”

Garen nodded to indicate that he understood.

“Then how should I analyze it? What do I need to use to control the gene chain?”

“This is the little thing we use the most often in this lab.” Mincar walked to the side and took a small white sphere off the window sill, throwing it to Garen directly.

After the white sphere was tossed out, it gradually slowed down, and finally floated in front of Garen.

It was a silver-white sphere, about the size of an egg, and it had something like a camera lens in the middle that was even turning and adjusting slightly.

“Genetic Operators, an extremely precise instrument that can only be used with Energy Machinist Willpower.” Mincar clapped his hands. “This thing is worth more than a million crystals, remember to be careful with it. There’s a computer control panel on it, you can search up the genetic chains of the creatures you’re looking for. You’ll need to remember a lot of things, so I suggest you choose the simplest one to start with.”

He turned around and left the lab after saying that, leaving Garen there alone.

Garen picked up the sphere and played with it for a bit, but as soon as he touched, he felt his right eye blurring slightly.

He blinked, and instantly felt the field of vision in his right eye expand. Everything had instantly been magnified, as though he had gone through an extremely long tunnel. After the dizziness passed, Garen saw a tiny particle of dust floating in front of his right eye. It had a strange hexagonal hole on it, and a strange-looking little bug had started living in it, constantly poking its black head out of the little hole.

“Is this a magnification effect?” Garen instantly realized that his right eye seemed to have zoomed in a spot in front of him.

Without further hesitation, he used his left eye to lock on to a position, and looked for the Cultivation Sphere as well. Soon enough, he found a small sphere that cultivated a wild wolf imprint.

Wild Wolves were low-practicality creatures among the cannon fodders, since they used up quite a lot of energy but were not all that powerful. Still, since Garen had a Wild Wolf Imprint now, he planned to research the principles behind it properly, to see if there was a simpler, more convenient way to reach the quantity limit.

He tried to release his Willpower threads, and as expected, those threads that used to be as thin as strands of hair, in the extremely magnified vision of his right eye, was made of even more, even thinner strands of threads woven together. Each thinner thread could be controlled, so Garen tried it, and confirmed his suspicions.

He tried to control the threads to approach that mound of grey cotton candy inside the Cultivation Sphere, that was a very primal grey cell. It was oval-shaped, and the cell nucleus looked like a walnut, surrounded by three black dots like satellites.

“How do I operate it?” Garen grabbed his laptop with one hand, there was a lot of internal information there. The Genetic Operator required very powerful computing power to maintain, because it was constantly burning up a lot of the Energy Machinist’s computing power. Garen felt as though he was a water tank being filled up, the burden on his computing power was just like the water being poured in. As time went on, he felt heavier and heavier.

After operating the super-thin Willpower threads for some time, Garen had no choice but to stop and rest for a while, giving his burning brain some reprieve. He read the information on the computer carefully, there was several hundred M’s worth of words and data on the genetic construct of Wild Wolves, which was equivalent to several hundreds of millions, or even up to a billion characters. These were all words he had to memorize…

“That’s why they say Energy Machinists are all monsters!” Garen could not help but swear. “No wonder I need the Energy Machine Imprint to continue to improve, without the save function of the Energy Machine Imprint, an average person could try for their entire life and it still would not be enough for them to memorize all this information.”

He rested for a while, and then started to let the computer flip the pages quickly, so his eyes could scan the information and save it into the Energy Machine Imprint. But the speed of the page-turning was extremely fast, several pages would have passed before an average person could even register what it was seeing.

This was the part of the Imprint that was responsible for computing power, the Computing Mod had a whole set of functions, including basic ones like saving, computing, and sending information. But just because he saved it, did not mean that it was his now, he still needed to memorize it to properly transfer it into his brain’s memory.

Put simply, this so-called Energy Machine Imprint was like a chip in the brain created from Willpower. It could help Energy Machinists perform all sorts of complicated operations.

But to Garen, who was himself an expert in biology, this was nothing. He already had a deep understanding of genetics from the Totem World.

To create an Energy Machine Imprint, he could use the gene fragments that already existed in the creatures, and then he could choose what to take and what to discard. But mostly, it involved him using his understanding of the creature’s gene chain to create a new gene fragment on his own, and then splicing it perfectly into the creature.

Cutting it, adding in the necessary features, standardizing the creature while specializing its abilities, and then reducing the energy consumption as well as the production times — these were all things Energy Machinists needed to do when creating an Energy Machine Imprint.

“The better you understand the creature, the more you will know about kind of gene fragments this type of creature can handle without falling apart, and at the same time, you also need to reach a new, delicate equilibrium.” Garen quickly understood the meaning behind this job.

It was indeed very difficult; to completely study a creature, including its genetic information, every stage of its physical development, its internal equilibrium, its endocrine exchange metabolism, and so one, would undeniably he a Herculean task.

But Garen had strong foundations in this, and after adding that to his terrifying computing power that was far beyond that of a regular Level Two Energy Machinist, he was soon trying his hand at modifying the Wild Wolf Imprint’s Production Mod. The first attempt ended in resolute failure.

But with the steadiness of his operating, as well as his using his computing power to fix it constantly, it was easy for him to gain full control of a mere Level One Imprint in no time. He just had to try twice, and succeeded easily.

At first Mincar had thought he would need a week to understand this, but he got it completely within two short hours.

Undoubtedly, having put so many potential points into his Intelligence, Garen was now an undisputed genius.

But learning his lesson from last time, after successfully producing a Wild Wolf Imprint that used less than 10% of the energy, he did not stop, and continued to modify the Imprint until it was practically unrecognizable, and even purposely made a few more difficult mistakes, putting on the appearance of what a normal, average Energy Machinist should be like.

It might not be a good thing to stand out too much too easily.

He checked the time, and only then did Garen realize that more than two hours had passed. Mincar had not returned yet, and he had finished reading the information, so he decided to study how to increase the upper limit of the number of cannon fodders he could control.

This included reducing the consumption of Willpower when controlling each unit, like Garen used just now. He could also use other items, like something that could amplify and support the Willpower, magnifying it, so that he could also reach his aim of a large-scale increase in the number of cannon fodders he could control.

Other than that, someone had also found the best combination to control the cannon fodder, using electronic chips to support the controlling, and the disadvantages of using that to replace Willpowers on most fronts, et cetera.

There was an essay there that mentioned this.

“Undeniably, the Energy Machinist is a powerful profession that developed from the ancient Modulation Engineers, and they are also the singular battle unit with the most potential in history, by a long shot! Even the most powerful Inherited Level pilot cannot match the potential of the Energy Machinist is large-scale battles. In that case, the upper limit of the creatures they can control has always been a huge problem plaguing low-level Energy Machinists. Most times, it is true that the cannon fodders can achieve unexpected effects. Therefore, to solve this problem, I would like to introduce a new idea. That is to self-distributed control units, L-units for short. This skill should be able to let Energy Machinists control a few of the other cores, and then using those cores to distribute control to many other cannon fodder creatures. A few of those cf creatures can also control cf creatures of the level beneath them, and as the layers go on, it will result in a powerful leveling system.’

This essay clearly defined the units, and Garen could not help but admire the technology of the time. Each of those peak-level scientists was the real deal, his only specialty was the little bit of background he had from the civilization of another world. In other aspects, he was lacking compared to these people.

“This is a level-based control system like that of the military, but it requires a great deal of resources to sustain. Compared to producing a squad like this, it would be more effective to use all those resources to properly train an elite task force.” Garen shook his head slightly.

This was followed by the detailed aspects of the essay, including the production process of a basic unit. But it was set aside because there were too many core techniques that were missing, in the Interstellar Age, there were too many weapons of mass destruction, so no matter how many cannon fodders you had, they could not match up to one peak-level powerhouse.

These skills naturally fell by the wayside, and no one provided them any more funds to advance the research. Even the author had probably more or less forgotten about it by now.

But when Garen read through it, he realized that the theory in this essay fit his Resonation Skill very well.

He could use the Resonation principle to create a control system, use his Willpower to control this system, and then use this system to connect to other energy sources, to control the large horde of cannon fodder underneath that.

“It’s perfect!”

Garen could not help a sigh of wonder, and then he quickly memorized this essay. But the essay also mentioned a production instrument that was necessary for creating the parts and the chip, as well an instrument to insert them safely, and finally they were missing a reliable control core communication skill, one that was not easily interfered with, and would not decrease with distance.

The first two were harder, but the last one could be easily substituted with Resonation Skill.

“That’s the one!” Garen turned off the website, feeling extremely pleased.

If he could just realize this skill, then he could break through the upper limit for the number of cannon fodders an Energy Machinist could control. In other words, as long as he had the materials, he could spawn Big Wild Wolves infinitely from the Biochemical Pool.

Chapter 945: Rush 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

When he left the special ability space, Garen was in a great mood.

In the world of Energy Machinists, he did indeed get different inspirations from all sorts of knowledge. In this high tech era, this Universal Age, this sort of information was the largest motivator. Every second of every day, there would be clashes between intelligence and flashes of thought.

In the stone basement, it was all quiet. He could hear almost nothing from outside, evidently the Predators had yet to begin their large-scale attack.

Garen glanced at the Biochemical Pool, he had used up more than half of the biochemical liquid inside, even the color was looking slightly pale. Still, it looked like it had some uses left in it.

“It’s too bad, if the biochemical liquid was better, I could reduce the production time of the Big Wild Wolves. One an hour would be easy.”

Garen sighed for a while, and began the production the seventh Big Wild Wolf anew before he walked out of the basement. There was a small hall on the first floor, and East Perrin was sitting, or rather leaning on a damaged metal chair. Her long hair cascaded down, and she slept deeply in the chair, leaning crookedly. She really did look utterly exhausted.

There were several pots of properly processed materials next to her, these seemed to have just arrived. He had no idea when she had left the town, as more Predators gathered outside, it grew more and more dangerous to go out. He had no idea what pains and tribulations she had to go through to obtain this pot of materials.

Garen was slightly moved.

He looked at East Perrin’s sexy slanted figure, her pretty features, the grey clothes she wore pressing her breasts into a seductive cleavage. Her long legs were closed tightly, practically revealing that shape between her legs. This woman was not wearing underwear…

“If she was in the regions, such a beauty would surely have a sponsor, and end up a canary in a golden cage, huh? But in the radiation belt, she had fought her way to the position of leader of a town. When two people have the same natural talent, a large difference lies in the surroundings, huh?”

Seeing that East Perrin was sleeping soundly, Garen decided not to disturb her. Perhaps after the next sunrise, there would be a drawn-out, large-scale defense battle. Those who were lucky might survive, but those who were so fortunate would be glad to get off with death, rumor had it that some Predators liked to slowly chew away at someone’s limbs while they were still alive. They would emit a toxin with numbing effects, paralyzing a person’s senses, so that the victim could watch his legs being eaten off with his own eyes before dying, or even seeing his whole lower half getting slowly chewed and divided up.

Even Garen felt that such a horrific scene would be too cruel.

Walking out of the stone house, he saw that the sky, about to break into dawn, was completely pitch-black. Even the moon and stars had been hidden behind the clouds, the weather growing more and more oppressive, as though there was a storm coming.

Garen could clearly feel the oppressive air of nervousness outside.

The six Big Wild Wolves were either standing or sprawled on the wall, some of them walking, others resting with their eyes closed.

From a distance, he could see the wandering green wolf eyes on the wall.

Their presence had given the town’s remaining residents a strong sense of security, as though they were an automatic defense line. Without anyone watching them, they could still constantly protect everyone.

Garen’s appearance seemed to have surprised the people outside, and he could see signs of cooking fires all around. Evidently, the current townspeople were using this underground basement as the center of the city.

The other ten, including East Perrin, all surrounded Garen’s basement.

“It’s starting…” Garen saw Malone come over and heard him speak softly.

“Yeah, they should attack at dawn.” Garen nodded.

The other eight had all gathered here, two of them children and the other six adults. The impulsive young man who had argued against Garen yesterday was here too, as well as that middle-aged woman who scolded him. The many dirty faces surrounded Garen. They each held the gun and ammunition with the strongest resultant force in their hands, it was a submachine gun that was similar to a service pistol.

“I’m afraid we won’t be able to defend this place…” Garen shook his head. “The place is too big. There are too many areas to defend, if they come with a large-scale attack, the Predators won’t just attack from one side like before, they will surely attack from all sides, and climb the walls at the same time.

“We can choose the most solid building to protect as our base,” someone suggested.

“But that way we’ll eventually be trapped there until we die!” retorted the middle-aged woman.

“That’s right,” Garen nodded in agreement. “Indeed, we’ll just end up being surrounded until we die. We’ll need to find a secure place that would be most easily defended, and use that as our new base, we can’t stay here anymore… Or else we’ll all die!”

Everyone fell silent at his words. Actually, none of them were stupid, those who could make it this far were all elites who were stronger in physical and mental capacity. Everyone had thought of that, but their attachment to Leo City made them reluctant to leave it. Now that Garen had voiced it out, however, no one would object.

Because everyone knew that he spoke the truth.

“With the six Big Wild Wolves around now, we can still rest for a while, but we might not have so much time after that,” said Garen calmly. “That’s why I need you to think properly, we need to find a place with a water that’s easily defended, preferably with only one or two sides that need defending. That would greatly reduce our burden.”

“How about Radiation Lake?” asked Malone in a small voice. “I remember there was a very large underground cave there.”

“Maybe not a cave, the Predators came from underground, they might know other ways of digging,” Garen shook his head.

“Then what about on top of the mountain?” The one who spoke was a petite young girl, her face was covered in mud so her features could not be seen clearly, but there did seem to be many bloody scars all over her face. Still, she seemed to have developed very nicely, revealing her fair white waist, white bandages wound around her chest several times tightly. And then she used her long black hair to cover it.

“Her name is Sinno(1), she’s the daughter of Sincan, who was the strongest hunter in town. When she was young, she thought that her pretty face would invite trouble and danger, so she carved up her own face with a knife. She’s a feisty one,” Malone introduced the situation to Garen softly. “Never underestimate her because she’s a woman, of all the adults here, she is the most capable in battle.”

That meant she was the number one battle general.

Garen knew what Malone meant, the strongest person in the whole town was actually this girl called Sinno, who looked no older than twenty. She did not look very buff or muscular either, and instead gave off a very nimble impression. She was clearly a skilled and agile fighter.

Normally, if he could win over the strongest fighter in a group, he would be able to easily earn the respect of the group, that was the way things usually worked.

Malone’s explanation also probably meant that he hoped Garen could convince this Sinno.

“Sinno, was it?” Garen looked at the girl. “Where do you mean by on top of the mountain?”

“I once ran in the wilderness for three days and nights in pursuit of a mutated beast, but finally I got careless and was attacked. As I was near death, I accidentally discovered a natural barrier that could be used for defending,” said Sinno calmly. “The mountain peak there is a large round disc, surrounded by cliffs everywhere, and there’s only one way up the mountain. Even that way is just a very narrow crack in the cliffs.”

“How about the mountain rock?” Garen asked with a frown. “If the rock is not hard enough, the Predators can still dig through and destroy the internal structure of the mountain.”

“I’m not sure about that.” Sinno shook her head. She was no expert on this, so naturally she would not have noticed the hardness of the rock or anything like that.”

“Are there any other places?” asked Garen, looking around him.

“What about the ancient cities?” Malone spoke.

“No, the radiation levels are too high there, no one can survive without protection.” Garen shook his head slightly. He had been to the ruins of an ancient city before, it looked like a very complete mechanical city, and even the anti-gravity levitating airships were completely undamaged, but there was no one there, simply because everything there had extremely intense malicious radiation.

Even he needed to use the Cold Radiation constantly to resist it before he could safely pass through. Even if an average person dressed in a hazmat suit and stayed in the Mech, they would not dare to stay for long. Rumor had it that there were documents stating that someone had sent an intelligent unmanned bot inside to explore, but even the unmanned bot could only stay there for less than a dozen minutes before it would start to melt and meld under the radiation, becoming part of the ancient city. Severing the connection.

“Don’t even consider the ancient city, it’s far too dangerous,” Garen rejected it again.

“We’ll just go to the mountaintop that Sinno suggested! Everyone, make your preparations!” said Garen loudly.

Everyone instantly scattered, and began to gather the things they needed. Regarding the transport they would leave with, Garen found a small airship that could just fit the ten of them, but it could not go very high, so it would surely be attacked by the Predators. That just meant that the crucial point lay in how they would break through the enemy ranks…

Considering the Predators’ thick skin that acted as a shield for long-range attacks, Garen woke East Perrin up and asked her to find some of the heavy rotary propellers that they had pulled out of the garbage pile. These were ancient antiques that only rotary propeller plans could use, but they were extremely huge, and almost half as long as the airship. After they sharpened the sides of the rotary propeller, the back and either side of the huge propellers had become a terrifying weapon that could cut and kill. The sparkling silver edges of the propeller were like sharp blades.

“Make them spin.” Garen ordered people to hurriedly attach three engines from the trucks on land to the propellers, and the high-efficiency engines were plenty powerful enough. The modification took just over ten minutes, everyone working against the clock at lightning speed.

“Make ’em spin!”

Garen stood behind the airship and yelled, pointing at the rotary propellers.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh…

The engines instantly started, and the propellers began to turn fiercely, creating a terrifying in their wake.

Garen picked up a piece of wood randomly and tossed it. With a crack, the plank was instantly cut into several pieces that shot away in all directions, nearly hitting some people.

He nodded in satisfaction and organized the people to pile up the bodies of the battle-dead, piling them all up at the entrance to the very center of the city. This was so that the bodies could become bait, tempting the Predators to come in and eat, thus buying a little more time for the survivors.

Chapter 946: Rush 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The emotional reactions that Garen was initially worried about were not present amongst any of the people here. In the radiation belt, those who had died were fully dead. No one felt silly nostalgia towards the corpses. Even if they were somewhat emotional, everyone could understand these current sentiments as many of them had done similar things to survive in the past.

The harshness of the radiation belt had entered the depths of everyone’s hearts long ago.

Woo…

The low howls of the Predators echoed from afar. It was obvious that the Predator Army was about to arrive soon. The sky was about to turn bright as well.

“It is much faster than we had expected…” Malone’s face was solemn.

“Where’s the water purifying filter? Move it up!” yelled Garen loudly. No one was defending the enclosure now. When the Big Wild Wolf was present, everyone was helping out here instead.

A few people worked together to move the water purifier up the Flying Ship. Then, they brought the remaining bits of radioactive meat jerky and other food up there as well.

Garen quickly returned to the basement. There, the Seventh Big Wild Wolf already came out and was crouching on the basement ground while resting. When it saw Garen enter, the Big Wild Wolf whined and fawned over him immediately.

After quickly altering his instructions, Garen used the Energy Machinist Imprint to release orders towards the Biochemical Pool.

Suddenly, across the floor of the entire basement, the Biochemical Pool slowly shrunk. Most of the biochemical fluid that was running out ended up evaporating quickly. The entire biochemical pool drew itself inwards rapidly and formed a gigantic black flesh ball. As time passed, the flesh ball shrunk within the pit on the ground. From its original diameter of over one meter, it slowly shrank to about the size of a soccer ball.

Garen walked over and grabbed it in one go, lifting it.

One of the benefits of using Stoneheart Flesh to build a Biochemical Pool was being able to take it along. Of course, this was only the lowest level of biochemical pools. There were more advanced ones that were items that could enter physical spaces completely to circulate on their own and form perfect nurturing and production environments. They were much more efficient than Stoneheart Flesh Biochemical Pools and were able to conserve materials better.

As he carried the Biochemical Pool and the materials that East Perrin had wrapped properly while the Big Wild Wolf walked beside his feet, Garen walked out of the basement quickly. He waved a few times at the crowds that had already packed while everyone walked up into the Flying Ship one after another.

Initially, the entire Flying Ship was shaped like a shuttle and completely black. However, since it was scraped out of the rubbish dump, it looked like something that had been patched together raggedly from the outside. It did not have half of the smooth aesthetic or sense of beauty that was expected of a Flying Ship.

A row of people walked up into the Flying Ship in succession.

No one knew whether they would be able to break out of the enclosure successfully. Garen stood at the head of the Flying Ship and could see from the sensors that their surroundings were filled with large clusters of red dots. This Flying Ship could only fly at low altitudes and nothing higher than five meters. It was a normal anti-gravity floating Flying Ship that could not travel at great speed because it was not a high ranking commodity in the region.

He assumed that it was highly likely that they would have to pay a severe price along with this journey…

Standing at the front of the Flying Ship, Garen gazed into the faraway distance.

On the further end of the dark grey grassy plains, large clusters of black Predators were charging forward towards them now. In a short while, they would flood Leo City fully like black tidewater.

He gazed away. The first break of dawn was gradually appearing in the sky now. East Perrin and Malone were seated on both sides of Garen respectively. They were responsible for operating a series of control conditions in the Flying Ship. All of the other seven people had already boarded the ship.

“What about the Big Wild Wolves?” East Perrin worriedly looked out of the Flying Ship’s window at the Big Wild Wolves that were still standing fast at the enclosure.

“I’ll let them return,” nodded Garen to indicate that he understood. He used his Willpower and Energy Machinist Imprint to send a signal to the seven Big Wild Wolves immediately, allowing them to return to the Flying Ship quickly.

He did not let them board the Ship but got them to follow it from below instead.

“The Flying Ship is too small and has only enough space to accommodate us. Allowing the Big Wild Wolves to board the Ship would only create heavier burdens for us. Therefore, I got them to help us break through the enclosure from below instead so that they could assist our escape,” answered Garen calmly under East Perrin’s doubtful gaze.

“How unfortunate…” said Malone quietly.

It was truly unfortunate. Garen had used two hours to individually nurture every single one of these Big Wild Wolves. However, as they followed the Flying Ship to break out of the enclosure, an unknown number of them had already died on the ground. It was uncertain whether the entire herd would be obliterated completely.

“Has the escape direction been determined?” instructed Garen.

Only then did East Perrin start to set the direction frantically. This was her first time operating a Flying Ship and it was clear that she had not gotten the hang of it yet.

She was only able to reply to him after a short while.

“Determined completely.”

“How many Predators are there in front?”

“About two thousand. We might stand a chance if we charge forward at the fastest speed!” Malone replied him immediately.

“Alright,” Garen nodded. “Once you’re unable to charge forward anymore, just leave the Flying Ship and walk up the mountain!”

“Yes!”

“Okay!”

Although it was easy to say, all three of them actually knew that once they were unable to charge forward, they would be waiting to die at the moment when the Flying Ship fell.

“Let’s go then,” Garen issued his final command.

Finally, the small-scale Flying Ship began to gradually lift itself into the sky lopsidedly. Next, it turned its body and flew in the direction of a large door that was open on the right side of the city.

The seven Big Wild Wolves leaped down towards the enclosure and followed the Flying Ship closely from below. They possessed great speed that made it seem as if they were faster than the Flying Ship and were able to follow the crowd that was ten meters above their heads with ease.

Whoosh!!

The black Flying Ship resembled a black flying fish. It fled the cylindrical Leo City speedily and flew quickly in the direction towards the right. Seven dots below it followed closely behind.

Large dark clusters of Predators stood in the direction in front of them.

Pfoo pfoo pfoo…

The Flying Ship that was moving slowly at first then charged towards the Predator Waves. The screw rudders that were installed on its side, back and front began rotating quickly. These screw rudders had been polished before. Other than the one at the back, none of them had radian angles and would not form thrusts that would affect the speed and forward direction of the Flying Ship.

The rotating screws resembled three grey circular faint shadows that were constantly releasing humming noises that indicated high speeds.

The Flying Ship was like a little fish that had plunged into black water. In the blink of an eye, it had burrowed into the Predator Waves immediately.

The seven Big Wild Wolves below leaped into the Predator Waves as well and began to slaughter them maniacally.

The moment they met with the seven or eight Predators that pounced on them, the Predators were brutally cut into numerous pieces immediately by the gigantic screw rudders. Some of the remaining Predators were pushed a few steps backward when they were hit by the corpses that were flung out.

However, the engines of the screw rudders were slightly burdened by the additional weight.

The front of the sharp Flying Ship resembled an awl. A brief popping noise could be heard when it pierced through the middle of the Predator clusters firmly. In the blink of an eye, it had struck and injured five or six Predators.

There were one or two Predators that were sent flying. However, it was inevitable that the speed of the Flying Ship had slowed down immensely as if it had sunken into mud.

The remaining Predators pounced around in all directions, resembling the motions of wrapping a dumpling when they pressed against the ship at once. Despite their comrades getting chopped into pieces by the screw rudders, they were not the slightest bit afraid.

“Speed up!!” Garen yelled loudly inside the cockpit of the Flying Ship. With panicked looks on their faces, Malone and East Perrin held the control handles and tried their best to make the Flying Ship charge forward.

“The screw rudders are going to stop turning soon!” echoed Sinno’s shouts from the pager.

“Keep holding on! Start using the guns to shoot them off the areas that they’re pouncing on!” commanded Garen loudly.

The sound of gunshots followed quickly after. The seven Big Wild Wolves squeezed against the Flying Ship closely and formed a little circle. They bit and killed the Predators that were trying to leap towards the Flying Ship. This allowed the pressure against the Flying Ship’s screw rudders to decrease greatly. They started turning quickly again soon.

Bullet cartridges from the heavy machine gun that was installed inside the Flying Ship swept through continuously and sent the approaching Predators flying. Currently, the Flying Ship had traveled more than a hundred meters through the Predator Waves. The Flying Ship was also barely able to preserve itself within its little safety circle without getting damaged. Although the wounds on the bodies of the Big Wild Wolves kept increasing, everything was still worthwhile as long as they were able to charge through the Predator Waves.

Roar!!

Suddenly, a furious roar echoed directly in front of them.

The vibration of the sound waves caused the ground to tremble violently.

“It’s a Level Two Predator!!” The expression on Malone’s face changed immediately while he was still piloting the Flying Ship.

“I’m coming!”

Garen used his Willpower to control the Big Wild Wolves below him and separated three from the pack quickly. He made them pounce in the direction of the roar immediately.

Bang!!

Two Big Wild Wolves collided with a grey shadow in mid-air. Both of the Big Wild Wolves whined and rushed backward while fresh blood flowed from their heads after getting hit. The remaining Big Wild Wolf opened its mouth and bared his fangs in an attempt to bite the back of the grey shadow’s neck. However, it was sent flying after getting slapped by the other party. It seemed as though its waist was now broken fractured from the assault.

The grey shadow had to pay a price too as its momentum and inertia decreased at once. However, when it fell on the heads of two Predators on the ground, it used the soles of its feet to squeeze and explode the brains of the Predators, causing them to roar madly.

The shadow was actually a muscular man in a grey vest. He was blind in one eye but his mouth was filled with sharp teeth. Meanwhile, a strange greenish gray color had appeared throughout the skin of his body that seemed to be lacking elasticity.

Two vicious-looking deep bloody wounds could be seen on his chest and back clearly. Blood flowed out of the open gash continuously but as time passed, it could be seen with the naked eye that the wound was shrinking slowly.

“How strong!” Garen’s pupils widened. The moment he saw this Level Two Predator, he could already feel that this could not be compared to the average Level Ones.

“Another four!” In one breath, he made all of the Big Wild Wolves pounce forward. These Big Wild Wolves that were strengthened three times in Level One were much stronger than regular cannon fodder. Their sharp claws and fangs were their most terrifying weapons.

However, this Level Two Predator possessed quick movements and was not slower than the Big Wild Wolves. Coupled with his violent strength, there would be an additional layer of invisible strength whenever he landed a punch on one of the Big Wild Wolves which made it difficult for them to get up even after a long time. Next, the surrounding Predators would rush forward and crowd around it before tearing it to pieces and biting it to death immediately. That was the power of the Energy Field that Level Two Predators specially possessed which was similar to the invisible Mind Force.

If they were not so many lower level Predators here, perhaps the Big Wild Wolves would not lose their fight against the Level Two Predator. However, under circumstances like these, as long as one of the Big Wild Wolf’s movements were delayed, the surrounding Predators would seize the chance to pounce forward.

The four Big Wild Wolves and the previous three others were instantly submerged by the Predator Waves. Their final contribution was biting off an arm and leg of the Level Two Predator and making its speed decrease greatly. It was instantly left behind as it angrily watched the Flying Ship escape nearby.

Once the threat of the Level Two Predator had been diminished, the surrounding Predators gradually lessened as well. Some of them were not fast enough to follow the Flying Ship and were gradually left behind. The critical attacks of the screw rudders and machine gun immediately got rid of the Predators that were trying to pursue them. The occasional Predators that managed to hang on the Ship and sneak past the entrance of the cabin were immediately attacked and killed from all sides by Sinno and the others there.

Suddenly, the Flying Ship shook violently while the dark Predator Waves in front disappeared completely.

When the last few Predators were flung away by the screw rudders, everyone breathed a huge sigh of relief… They made it through! They had finally made it through!!

At this moment, a loud whistle echoed from the back of the Flying Ship.

It was a gigantic metal fragment that had been violently thrown by someone. Its sharp edges spun rapidly and formed a terrifyingly huge razor that was about to crash against the Flying Ship.

Roar!!!

In the faraway distance behind them, a Predator whose skin was completely bright red raised its head towards the sky and roared furiously before charging towards the Flying Ship speedily.

Chapter 947: New Direction 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“That’s a Level Three Predator!! Oh my God!” Malone yelled.

“Run!!!” Garen had only seen that Predator from afar but could already feel a faint piercing pain in his eyes. Level Three Predators were equivalent to first-rate Level Three Mech Pilots. He would not be afraid if he still had his initial Willpower, but now that a sea of Predators was chasing him, even the strongest Mech Pilot that ventured into those dangerous waters would die if they were not of Inherited Level. Moreover, his combat Willpower had become useless long ago. Therefore, he could only rely on his non-combative Willpower that was not even a complete system yet.

The Flying Ship increased its speed and moved forward. However, it had already reached its maximum load, making it impossible for the Ship to increase its speed now. In the end, there was no way for them to dodge the gigantic metal fragment that was rushing at them from behind.

Bang!!

After a heavy collision noise could be heard, the fragment that was spinning quickly penetrated the back half of the Flying Ship immediately. It seemed as if it had embedded itself inside suddenly, piercing the back of the Flying Ship deeply. The screw rudders that were still rotating earlier were immediately smashed to the point where they had twisted and broke off. The entire Flying Ship had become terribly slanted and almost penetrated the ground.

It was fortunate that the Flying Ship’s anti-gravity and acceleration systems were located at the bottom of the Ship. Otherwise, the motive power that propelled the Ship forward would be destroyed immediately.

Garen, Malone, and East Perrin had panicked expressions on their faces inside the cockpit. After charging through the sea of Predators and seeing a glimmer of hope, none of them wanted to fall so easily here.

“Fire backwards!” Garen commanded.

Without needing to be ordered, the people in the cabin at the back of the Flying Ship had already steadied their bodies and started to shoot at the back.

The previous collision had killed two people immediately. This caused the remaining people who were frightened earlier to explode madly with rage now. The operated the machine guns and raked the back with continuous machine gunfire maniacally as if they were leaning towards this fearful mentality.

After the resistance from the chains of bullets from four machine guns, the speed of the Level Three Predator behind them slowed down. The bullets that hit his body ricocheted off continuously. He did not have a single scar and chose to ignore them completely. However, his speed was slightly decreased because of this. After a few tries, the Level Three Predator had realized that it was impossible for him to chase the Flying Ship. He had also separated himself from the rest of the group and was too far away from them now. Therefore, he could only turn around and leave angrily.

Black smoke was coming out of the tail end of the Flying Ship. After moving forward crookedly and escaping for a certain distance, it was barely able to keep itself from falling completely. It moved shakily and flew forward while enduring everything continuously.

Ten minutes later, the crowd was still on edge. They did not dare to relax because they were afraid that another sudden ambush would occur again. However, misfortune did not befall them.

The Flying Ship finally left the region where the Predators had gathered. When they could no longer see a single red dot on the sensor, everyone finally breathed a sigh of relief.

“We’re safe…”

“Finally safe!!”

“Fanny! Are you okay? Fanny!” Inside the passenger cabin, other than the two corpses that were rolled up and taken outside, another person had their pulmonary lobe pierced by a piece of gigantic metal fragment that had flew over and penetrated the Flying Ship. Only when they had relaxed did they realize that his lower body was covered and overflowing with fresh blood. However, this person did not seem to understand the current situation. He had only realized that his hand were covered in blood when he wiped the wound near his lungs.

“Where are the hemostatic drugs?! Hurry! Hemostatic drugs!” yelled Sinno when he rushed over and covered Fanny’s wound.

“There are infectious reactions! Damn! There are germs and viruses from the Predator!!” screamed the youth that had defied Garen previously.

“Shut up!”

Whack!

Sinno slapped him painfully.

Someone brought over the remaining bits of hemostatic medicine and other drugs that could resist infections.

“I’ve lost too much blood. I know that I can’t go on any longer so don’t waste the medicine on me,” Fanny smiled, his face devoid of any signs of rosiness.

“How could that be?! Fanny, there’s nothing wrong with you! Nothing at all!!” yelled Sinno. She and Fanny had an intriguing relationship. They were like comrades-in-arms that had a friendship where they could live peacefully while relying on the other person. However, they were also like brother and sister. Fanny would always help Sinno check her openings and plug her loopholes when she was not paying attention.

“He’s already been infected! There’s no cure!! We can’t waste the medicine on him! This belongs to all of us!!!” yelled the youth again despite being hit earlier. The slap had caused both of his eyes to turn bright red while one of his cheeks had immediately swelled up badly.

“Damn! I freaking told you to shut up!!” Suddenly, Sinno threaded on his abdomen with one foot and kicked the fellow two meters away, causing him to nearly fall out of the gap at the end of the damaged Flying Ship.

“Say another word and I’ll kill you!!” Sinno glared at him fiercely. Her body was trembling as she pointed at the youth, as if she could murder him at any time.

“This medicine was originally retrieved by both Sinno and Fanny. It’s only right that we use it on them,” said a boy quietly with a slightly sentimental look on his face. He was one of the two children who had brought the medicine.

The hemostatic medicine was applied on Fanny’s wound evenly. However, it could not stop the edges of the wound from being infected continuously. The edges started to turn purple rapidly and lose its elasticity. It slowly began to release a rotten stench as well.

“Don’t waste it.” Fanny tried to move away but was firmly held in place by Sinno.

In the radiation belt, a little bit of medicine was the price to pay in exchange for a life many times. Therefore, all medicine was more valuable than gold and much more expensive than it as well.

Only four adults were left at the back of the Flying Ship. Both of the children had remained unharmed because they hid themselves in the safety of the middle of the Flying Ship. If Fanny died, Sinno, the middle-aged woman, and the male youth would be the only three adults left.

After the catastrophe within the vast Leo City, there were only these few people left. The atmosphere inside the Flying Ship was clearly much more desolate now.

“That’s right! Mr. Garen! Mr. Garen is amazing so it’s possible that he might have a solution?!” yelled the boy suddenly.

These words instantly lit up the eyes of the other people.

Indeed, Garen had been mysterious ever since he showed up. He was even able to use his mysterious means to create a large herd of Big Wild Wolves that were used as his strong wild animal-like pets to help everyone defend the area. If it was not for him, none of the people here would have survived.

If the seven Big Wild Wolves were not there, the Predator that was hiding inside the city would have devoured and killed everyone.

It was not an understatement to say that Garen had saved everyone here.

“I’ll go look for him!”

Sinno bounced up quickly and rushed towards the cockpit in front like a cheetah.

She pushed the door open instantly but did not run inside when she saw Garen walking towards her while furrowing his eyebrows.

“You don’t have to call me. I’ve seen your circumstances.”

He quickly walked towards Fanny and crouched down beside his body while checking his wound for a little while.

The wound was located at the left side of his lungs. It was so severe that it affected Fanny’s breathing, forcing him to take big gulps of air while gasping for breath. Murmuring noises escaped his throat occasionally, making it obvious that the internal bleeding in his lungs was getting more serious.

He checked Fanny’s pulse and noticed that it was very fast while his breathing was rapid and his complexion was getting paler. His blood pressure was gradually lowering as well.

Click click click! Garen snapped his fingers three times and tapped the main arteries throughout Fanny’s body that were connected to his lungs a few times. He used his pressure points, a jolting technique and coupled it with his own Cold Radiation to freeze Fanny’s blood vessels temporarily.

“What does it feel like?” he asked quickly.

“Cold… So cold…” Fanny’s lips had started to turn purple.

Garen pressed his hand against Fanny’s wound before a thin layer of ice rapidly formed there. Other than the affected external wound, the ice moved inside and froze the internal injuries in his lungs completely as well. In a place where the lines of vision of others could not reach, thin blue strands shot out of Garen’s fingertip at once. It burrowed into Fanny’s lungs and began to hungrily devour the blood that had accumulated there. It resembled a little snake that was swallowing something delicious.

Less than ten seconds later, it had devoured the accumulated blood in Fanny’s lungs completely.

“The issue of blood in his lungs has been solved. The infection however…” Garen retracted the strands from the Living Secret Technique and stood up while furrowing his eyebrows. “I’m unfamiliar with the Predator’s virus and I’ve never researched it. I don’t have any experimental apparatus here either, so I don’t have a solution for now.”

“What apparatus do you need?!” Sinno stood up. Her posture indicated that she would go and get anything that Garen required immediately.

“You won’t be able to get any of them in time,” Garen shook his head.

“I swear I’ll give you anything you want as long as you save him!!” growled Sinno softly. Both of her eyes were bloodshot and her hands were curled into tight fists.

Fanny’s consciousness had become blurry now, making it seem as if he was about to fall into shock soon. Garen stepped forward and quickly tapped some of his pressure points lightly while using his Secret Technique to temporarily stabilize the situation to the best of his abilities.

“You swear to give me anything I want?” Garen sneered. “What right do you have to say that? Do you really think you can give me what I desire? Don’t say silly things if you don’t know anything.”

Sinno clenched her fists tightly while her entire body trembled. She resembled a fierce beast that could go crazy at any time.

Ahh!!!!

She howled furiously as if she wanted to release all of the pain in her mind by yelling.

“I have only one solution which will barely sustain his life. However, the repercussions of this solution are extremely severe. From today onwards, his life will not be his own but will be completely controlled by me instead,” Garen opened his mouth and said slowly. “Moreover, he could become a terrifying monster at any time.”

“As long as he survives anything is fine!” Sinno nodded firmly. She immediately made the decision on behalf of Fanny who was no longer conscious.

“Alright!”

Garen nodded and knelt down. He had swallowed a lot of highly radioactive Nutritional Liquid and his body was filled with Distorted Seeds. Therefore, he could release them as he pleased now. The Distorted Seed seemed like a living creature that possessed numerous octopus tentacles that were waving about. Garen pressed it against Fanny’s chest gently.

Since he was moving at rapid speed, no one could clearly see the thing in his hand. They could only see a blue shadow that flashed past.

From the perspective of an outsider, it seemed as though Garen had simply pressed an open palm against Fanny’s chest where his heart was located.

“Alright, wait for it to be over,” Garen stood up. Despite not knowing the power of the Predator’s virus, he was extremely confident with the strength of his Hellfrost Peacock. The Hellfrost Peacock was considered a frightening beast in the universe that could rule the whole world. Although the ‘world’ in that context was referring to a planet, he could still see the magnitude of the power of Hellfrost Peacock that belonged to the Planet Overlord Level.

If the Predator virus did not belong to the Planet Overlord Level, it would merely be nutrients for the Hellfrost Peacock’s Distorted Seed.

The effects were truly fast as well. Right after he placed the Distorted Seed inside Fanny’s body, his condition improved rapidly. His breathing gradually regained its vigor and his heart rate slowly returned to normal too. The infections in his wound did not worsen and the only thing that shocked the others was the light gray outer shell layer that started to cover his entire body faintly. It seemed like a layer of scales.

“These are special cells that I retrieved from the bodies of the mutated creatures. I can control them to strengthen the bodies of other people. Nothing happens when they are not activated but once that happens, the side effects will be terrifying. He will immediately become a powerful monster that will slaughter everyone but me.”

Chapter 948: New Direction 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen explained the functions of the Distorted Seed in a simple manner, which immediately gave the few people inside the Ship chills. Was this not another version of a Predator?

As someone who could research cells like these, Garen had started to faintly exude the air of a mad scientist. This made the small group of people revere him even more.

“All of you need to be careful because I won’t be able to control him after he changes,” Garen reminded them seriously.

Indeed, the Distorted Seed could lengthen a person’s lifespan after they consumed it. Measures like this could indeed be individual means to save someone who had fallen into a state of complete despair. After all, the hosts of the parasitic Distorted Seeds would not become monsters immediately. As long as Garen did not activate it, it would not activate itself either. Therefore, it could live a steady life like a normal human. Moreover, the great qualities that were brought on by the Distorted Seed were beneficial towards humans. Two examples of this were the female student that was a host of the parasitic Distorted Seed in the Inner Courtyard and Inari, the commander of the mercenary group that was given a special mission. As long as Garen did not activate the Seeds, both of them would continue being his spies who would not be discovered by others.

It was unfortunate that Garen had undergone the process of being ambushed too early and could not activate these hidden forces in time. All of these changes happened too quickly.

After solving Fanny’s issue, Garen realized immediately that the few people here were looking at him slightly differently now. Although his image had now turned into that of a mad scientist, these measures were still considered by the crowd as the ultimate life-saving solution even when they were not wounded with fatal injuries! Within harsh environments like the radiation belt, no one would mind turning into a monster as long as it meant that they could continue surviving. Moreover, this was also a chance for them to become stronger.

After looking at everyone’s bewildered expressions, Garen returned to the cockpit quickly. Malone and East Perrin were still determinedly piloting the Flying Ship forward in a fixed direction

“How did it go?” asked East Perrin.

“It’s solved,” Garen exhaled and sat down. “How much longer before we arrive?”

“We might need a few more hours but we don’t know if this thing will be able to hold itself together until we reach the place” continued Malone beside him. “Leo City was destroyed and we’re the only few people left. Next time…”

“What are you scared of? We managed to survive even though there were only so few of us! Next time, as long as it’s safe enough and we have food and water, won’t it be easy for us to recruit others?” replied East Perrin nonchalantly.

“The Predator Waves was not a small issue that would only occur in one or two places,” interrupted Garen abruptly.

“What do you mean?” East Perrin glanced at Garen in shock.

“I was talking about the Predator Waves,” Garen looked her in the eye firmly and spat out the words individually. “This isn’t a simple issue that only occurs in one or two regions. Predators are currently on every inch of the Mother Planet. Every single region has cut off communication with the outside world and even trash isn’t sent outside anymore, do you understand?”

The arrival of this information was too sudden, causing East Perrin to almost forget that she was currently piloting the Flying Ship. She had nearly loosened her grip and almost allowed the Flying Ship to crash on the ground below.

“It isn’t just happening now. The Predator Waves will sustain themselves for a long time,” said Garen simply. “Predators that can fly might even appear next time and those that can breathe underwater might appear in the sea. That will be truly disastrous. They break out once every other hundred years.”

East Perrin steadied the Flying Ship and blanked out for a short while before looking at Malone.

“It’s true,” sighed Malone while nodding.

“It’s true?” East Perrin was slightly sluggish now.

The entire planet was filled with Predators. Other than the regions, there were no other places that were completely safe. Where would they go?

“Why do you think any of those regions haven’t expanded despite having such powerful forces? They could purify the radioactive areas slowly but none of them have done that. It’s because of the Predator Waves that occur every hundred years,” Malone explained. “I experienced it once previously.”

Experienced it once?

Garen glanced at this old man in a rather surprised manner. Was this fellow saying that he was actually more than a hundred years old? This was not a simple feat under the circumstance that the average lifespan within the radiation belt was only seventy to eighty years old. If this man was actually able to live for more than a hundred years, one could well imagine that he had a story behind it.

“We need a secure base. If that mountaintop is unsuitable, we need to think of another solution!” said Garen certainly. “I don’t wish to die by the hands of those unintelligent pieces of garbage.”

“I feel the same way,” said Malone in a low voice. “I’ve lived for more than a hundred years but I still want to live for a longer period of time. I don’t plan on dying yet.”

“Stupid old man, if you don’t want to die yet despite already living for such a long time, it’s less likely that young people like us are thinking of dying!” East Perrin rejuvenated immediately. Since her previous days were already tainted with blood from the edge of her blade, it made no difference that her current days were only slightly more dangerous.

“Right now, I’m only hoping that there won’t be any Predators in the place that we’re going to…” said Garen simply.

“No one lives there. If there aren’t any people, there shouldn’t be any Predators either…” said East Perrin hesitantly.

***********************

On the dark gray grassy plains, an abnormally shaped black stone mountain stood upright on the grass quietly.

The mountain resembled a gigantic black rock that was stabbed into the ground while upside down. It was shaped like a trapezoid while the surface of its terrain was filled with bumpy potholes that resembled bullet holes. The strangest part of it was the presence of a thin canyon that could be used as a walkway up to the side of the body of the mountain. The other parts were nothing but sheer cliffs and overhanging rocks while an abundance of various types of moss grew on the surface of the hollow pits. Therefore, the cliff was extremely slippery, making it impossible for people to climb it or hang ropes there.

The body of the entire mountain looked like a pyramid that had been smashed upside down by a giant. However, this strange shape was able to stand on the ground extremely firmly.

Currently, on the grassy plains near the body of the mountain, a damaged, shuttle shaped Flying Ship that was filled with patches was crookedly flying towards the only canyon path near the mountaintop. The Flying Ship that was only slightly longer than ten meters merely resembled a little earthworm in comparison to the mountain that was more than a hundred meters tall. Their size difference was not worth mentioning at all.

If it was not for the eye-catching black smoke that was coming out of the back of the Flying Ship, there was a probability that no one would be able to easily discover this terribly damaged little Flying Ship that seemed as though it would explode at any moment.

“It’s here.”

Inside the cockpit of the Flying Ship, Sinno spoke excitedly and pointed at the mountain in front while standing behind the trio that were seated.

“This is the place I visited previously! This place is very strange because blades of grass don’t grow on the mountain. Instead, only slippery moss grows here. If it wasn’t for my good fortune previously, I don’t know how I would’ve managed to climb up. I don’t think I would’ve been able to survive until today,” she said in a slightly glad tone.

“Do you have any other valuable information?” asked Garen quietly. “Regarding this mountain, what other dangers are there? Or other places that we should pay attention to?”

“I don’t know, I’m only aware that this mountain is extremely slippery. However, it won’t be slippery anymore once you’ve climbed to the flat ground at the top of the mountain. The moss only grows on the slopes and cliffs, making this place an ideal base,” Sinno shook her head.

“Let’s climb up then,” Garen nodded and signaled East Perrin and Malone to start accelerating before flying towards the mountain’s sole little path.

The Flying Ship faintly shook for awhile and tilted before it began to climb up the black mountain. The strange canyon provided the only path that led up to the mountaintop. There were tall, straight cliffs and mountain walls on both sides, leaving a little path in the middle of the canyon that was not even ten meters wide. It seemed as though people had dug it out so that they could go up and down the mountain.

The Flying Ship climbed up the middle of the canyon and approached the center of mountain closer.

Soon, a winding stream appeared on the right side. It flowed down along the ground of the mountain slowly. The stream was very small and only as wide as an opened palm. However, it would not be a problem for it to fill the needs of the few people that were currently here. There would not be any problems as long as they used the water purifier to filter it.

When they saw the water, the agitated people inside the Flying Ship calmed down immediately. In the radiation belt, the thing that frightened them the most was a lack of water.

“There’s a small lake that collects water throughout the year at the top. A water source is not a problem at all,” added Sinno. “This is a key reason why I said this place would make the most suitable base. However, the quality of the water here isn’t very good. It’s likely that it’ll be highly radioactive even after being filtered.”

“If we can’t even secure our lives now, it doesn’t matter if we end up drinking some highly radioactive water as long as we can continue surviving. A shorter lifespan is still better than death!” huffed Malone. “How is Fanny’s condition?”

“He’s quietened down and his condition has improved. He should be better after a few more days.” When she said this, Sinno’s gaze had simply brightened when she looked at Garen. Other than gratitude, there was also a longing for this terrifying self-healing ability that could be seen in her eyes. In the radiation belt, someone who possessed regenerative abilities like these could simply increase their rate of survival by more than half!

“Don’t look at me like that. You’ll see how troublesome it will be in the future,” Garen shook his head.

When the Distorted Seed went crazy, he would not be able to control it when it went on a killing spree against any living thing. Garen himself was afraid of that insanity as well.

He shook his head again when he thought of that.

The Flying Ship was gradually reaching the mountaintop soon. As the high density glass in front turned from darkness to light, the entire Flying Ship flew out of the little canyon path quickly and arrived at the mountaintop immediately.

The mountaintop was a large stretch of empty black flat ground. There were some bumpy pits while water had accumulated in certain areas. There was a huge lake at the right edge of the mountain. Two narrow streams flowed down both sides of the lake. One of the streams was the one that they had seen earlier while the other one cascaded down the cliff of the mountain. It looked like a white ribbon that was suspended from the cliff which was constantly being blown by the wind.

The most beautiful one of these water sources was the lake that had a diameter of at least one hundred meters. It was completely azure as the highly radioactive lake water produced a pure blue color that resembled the sky. There were no grassy plants inside except for the abundance of moss. All of the moss was blue as if the were the true reason behind the blueness of the lake water.

When looking at the lake from afar, schools of tiny black fish could be seen swimming about freely.

“What a good place!” Garen could not help but praise it as well.

“The radiation levels are twice as high as the flat ground. More severe side effects of the radiation illness will appear if you spend more than three days here,” said Malone while furrowing his brows when he saw the Flying Ship’s sensors that were detecting the radiation levels here. “No wonder none of the radioactive people came up to live here. This place looks beautiful but it’s actually a hell hole!”

The tilted Flying Ship decelerated to a steady pace gradually before finally stopping at the edge of the lake slowly.

“I’m going down to take a look.” At this moment, Garen had released the Cold Radiation that he was concealing within his body earlier. He walked out of the cockpit under the strange and amazed gazes of the two others.

“Mr. Garen is truly a mad scientist. The ability to modify himself into this state is… truly… amazing!” A strange look had appeared in Malone’s eyes. He had never expected to spend so much time beside a person who was so highly radioactive while being able to remain in good health himself. Moreover, this highly radioactive person had neither serious illnesses or weaknesses nor had he lost his mind and turned into a Predator. This was the strangest part that made people wonder about him.

“Mr. Garen is our hope now,” nodded East Perrin with a look on her face that indicated that this was not an accident at all because she had seen this scene long ago.

Chapter 949: Building a New Base 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen walked out of the Flying Ship. He reached his hand out to grasp the edge of the door frame at the exit of the Flying Ship. He could feel a strong burning sensation from the radiation that was coming towards his face and body. This sensation was trying to enter his body through his breathing.

The radiation levels were truly high and the Flying Ship’s anti-radiation panels would not be able to withstand it for much longer.

Judgments stirred in his mind.

He walked along the mountaintop towards the edge of the lake where the water was sky-blue like a large pure blue gemstone. Small ripples stirred across the surface of the lake when the wind blew past.

When they saw Garen walking over, a few tiny fishes swam over in his direction curiously. They poked their little mouths above the surface of the water in a peculiar manner that he could not understand.

Garen felt the air carefully and noticed that the temperature here was about twenty degrees warmer. It was slightly hot and more humid. The water vapor was probably being evaporated from the lake.

“If the issue of high radiation levels was not a problem, this would be a very good place to live.”

Garen crouched down and picked up a small, broken stone and then gently threw it into the water.

A ‘plop’ could be heard before one of the tiny fishes in the water was struck by the stone. It floated up before strands of blue blood dissipated. The other fishes dispersed quickly.

Garen reached into the water and picked up the dead body of the tiny fish. He sniffed it before putting it into his mouth and gently biting a piece of the fish’s flesh. He chewed it carefully and slowly.

It tasted slightly salty and somewhat fishy but the radiation levels was not too strong.

“It’s edible. Moreover, the salt content has lessened, so it shouldn’t be poisonous,” Garen nodded before standing up.

He started to wander around the entire mountaintop which was a wide and flat area that had a diameter of over two hundred meters. Although it was not extremely smooth, it was still a very suitable place for these few people to live.

This was the safest spot because the only path to the mountaintop was located in a narrow entrance near the edge. That place resembled a tunnel that led all the way down to the foot of the mountain. As long as they defended it properly, they would be able to completely block off the passage up the mountain.

The other passengers on the Flying Ship had alighted the vehicle one by one. They sized up their surrounding environments. When they discovered that the tiny fishes in the lake were edible, everyone else relaxed as well.

“There’s water and a small amount of food here. We could definitely breed these edible tiny fishes manually,” said Malone immediately when he saw the scenery in front of him.

“How many more days will our food supply last us?” Garen turned around and asked.

“About a week. Although half of it was taken away, we don’t have that many people left now since many of us died. Therefore, if we ration it out equally, we still have a lot of food left,” answered East Perrin in low spirits.

“Get ready to tear down the Flying Ship. Block off this passage completely and use it to make a door that can be opened and closed. Next, use parts of the metal and some rocks to put up a little house. No problem, right?” commanded Garen.

“No problem.”

Every one of these people were outdoor survival powerhouses. In the radiation belt, these were vital survival skills. Moreover, they had brought electric saws and drills and other similar tools to increase their work speed and make it more convenient this time. They were more efficient than usual.

The four adults including Fanny began to come down. They held the handles together and prepared to set up the simple house.

The electric saw, cutting apparatus, and motor-driven excavator were taken down from the Flying Ship. East Perrin quickly and efficiently removed the motor equipment from the back of the Flying Ship. Although it was not very powerful and could not compare to a Mech’s power furnace because the Flying Ship had its own power furnace, as long as they added some energy batteries, they would be able to modify it into a device for the automatic doors to open and close.

As for building the house, they tore down the things in the Flying Ship that could be used. Next, they used means such as welding screws together and connecting them together. Less than half an hour later, with the help of the four adults and two children, a large triangle tent near the lake was pitched. It had an extremely simple structure that only composed of three large metal boards that were welded together to form a pyramid. Inside, a few pieces of the Flying Ship’s skeleton was fixed in the middle while a little door was cut open on the side. After adding a simple lock and chain clasp, everything was done.

Everyone piled the cotton-padded quilts and other similar items that they had brought with them into the tent. Next, they fixed the corners and remaining bits of the tent into the ground.

“The stones here are so hard!”

While holding the electric drill and painstakingly drilling for a long time, the middle-aged woman furrowed her eyebrows and said, “I’ve changed the drill tip of the electric drill three times but I’ve only managed to make a few holes.”

“Isn’t it better if it’s hard?” Garen nodded and said, “That way, the Predators can’t charge up here easily.”

He grabbed a piece of metal single-handedly and smashed it by the side of the entrance to the passage violently. Next, the male youth who had defied him previously took a tool and welded this metal piece in a fixed position at the edge of the passage.

The entire Flying Ship that was over ten meters long was quickly dismantled to near completion. Only three parts of the Ship’s skeleton remained inside.

Meanwhile, a pointed large metal tent that was seven to eight meters wide was built on the flat ground of the mountaintop. It would be sufficient for the people here to go in and shield themselves from the sun and rain.

The corners of the tent were fixed by melting the metal there. Coupled with the thick palm-sized nails that were nailed to the ground deeply, it was clear that the tent was extremely stable.

“What do we do with this anti-gravity engine?” East Perrin held a dark motor-like little object and walked over.

Garen glanced at this thing.

“We can use it to bear loads. We might be able to use it when we’re transporting items. Put it aside first and make sure to maintain it properly.”

“Speaking of that, we’re almost out of maintenance oil,” said East Perrin helplessly.

Garen nodded to indicate that he understood.

“We’ll talk about this another time. I’ll go look for a somewhere to place my Biochemical Pool.”

East Perrin nodded and turned around before looking for something else to do.

Garen picked up the flesh ball that was once his Biochemical Pool and walked up to another stretch of flat ground on the mountaintop. He crouched down and stuck his palm closely against the ground.

The cool stones were hard to the touch. He moved slightly before the Blue Strands flowed out of his palm swiftly and silently. The strands began to devour the stones on the ground madly.

In theory, the Hellfrost Peacock could devour all things. However, it devoured certain things at slower speeds.

Garen felt it carefully. The Hellfrost Peacock’s rate of devouring the black stones on this mountain was not slow. Moreover, during the devouring process, bouts of strange energy surged through his body faintly. After being refined by the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, this energy was able to fuse with his Living Secret Technique slowly. He was unsure of the exact nature of this energy but knew that it was not part of the Blue Strands. However, it’s purity level seemed very high because it was able to exist independently within the Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

“I don’t know the functions of this thing,” Garen knitted his eyebrows together and relaxed his palm. However, he was surprised when he realized that he had corroded a large deep black hole on the ground after a short amount of time. When he looked down into it from above, it seemed at least one meter deep.

“This is a good way to build a house.” He thought of this point suddenly.

He decided to just press both of his hands close to the ground.

Seemingly countless Blue Strands from his Living Secret Technique flowed into the stone on the ground. It began to consume this stone greedily.

As time passed, a gigantic underground hole gradually formed on the mountain floor. Moreover, by following Garen’s calculations, the strands had accurately built a hollow underground structure that resembled a gigantic underground base. It extended all the way to the edge of the lake and stopped below everyone’s feet.

The hollow underground space was divided into three levels. The top level was where everyone would live and make decisions. The living space was on the right while the meeting room for decision making was on the left. Below them was a large space in the middle that Garen had not decided a use for yet. The space was ten meters high and lowest level was an area that he had left for himself to arrange the Biochemical Pool and do experiments.

After opening a door upstairs, Garen jumped inside at once. The Living Secret Technique’s digging speed amazed Garen himself as well. Within less than an hour, it had dug a huge space underground that was enough to accommodate hundreds of people.

He began to quickly build a flight of stairs and make other arrangements inside. He also made a ventilation channel that led outside to ensure that there was air circulation.

Garen only stopped after being busy for more than an hour. He emerged from the underground again and walked up the flight of stone stairs that he had built. Garen saw that a few people had gathered around the entrance outside, including East Perrin and a few others that were glancing at him suspiciously.

“I used special means to dig a hole. We can probably stay here safely for a while,” Garen shrugged. “Don’t look at me that way. I merely used certain corrosive abilities to excavate a hole quickly. If I had used the tools and brute force, I don’t think I could dig such a good underground space even after a few months.”

“Mr. Garen is simply… He’s simply…” Both of the children were too amazed to speak.

“The means of Energy Machinists are not something that we can imagine.” Malone was the first one to explain. He used this time to inform the others that Garen was an Energy Machinist. This career was extremely mysterious and powerful in the eyes of most people. Currently, Garen had become even more omnipotent to them…

When they realized that he was a mysteriously powerful Energy Machinist, the little group nodded in a slightly relieved manner.

“If you could actually build such a good place, why did you make us dismantle steel boards outside earlier?” quietly muttered East Perrin somewhat bitterly while glaring at Garen.

“Alright, let’s move the things inside now,” Garen clapped his hands. “The task of preparing meals will be handed to you as well. I’m going to arrange the defenses.”

He did not bother with the arrangements that the others would make. He needed to arrange his Biochemical Pool immediately and start nurturing Big Wild Wolves. Otherwise, since there were only a few people here, trouble would definitely ensue if they encountered Predators.

He ran to the bottom level quickly. After setting up a few more ventilation passages only then did Garen give up on the other tasks so that he could dig a hole to position his Biochemical Pool. He threw the ball inside and watched as it expanded into a little circular pond automatically. After that, he followed the steps to handle his materials and mixed the Biochemical Fluid properly before pouring it into a few Predator corpses that had been prepared earlier.

Garen had not expected that the Predators would replace the flesh of the mutated beasts that were used as the Biochemical Pool’s nurturing material. The effects were extraordinarily excellent as well. It seemed as though it was abundant in nutrients.

The pool water quickly turned into a dark red color that resembled dead blood cells. Moreover, the water in the middle of the pool tossed about continuously.

Garen knelt beside the Biochemical Pool. Countless strands of his Energy Machinist Willpower burrowed into the Biochemical Pool before an invisible panel that could be seen by no one else except himself appeared before his eyes.

The current state of the Biochemical Pool was displayed clearly there. This was a control panel that was embedded in the Energy Machine Imprint. Once it had integrated with the Biochemical Pool, he could monitor its state any time.

The model of a black Big Wild Wolf was displayed on the panel.

‘Big Wild Wolf: Speed 1, Defense 0.5, Vitality Restoration 0.5, Destructive Power 1, No Additional Abilities.’

This was the Wild Wolf Imprint template that was usually produced by Energy Machinists that used Biochemical Pools. However, as Garen’s Willpower continuously manipulated and nurtured the characteristics of the Biochemical Pool, some of his Willpower had slowly seeped into the Wild Wolf embryos in the Biochemical Pool.

Slight changes appeared in the data on the panel.

‘Big Wild Wolf: Speed 1+1, Defense 0.5+1, Vitality Restoration 0.5, Destructive Power 1. Additional Effects: Level Two NIS Willpower has been strengthened (Speed +1, Basic Defense +1)’

Chapter 950: Building a New Base 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“This is one of the benefits that I obtained from practicing the Energy Machinist NIS Training Method,” understood Garen clearly. Everything could be seen clearly on this condition panel.

This time, the Biochemical Fluid that had synthesized with the Predator corpse seemed quite good. It was of good quality and was produced in a shorter span of time than earlier. Within less than an hour and a half, the first Big Wild Wolf walked out of the Biochemical Pool and shook the Biochemical Fluid off its body. Thick black fur had started growing on the surface of the Big Wild Wolf’s body at a speed that could be seen by the naked eye.

Garen stroked its neck.

“Go now, follow the passage and go down. Hunt the surrounding Predators that are nearby,” he had modified the control model before transmitting a set of the Predator’s images.

He reached his hand out and placed a Distorted Seed into the Big Wild Wolf’s body gently. He watched it run out of the third level quickly before rushing outside.

The door at the first level was not built yet. The sound of cheering could be heard faintly when the Big Wild Wolf ran out now.

It was clear that the Big Wild Wolf’s combat abilities had received sufficient approval from everyone. They looked at it as if it were a guardian deity.

Garen smiled and examined the next embryo that he was breeding.

He knelt beside it and began to practice the Level Three Energy Machinist grade. He would be able to enter Level Three soon enough and the Big Wild Wolf would become slightly stronger after that. Simultaneously, his own Willpower would be able to perform computing operations that were even more advanced. The shop in the special ability space had assisted him greatly, especially regarding the various knowledge in the Energy Machinist aspect. He did not have a teacher initially and was extremely deficient in this aspect. However, working in the shop was a good opportunity for him to familiarize himself with the world of Energy Machinists.

After feeling the clusters of Inherited Level Mech Pilot Willpower in his body, ripples began stirring in Garen’s mind faintly.

The Seventh Divine Wind General’s attack was too brutal. Moreover, the additional assault from the Biochemist Bamente made it impossible for him to train both his combat abilities and strength until now. He had no way of practicing his combat Training Methods either. Fortunately, he could still rely on the path of an Energy Machinist to advance forward. Otherwise, this reincarnation would be truly wasted.

“I’ll wait until I’ve reached the Advanced Energy Machinist Level. Perhaps I’ll be able to find a way to get rid of the remnants of this Willpower.”

After slowly closing his eyes, Garen allowed the Energy Machine Imprint to produce Big Wild Wolves automatically while he began to carefully compute the Level Three Energy Machinist multidimensional computing module.

*****************

Time passed quickly and in the blink of an eye, Garen and the others had already spent two days on the mountaintop.

Within a couple of days, Garen had already made up for the previous ten Big Wild Wolves completely. All of them were Big Wild Wolves that were strengthened by the Distorted Seeds. Each of them were almost two meters long, possessed robust builds, and looked like little calves. Garen released all of them down the mountain to hunt the surrounding Predators freely. Occasionally, they would bring some Predator corpses back to him to be used as nurturing materials for the Biochemical Pool.

As long as these ten Big Wild Wolves had spacious and circular terrains, they would form a wolf pack that had no problems ambushing little groups of Predators. According to the feedback that Garen had received, this pack of ten wolves had already killed almost twenty Predators within the two days.

Almost all of the wandering Predators near the mountain had been slaughtered. Thus, the Big Bad Wolves had carved out a circle with a diameter of a few hundred meters in the center of the mountain that was completely safe.

This allowed East Perrin and the others on the mountain to finally be completely relieved temporarily. During the past two days, they rushed down the mountain after being informed about this by Garen and collected the materials from their surroundings that were needed to cultivate the Biochemical Fluid. They also dug out some edible plant rhizomes while the old man Malone began to research and test the types of food that the tiny fish inside the little pond liked to eat in preparation to proceed with the breeding.

Meanwhile, Garen went to the special ability space on the side to do his work while constantly training his Willpower processes simultaneously. Finally, he managed to achieve new progress.

At noon on the third day, within the third level of the cave, Garen laid face up on a simple stone bed. Both of his eyes were tightly shut but tiny beads of sweat were pouring out of the skin on his entire body. It seemed as though he was using a tremendous amount of strength and consuming a large amount of it.

In the air in front of Garen’s face that no one else could see, a complicated multidimensional structure that resembled a tower of building blocks was currently suspended there.

This structure resembled a little toy. It was only a few centimeters tall and was hanging in front of Garen’s forehead. The entire little toy was made up of hundreds of tiny wooden building blocks. Symbols and numbers that formed equations regarding mathematical functions were carved on each of these wooden blocks.

As time continued to pass, one of the mathematical wooden blocks at the top moved left of the formation and moved automatically. That answer of the equation on the wooden block had been solved by Garen.

These were the Energy Machinist’s Level Three computing modules. There was more than a single answer for each of these wooden blocks and there would always be various answers. The permutations and combinations that were achieved when different answers were selected would continuously produce various chain reactions.

Garen needed to find the most suitable permutations and combinations for these answers. Next, he would need to arrange them into a brand new broader question that could be solved. After solving the main question, he would finally achieve Level Three.

These were known as double prime factoring that was a task that needed to be done by all Level Three Energy Machinists. They needed to solve the first equation by factoring it and solving hundreds of other difficult equations. Next, they would need to choose a suitable answer to form the second equation. However, this equation would need to be solvable. If it could not be solved, it meant that their combination had failed and they would need to start over again. Even if they were able to solve it, the second question that they had formulated could not be too simple. Despite managing to compute it and become a Level Three Energy Machinist, their potential would be limited if they continued to walk down that path.

In other words, those who took shortcuts and did not challenge themselves would definitely not go far. On the other hand, prodigies who spent their time on unnecessary minor issues would waste a lot of time and mental effort. Therefore, Energy Machinists needed to grasp everything in a balanced manner on their own.

The processes of double prime factoring were extremely terrifying. Through the perspective of an average person, they were simply frightening mathematical questions that were difficult to solve. However, Energy Machinists looked at it as a level for them to ensure that they had a solid foundation at Level Three before leaping to greater heights. If they had set this foundation properly, they would able to reach further distances in the future. Additionally, if they had resorted to tricks to solve the second prime factor with a simple solution, they would probably stop progressing at Level Three as well.

This was because the changes in the Willpower characteristics that were triggered by Level Three were the cornerstones that were used to set up their future Willpower modules.

Energy Machinists constantly used these difficult computing equations as a method to produce a series of complicated but subtle qualitative changes within their Willpower. They would finally be able to accomplish even higher grades of Willpower once they had succeeded. This was the road to advancement for Energy Machinists.

Garen understood this as well. However, he had already factorized the first prime number more than ten times. It would be simpler for him to use his current Prodigy Level computing power to find a simple factor to form the second equation, but he would naturally not desire to go down on that path.

Therefore, he continued calculating it again.

He had already achieved 8 points of Intelligence in his Attribute Pane. This was a terrifying value as it indicated that his Intelligence had synthesized with his computing power to become at least eight times better than the average human. Of course, many abnormal qualitative changes would occur throughout this distance of eight times. It was similar to the martial arts principle which stated that one would not be able to see the other side if the balance was not right.

Currently, he had already reached a level that where he would be considered an intellectual genius among Energy Machinists.

His strong computing power that was increased by three times revolved madly while the sweat on Garen’s forehead increased. The muscles throughout his entire body had started to spasm and twitch while his face turned pale and his breathing quickened gradually.

The movements and speed of the module at his forehead accelerated and changes quickly started to appear.

Suddenly, a cracking noise could be heard.

Garen could only feel as if subtle increases of power had occurred in his brain instantly. It seemed as though some parts had been enlightened at once. Initially, he could not see the places beyond his reach clearly. However, they had become slightly easier to grasp immediately.

He was able to solve the first of a hundred questions rapidly before the second one formed automatically. The second mathematical problem more complicated and harder to understand.

Garen forced his brain to relax. The second mathematical problem was something that he had learned before. It was a function equation that was extremely complicated. Moreover, it was one of the classic difficult mathematical problems in this world.

When the familiar solving process floated past his Willpower, Garen could only hear a soft melodious noise. Immediately, it seemed as though his Willpower had been unlocked. It floated out gently as if it had just burst through the surface of the water from the depths of the ocean at once.

He did it!!!

He let out a long sigh of relief as the unusual condition that caused a heavy burden in his body gradually disappeared.

After resting for awhile, he opened his eyes and sat up. He felt as if his entire body was exhausted. Mentally, he really, really wanted to sleep.

“Being able to automatically form stereotypically difficult questions like that mean that I can surpass Level Three Energy Machinist equations of mid-range to upper-level difficulties. The possibility of discovering an exceptional Energy Machinist is only one in a hundred. Moreover, they would need to spend a few months doing this while I only needed a few days…”

He glanced at the value of his Intelligence Points.

He shockingly discovered that his Intelligence had increased again from 8.0 to 8.1 this time. It was clear that this minor progress had trained his brain as well.

“If Energy Machinists trained their brains like this daily, it will definitely become energy to continuously increase their computing power for a certain period of time. It reached an abnormal degree progressively… The person that invented Energy Machinist Training Methods is truly terrifying…” Garen sighed.

(Unfortunately, it would be perfect if I still had sufficient Potential Points. I only have 32 Potential Points left now. After reaching 8 Intelligence Points, I would still need another 60 Points if I wanted to increase it by one more level. My gains could not make up for my losses even if I found another Staff of Absolute Yin) thought Garen.

Although he was slightly regretful that his Potential Points could only help him in limited amounts, Garen was not completely remorseful over this fact because he knew that he could not rely on Potential Points forever. Once he became too dependent on this thing, would he collapse completely after encountering a minor hitch in the future?

Therefore, Garen had become conscious of this issue long ago. Many times, he would intentionally refrain from relying on Potential Points to strengthen himself. Instead, he would rely more heavily on the knowledge that he gained from different worlds as strength and use them as his final trump cards.

This applied to his current self as well. The thing that helped him the most was no longer merely Potential Points, as he had the Living Secret Technique and Hellfrost Peacock Technique as well now.

The Distorted Seeds could increase a living creature’s physical fitness by three times. This gave him a sturdy foundation while living in troubled times.

(Long periods of grinding lie ahead after becoming Level Three Energy Machinists. The difficult aspect of Level Four Energy Machinists is the triple prime factoring. Since there’s an additional level in comparison to Level Three, it becomes much harder. Without an overall outlook and computing powers that are strong enough, I don’t even have to think of advancing even more) Garen had finally understood.

Level Four Energy Machinists were the true divide between Lower and Middle-Level Energy Machinists. Level Four Energy Machinists could possess two Energy Machine Imprints and could create two cannon fodder creatures and two elite modified creatures.

He had also discovered through Mincar that Level Four Energy Machinists also served as great support levels for many renowned workshops and the backbones of major business alliances. In more current and popular terms, this was similar to the difference between college students and professors within a college setting. Within a factory, they would be positioned about the workers at the bottom level. They would be in charge of the skills that would be used by the individuals in the lower levels that served as the nucleus and framework of the organization. Moreover, there were a group of people in a level that no organization could lack.

They were the white-collar workers that possessed some power within the special ability spaces throughout the entire Energy Machinist society.

“But since I want to enter Level Four, it’ll probably take at least half a year more.” Garen tried to calculate his progress rate. Level Four would require him to form modules and answer them after that. Therefore, he would need to spend an extremely long time doing that. Half a year was too long. It would be a waste for him to merely spend such an extended period of time purely computing in one place. It would be more beneficial if he were to try solving that other technique instead.

Garen could solve the L-units Skills that he used to control the upper limits of the quantities of Big Wild Wolves.

According to the materials and skills that he currently possessed for Resonation, these were accumulated from the developments of a civilization in the world. They had integrated with the composition of the L-units and definitely possessed a probability of being implemented.

Chapter 951: Production Thread 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After becoming a Level Three Machinist, Garen stood up from his bed, wishing to solve the upper limits of controlling the Big Wild Wolf. In order to do this, he first had to produce a Production Threads for the chips. Garen had already chosen a type of plant for the Resonation aspect, which could still produce pheromones even after being separated. This could be used as the foundation code for communication.

Garen found a towel to wipe the sweat off his body before heading up to the third floor. He reached the second floor, which was where East Perrin and a few other females were temporarily living in. They had their own rooms at the corner of the second floor, just like Garen. They had used the doors from the flying ship as their doors, which was a perfect fit after Garen cutting it down to the proper size.

East Perrin and the only small girl were sitting together, enjoying their meal. Both of them seemed to be whispering about something.

Garen walked up to them, seeing them acting very friendly with each other as they whispered into each other’s ears.

His footsteps seemed to have shocked the young girl as she quickly rushed to the other side of the room to sit down. She lowered her blushed face as she didn’t dare to look at Garen.

East Perrin was standing there trying to hold off her laughter.

“What are you laughing at? What are you guys whispering about?” Garen had never treated the women in the radiation belt as women as the people here were very agile and brave. The women here were on par with the men and they could do anything the men could.

“We are talking about you,” East Perrin shook her head. “I can’t help it. This little girl loves you but she doesn’t dare to confess her feeling towards you. Hence, she can only whisper it to me,” she spoke out loudly in broad daylight.

Ah!

The little girl by the side screamed as she covered her face and ran away.

Garen was speechless and even more so for East Perrin.

“She says she wants to give away her virginity to you. Are you interested in it?” East Perrin looked at Garen boldly. Her expression was very honest but her gaze was extremely mischievous.

“Alright now is not the time to talk nonsense. Come with me,” Garen said calmly.

“To where?”

“To find a Production Thread that could produce the chips. Do you know where to find one?” Garen asked.

“Production Thread?” East Perrin rubbed her chin. “Actually, I do know where to find one. However, it is slightly far from here. Since we’re going out, we should find some washable clothes for everyone,” she pulled her shirt down.

Her tight gray shirt was ragged. Since she wasn’t wearing a bra, her raw body was streamlined across the shirt with two pokies protruding out of the shirt without any cover.

“What do you think? Feel like fucking me, right?” East Perrin looked at Garen teasingly.

“You better do your work!” Garen rolled his eyes as he reached out his hands and grabbed her breast.

“Hey, that’s painful!”

East Perrin avoided him helplessly.

The relationship between a male and female in the radiation belt was pretty direct. If one had an interest, they could directly go into their room and they could start mating immediately if the opposing party did not reject the offer. It’s totally fine for them to give birth without any marriage or tedious etiquette. The radiation people did not know what their life-span was, hence their motto in life was to enjoy life while it lasted. For a person such as East Perrin, who was still a virgin at such an age was considered extremely rare.

It’s not that Garen wasn’t interested in her. Afterall, there were urges he as a man could not hold back. However, he would lose his sex drive because he would recall Celine every time he tried to make his move. Celine might still be bearing the stress that he was supposed to bear or was trying her best to protect his family. How could he have forgotten such a favor?

“Alright, get ready to move out,” Garen said coldly.

“Yes, boss!” East Perrin placed her tongue out and intentionally walked to her room in front of Garen while sticking out her butt.

***************

In the gray field, the rebel army was holding banners while a team of at least a dozen people moving forward slowly.

Although this group of people were all in gray-black attires, they looked like they were stained with blood as if they had just lost a war.

The one who walked at the front was a young man with a black headscarf on his head. He looked very persevere but his eyes showed a sign of gentleness. His soft and gentle black hair would move about as wind blew across his face.

There was also a gentle and graceful girl in a veil walking beside him. The duo led the team while two muscular men carried the flags behind them.

“Hurry! Everyone, please hold out a bit longer! We’re reaching the stronghold soon!” the man in black headscarf shouted.

“Clint, are you sure you won’t attract the predators while you simply shout out?” The muscular man carrying the flag looked at the man in the black headscarf hopelessly.

“Trust me on this,” Clint turned his head around and revealed his white teeth as he smiled. “As a man, this is my seventh sense!”

What he relied on was not his own intuition but Red Moon’s scanning device on his body.

“Alright, I’ll believe you once more since you’ve rarely gotten it wrong,” the muscular man shrugged helplessly.

“Ouch!”

One of the team members shouted out of the blue as he crouched down and covered his leg.

The veiled girl at the front of the team immediately went to check on him.

“You’ve been stung by a scorpion. You’ll be fine.”

The man nodded as he gritted his teeth.

The girl used her nails to cut open the man’s swollen area, causing a huge amount of viscous blood spilling out from the wound to the field nearby. Then, the girl’s finger glowed green. It shone onto the wound and the recovery was sped up multiple time, healing it in no time.

Within ten seconds, the wound was fully healed.

“No matter how many times I witness it, your Willpower is definitely incredible Lon!” Clint praised. “If it weren’t for you, we’d be in big trouble.”

“It is my responsibility,” Baylon smiled. “I wonder where brother had gone to.”

One could see that she missed him just by looking into her beautiful eyes.

“I wonder too. We heard the news that he had been surrounded and killed when we entered the region and couldn’t believe our ears. If Red Moon didn’t inform us that he’s still alive, I would think that he is already dead!” Clint nodded.

They had led a life of freedom in the underground rebel army for the past two years. There were no laws and very little restrains there. Since they had enough strength, they stood firm with their own feet under the guidance of the person who had saved their lives, becoming one of the main forces in the underground rebel army. Clint had reached level three in his Nine Mega Cannon Training Method and possessed the strength similar to a top-notch Level Five Pilot. Although he was still no match to the Inherited Level powerhouses, his strength was on par with a New-Moon Level Resonance Pilot.

Due to special circumstances, they were not able to unleash their true Willpower potential without operating a Mech. However, if they were able to get their hands on a Mech, they would be nothing but powerful. Fairy was a person who was considered their trump card in the rebel army.

On the other hand, Baylon had been stuck at Level Two after trying to mimic her brother Nonosiva’s fighting style. According to Redmoon, she had damaged her root as she tried to breakthrough into Level Two without sufficient foundation. Although she was promoted, it would be hard for her to increase further without proper treatment of her damaged root.

Hence, Baylon was still stuck at Level Two which was about as strong as a typical Level Four Pilot.

Both of them managed to make a lot of new friends underground but they still couldn’t find Nonosiva’s location. After being saved by Nonosiva once, Clint was very grateful and respectful towards Baylon’s brother. Recalling his overwhelming strength back then, he felt that he was out of his league even to this date.

No matter how many times Red Moon had told him that he was no longer weaker than Nonosiva when he’s operating a Mech, Clint still strongly felt that he would still lose to him if they were to fight.

“If Nono big brother is still around, I wonder what kind of realm his strength would have reached…” Clint said emotionally.

“Those Fila, Van Doe and the Seventh Divine Wind General are too cruel! I will definitely avenge brother someday!” Baylon clenched her fist as she muttered.

“Then you better start working hard,” a lazy voice flashed across both of their heads. It was Red Moon’s. “You should abandon that trickster, the sooner the better. I have already told you guys many times that you were not saved by him but Nonosiva but you guys always put a deaf ear on me. It’s unfortunate that we cannot get in touch with him due to the large disruption or else we would have known the truth by now.”

“He was there on the scene, how could it not be him?” Nonosiva may have came beforehand but I believe uncle is still the one who saved us,” Clint said hopelessly. “Red Moon, I will be angry if you say any further. Uncle is our lifesaver. Even if he didn’t save us back then, he had helped us out so many times during these times. Ever since my sister passed away, he has been my only family so could you please not slander him?”

“You idiot! I don’t even know how to scold you now. You even helped him count his money when he sold you guys off,” Red Moon said hopelessly. “Fine whatever. Fortunately, Lon is getting good at healing people. If not for Lon the last few times, you would have died from that old hag Squid.”

“Nothing I can do about it… Squid is an Inherited Level and I’m no match for him…” Clint scratched his head as he said honestly.

“Let’s move on quickly or else we won’t be able to reach the Ancient Ruins before the sky turns dark,” Baylon said softly.

“Fine, let’s hurry up. The place we’re currently heading, the Eighth Ancient Ruin, has a very high intensity of radiation. We will be relying on Lon if anybody’s radiation sickness worsens,” Clint said softly.

“Sure no problem,” Baylon nodded.

She looked ahead with a slight sense of melancholy.

Brother… Where are you? I now possess the ability to heal the residual Willpower of an Inherited Level Pilot, which meant that I now have what it takes to heal your injury. If you’re still alive, I prayed to God that Lord Red Moon would be able to contact you…

*************

On the grey field, three black dots were sprinting swiftly in it. They were three giant wolves which bodies spanned about two meters long. Its bodies were covered in black fur and were carrying two men and a girl in ragged clothes on their back.

“The Seventh Ancient Ruins? Someone dared to go there even though it’s an ancient ruin?” Garen was riding on the giant wolf firmly as he turned his head to the left and spoke to East Perrin.

“Yes. In this vicinity of the radiation belt, if there is any place to search for a Production Thread which was used to produce the Chip Element, then the only possible place is the Seventh Ancient Ruins. Those garbage mountains wouldn’t even have these kinds of stuff and would only have some parts at most. On the other hand, The radiation intensity on the Seventh Ancient Ruins was lower than the other year. Although it was still three times more intense than outside, it was nothing compared to the other Ancient Ruins,” East Perrin nodded as she replied.

“When we reach there, Fanny and I will enter the ruin and you’ll be waiting for us outside,” Garen nodded. “Afterall, the amount of radiation we can resist is much higher than you.”

“Alright, I will hide outside while waiting for you two. If I encounter a large scale attack from the predators, I will send out the signal,” East Perrin knew that she would not be useful inside and would only cause trouble if she were to do so. Hence, she didn’t press onto the issue further.

Chapter 952: Production Thread 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The three giant wolves ran for multiple hours before the white abandoned stone structures appeared on the horizon. Some of the structures had cylindrical column and some walls were already broken. There was also a lot of toy-like rubbish that was spread across the floor. The ruin looked extremely old.

They eventually entered the inner regions of the ancient ruins as the wolves kept pressing on.

Surrounding that area, abandoned building structures became more and more as they entered.

“Be careful. This ancient ruin is different from the other ruins. Rumor has it that people often encounter a frightening scene. Those who do not encounter it would return safely while those who encounter the frightening scene had all disappeared and they never returned.” East Perrin stopped in his tracks as the intensity of the radiation would be unbearable for him if he were to keep moving forward.

“Relax. We will come out the moment we find the Production Thread that can be used to create the Chip Element. We just need to get our hands on the main item, the Control Terminal and the remaining parts of the Production Thread can be sourced elsewhere. There are many replacement parts that can produce the same precision,” Fanny smiled as he comforted, “wait for our good news here.”

“Yes, it’s fine. Don’t worry about us and wait for our news back home,” Garen nodded as well.

“Alright then.” East Perrin walked towards one of the broken walls and squatted down as he got down from the wolf’s back. “I will hide here while I wait for the two of you. Come back soon.”

Garen and Fanny gave an okay gesture with their hands as they rode the wolves and entered deeper into the Seventh Ancient Ruins.

The entire Seventh Ancient Ruins was like an abandoned mechanical factory. Some areas looked like a broken grand theater that had not been used for a long time. The exquisitely decorated stage and machines in the area were all broken.

The black machining tools, cutting platform, and heavy-duty roller were neatly arranged just beside the grand theater. It looked extremely strange as if someone had done some performance with the heavy duty roller.

Frankly speaking, who would really use a heavy-duty roller as a part of their performance?

Garen and Fanny walked passed a Ferris wheel. Instead of having seats on the red Ferris wheel, there were sharp blades and the Ferris wheel would squeak about as the wind blew gently.

Both of them looked around as they searched for the much-needed machining tool. The current radiation they were experiencing was thrice the amount compared to outside. Garen had started releasing his Cold Radiation to cancel off to restrain the exposure from the high-intensity radiation. Fanny showered himself within the Cold Radiation and wasn’t affected by it at all. This was all thanks to the modified Distorted Seed.

Wa wa wa…

Suddenly, a child-like cry could be heard from their side.

Growl… The giant wolves stopped their footsteps and started to growl.

Garen and Fanny looked around and saw a few alarm clocks with limbs flying in midair, running away from them, though they weren’t too far away. They then disappeared, as if they were like some meddling kids fooling around.

Beep beep beep… Click click…

A sudden noise came from the other side as a few gears with butterfly wings flew past them.

“What is this!” Garen immediately picked up a pebble and threw it at one of the gears. The palm-sized gear was hit straight at the center with great precision.

The pebble pierced through the gear and surprisingly, blood started bleeding out from the center of the gear, just like a human would. It then dropped to the ground and disappeared the moment it touched the ground. The remaining gear butterflies seemed to be shocked by the event as they flew about randomly until they gradually vanished.

Then, an innocent laughter of a child filled the entire area.

“Let’s hurry up. Something strange is going on here.” Garen felt that the soul of the Nine Headed Dragon deep within him was on guard. His face turned serious. He knew that if something could threaten the Nine Headed Dragon, it was definitely something dangerous.

“Alright,” Fanny felt something strange going on as well.

Both of them ushered the giant wolves to run inside while they kept looking around for the Production Thread they wanted.

The black factory equipment, white abandoned buildings, and the red stages were everywhere. Occasionally, the Ferris wheel and wooden carriage were stuck in between them.

Lalala… Lalala… Suddenly, towards the front-left side, a rectangular silver machining tool with four of its limbs was skipping about while humming a song.

“What the hell! I just saw a machining tool taking a stroll!” Fanny was speechless as he stared at the bloated machining tool twitching its stomach about. It was walking around happily.

“What’s troublesome is that thing on it.” Garen didn’t pay attention to the strange machining tool but rather the brown bear puppet on it.

The small bear puppet looked very cute with its two black eyes, white mouth, and nose. Its limbs were holding onto the machining tools. Suddenly, as if it had noticed their presence, it turned its head around. Its lips then arched upwards, revealing a very cute smile.

Suddenly, its lips cracked open and the bear’s mouth was extended to its ears! It revealed a sinister smile, as well as its sharp fangs.

“F*ck me! What is that thing!?” Fanny’s jaw dropped as he saw the bear puppet pounced towards them with its wide mouth open. As that happened, its body grew bigger and bigger.

The inside of its mouth was blood red and it kept giving off a stench that no word could describe. Its mouth expanded quickly from the size of a palm to a meter, two meters, three meters, and five meters wide before it pounced towards them!

By the time it was in front of them, that mouth was already six meters wide!

Roar!

A deep and fierce growl came from Garen in which this shapeless roar stunned the bear.

Poof!

The bear immediately turned around and fled like a deflating balloon as it flew far away. Within seconds, it had disappeared from their sight.

They regained their composure after that.

Fanny was drench in cold sweat and he didn’t even have the intention to evade it at all! He knew that he was in danger but he had no intention of evading or attacking. All he did was stare at the bloody big mouth that was coming towards them.

“I’ve… seen a ghost!” He muttered.

Garen’s face was gloomy as well.

It was an evil force that involved the soul, the dream world, illusions, and a lot of other stuff. All these while he had thought that the force didn’t discriminate evil or justice but used the nature of the user. However, when he sensed the aura of the little bear, he finally understood what a real evil force was!

“Bring that machining tool along and we’re leaving!” He said.

By the time Fanny looked at that tool again, it had already turned back to normal, standing firmly on the ground. He didn’t even know how he came out alive from that incident.

The tool no longer had long legs, a bear puppet or even taking a stroll on its own. Fanny felt that what he just saw was just an illusion.

“Did I just witness an illusion?” He whispered.

“If you think that it is an illusion, then it is. If you think that is real, then it shall be real,” Garen replied coldly. Since he had some knowledge of the Witch’s aspect of the Dream World and its system, he knew how profound the system was. The damage done in the Dream World would often leave its mark in the Material World as well.

The duo brought the giant wolves along to the machining tool to take off the control terminal and a few high precision main parts. They then put them into the parcels that they brought along.

“Let’s leave immediately!” Garen didn’t want to stay here any longer before the evil aura started to gather once more. It was formless and seemed to be a pure illusion of evil energy. Inside it was a combination of pain, evil thoughts, jealousy, tyranny, innocence, and cuteness clustered together into an entity.

Both of them immediately left the area with the main parts of the machining tools.

A few palm-sized soybeans with nose, eyes, and mouth started singing as it rolled beside them, floating in the air.

Choo choo! Choo choo! Choo choo choo choo!

It mimicked the noise of a train as they kept on rolling.

“F*ck off!” Fanny waved his hands as he felt that the sound was making him dizzy.

However, he couldn’t touch these soybeans with his hands.

Then, the gears with butterfly wings started to appear once more as it kept flying around and above their heads.

“Hurry!” Garen felt that that evil energy was getting stronger. If not for the consciousness of the Nine Headed Dragon that was threatening them, they might have already been swallowed by this energy.

He wouldn’t be able last long as the consciousness of the Nine Headed Dragon wasn’t something he could control at will unless he had mastered his Secret Technique.

The duo ran for their lives as they followed the path they came from.

As they ran, the ground started to move, causing them and the wolves to not be able to stand firmly.

“It’s trying to… stop us… from leaving…” Garen turned his head around and his voice seemed to have slowed down, making it sound deeper and slower just like a movie being played in slow motion.

“Run…” Fanny realized his voice became very slow and deep as he shouted.

Moreover, Fanny’s ears, nose, and eyes started bleeding. Red blood slowly flowed down his cheeks.

He wiped off the blood out of fear. As he tried to increase his pace, the giant wolf underneath him started to behave strangely. It kneeled down and refused to run any further.

“Run!” Suddenly a powerful force pulled along his collar and threw him out.

Fanny could only feel that the sky was spinning around as he was thrown very far away. The next thing he felt was a heavy crash onto the field outside of the Ancient Ruins.

Boom!

Ouch… As he regained his consciousness, he saw Garen flying out behind him and started running once more the moment he got to his feet.

Two giant wolves were left behind. They were instantly swallowed by the invisible force and they vanished.

“Run!” Garen shouted as they, including East Perrin who was hiding, started running away from the Seventh Ancient Ruins.

Chapter 953: Accumulation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What is that thing!?” Fanny kept wiping off the blood flowing out from his face — it was very sticky. He didn’t feel any pain and experience but only numbness as if her face was injected with a dose of anesthetic.

The three of them walked back through the path they came from. Since they had lost two giant wolves, they had no choice but to head back slowly.

“I don’t know.” Garen shook his head. “Do you guys believe in the soul?” He questioned back.

Fanny frowned as he pondered.

“Lord Garen, are you trying to say that thing is a soul?”

“Not just any soul. That was an accumulation of polluted negative energy. You can view it as a polluted spiritual field.” Garen used the world’s system as an analogy to explain.

“That thing is a cluster of different content and isn’t something that can be handled with an average way.”

“What did you guys encounter?” East Perrin was curious as she listened from the sideline. She was stunned too when she saw that Fanny’s face was covered with blood.

“Something extremely strange. I will tell you everything once we get back.” Fanny shook his head and he didn’t want to go back in there for the rest of her life.

“Now that we have everything, we need to go back as soon as possible. We may not outrun those Predators if we were to encounter them,” Garen said casually. From the soul that he had encountered in the Ancient Ruins, he understood that even though this world was very technologically advanced, it would still be connected to the realm of soul once it had reached its limits. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be able to explain the phenomenon inside the ancient ruins.

However, from the encounter, he could sense that the Seventh Ancient Ruins contained something strange that no one knew about. This strange being was able to involve itself in the realm of the soul as it was able to activate the consciousness of the Nine Headed Dragon. If the strongest man in this world had its way around the soul, he would have to be extremely careful in the future, and not rely heavily on the idea of him being able to reincarnate again and again without fear. If he were to encounter a powerhouse who had knowledge in souls, he would be in danger as he would be defenseless while reincarnating. If that were the case, he might have permanently lost his life.

“Okay let’s quicken our pace and head back home.” Garen increased his pace as he led the way.

The other two followed along behind. Frankly speaking, East Perrin felt a sense of security ever since Garen became a leader. She, who had never relied on someone felt very much at ease.

She let out a sigh of relief upon realizing that she was no longer the leader who had to independently lead Leo City.

“Perhaps it’s better to rely on someone sometimes,” East Perrin blushed as she looked at Garen’s back.

The trio then quickly journeyed their way back home.

Suddenly, Garen stopped moving and he looked far into the horizon. There was a line of black dots at the other end of the field.

“They’re human. Unsure which team it is,” He said softly.

“Do you want to get in contact with them?” East Perrin lowered down her voice.

Garen pondered for a moment and eventually shook his head.

“In this current chaotic situation, we wouldn’t know what their intention is, right? Whatever, it’s fine. We are relatively safe even on our own. At the moment, everyone can be considered as the enemy since we’re all in the same situation.”

“Indeed. The radiation belt has always been chaotic. There are radiation people who eat their own kind to survive in this harsh environment,” Fanny agreed, “it seems like they’re here for the ancient ruins as well. With their team of this scale, they’re definitely stronger than us.”

“True. If you don’t have the strength, you don’t have the qualification to speak up or make demands,” East Perrin nodded in agreement as well.

“Let’s go.” Garen turned around and left as the other two followed along.

He didn’t realize that the Nameless Forbidden Willpower inside him was pulsating slightly as Red Moon’s Willpower was trying to contact him. However, the pulsation was undetectable under the restriction of the Inherited Level of the Seventh Wind General.

The team of three people and a wolf walked further. Soon, they disappeared from the horizon of the field.

About a kilometer away from them, Clint put away his binoculars as he stood on the field.

“Looks like a team of three people and a wolf. What a strange combination.”

“What’s so strange about it? You can encounter all sorts of strange combinations in this field,” Red Moon said boringly. He seemed to have sensed the slight pulse of his Willpower. However, it was too weak to the point that he thought he had mistaken it for something else.

“Let’s go and look for that thing we want,” Baylon urged, “it will get dark if we don’t hurry up.”

“Alright. The Seventh Ancient Ruin is just up ahead. The sky is turning dark so everyone, hurry up!” Clint shouted as he waved his hand.

“Oh!”

The team behind him started cheering. They were all convinced that he was a good leader despite his young age. It wasn’t just his sincerity, but every time there was a dangerous situation, he would be the first one to fight back with his overwhelming strength.

It’s practically impossible to find a person with such personality in the radiation belt.

Clint and Baylon lead the team as they headed towards the Seventh Ancient Ruins.

The invisible world’s force field surrounding the two of them, which Garen called it the Force of Cause and Effect, was becoming more and more concentrated.

As they closed their distance, the evil force inside the Seventh Ancient Ruins became stronger. If someone could see this energy, then they would see a dark cloud engulfing the entire Seventh Ancient Ruins, reaching its hand out towards Clint and his people.

No one knew that they were heading towards the death’s doorstep on this journey. That place was also where Clint and Baylon would be facing death!

If Garen could analyze the information on the Force of Cause and Effect on himself, he would know that the Seventh Ancient Ruins would be one of the places where Clint and his team were fated to die. He was just merely testing the water for the future main character.

High risk came with a high reward; this was the never changing truth. If he was able to successfully escape from death, then the reward and growth he would obtain from this place would be tremendous.

The Force of Cause and Effect had far surpassed Garen’s expectation in this world as it was hinted that it had the power to control fate itself. Compared to the world Garen had lived in, it was much stronger than the rest.

*****************

As they returned back to the black stone mountains, Garen immediately started to work on finishing the Production Thread. As a mechanical expert, East Perrin helped out as well while the others helped out in improving the lifestyle and setting up all kinds of safety features.

Malone’s experiment in farming the edible small fishes was showing some results. However, due to the high intensity radiation on the mountain, he started coughing recently. If he wasn’t careful, he would contract a flu.

However, everyone was experiencing the same thing. Although the top of the mountain was very safe, the radiation was too intense, causing everyone’s physique to drop.

As time passed, Garen started working under Mincar in the Special Ability Space while he kept fixing the chip’s Production Thread. However, a new problem surfaced. In order to produce the chip, he needed a laptop, which could be replaced with the old quantum computer model on the Flying Ship. However, the chip also required Gui Mineral, aluminum, and copper. Since he didn’t have the blueprint of the chip, it was impossible for Garen to design the control chip’s circuit on his own as he wasn’t an expert in this.

Fortunately, old man Mincar knew where to obtain the rare earth mineral, Gui Mineral. The aluminum and copper could be obtained by processing the materials used by the Flying Ship. Unfortunately, it would be slightly troublesome to obtain them as they did not have any instrument in extracting these materials. Hence, they were not able to obtain those of good quality.

“I’ve heard of a chip that was completely built on organic materials instead of metals. It uses bioelectricity to process the computation. Moreover, the miniature computer to create the chip is smaller than a hair’s width.” After understanding Garen’s obstacle, he came up with a good idea.

“Living Chip?” Garen reacted immediately, “Has someone created such an item before?”

“Of course. We don’t need to fully create a Living Chip. What I mean is that since they are able to create a chip based on different parts of a living being, isn’t it the same if we use the organic material to replace the metal resources that we lack?” Mincar smiled.

Garen was stunned. He then nodded after pondering for some time.

“Hmm. It’s worth a try.”

His Energy Machine Imprint was the best high-performance computer and the organic materials were abundant natural resources as well. A living being was just nature’s way to store all of the organic materials in one place.

He was able to manufacture the core of the chip with the Production Thread. After throwing it into the Biochemical Pool and improvising it with the Energy Machine Imprint, he was able to combine everything together with organic materials of different properties.

After experimenting for three days, Garen had finally invented a semi-biological chip.

*************

“Now that the chip has been resolved, the next step is to combining everything to create the Core Terminal!” Garen was very happy. If he could finish building the core, he would solve the problem of controlling the giant wolves in certain amounts.

He came out from the basement with a messy hair only to see East Perrin and the others were not around. The second floor was eerily quiet; not a noise could be heard.

“East Perrin!” He frowned as he shouted.

There was no response.

Slam.

Suddenly, a gentle knock was heard from the room at the far end.

Garen had been in the basement for two days straight and had no clue to what had happened outside.

He immediately rushed to that room. He tried to open it but it seemed to be locked from the inside.

He pointed at the keyhole with his finger as a blue line shot out, melting it into a circular hole.

Click, the metal door was opened.

However, something seemed to be preventing the door from opening.

Garen used some force to push open the door.

Boom.

A hot naked woman’s body was pushed away from the door.

It was East Perrin. She seemed to be in the middle of a shower and even had a bowl of water in the middle of the room. There even was white foams on her body covering her breast and private part.

“Uhh… Uhh…” East Perrin’s face turned pale and didn’t know how to react.

Chapter 954: Accumulation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“How are you!” Garen was stunned and instantly crouched down to hold onto her body. Her pulse was beating rapidly; her body was emitting a strong radiation contamination.

“Radiation…” She struggled to let out a weak voice.

Garen blanked out for a bit before turning towards her.

“Can you endure such a high radiation? I actually expected this day to come, but I didn’t expect it to be this soon. Be careful! I will begin now.”

East Perrin nodded her head. She knew that no matter what happened, she would be reformed by Garen and became just like Fanny. Her life was in Garen’s hands. Once the mutation broke out, she would lose herself entirely, but how much worse could this be compared to before? Like it or not, Garen would be the leader. There wasn’t a single person who would not follow every single one of his commands. Without him, they would have been dead long ago.

Garen held his hand out and gently pressed it onto East Perrin’s left breast. With a blue, soundless fleeting flash, it ended. She did not even feel a thing.

The Distorted Seed Parasitism swiftly entered the heart and became one whole with the myocardium straight away.

Within seconds, East Perrin’s breathing slowed down, her heartbeat rate decreased rapidly. A vast amount of Cold Radiation radiated from her heart, which was taken as the center and towards every part of her body, swallowing the vicious radiation virus.

“Well… Good.” Just approximately ten seconds and she could speak already, “There’s still Sinno and the others. They might not be able to hold on much longer.”

“Alright, I’ll go straight away!” Garen nodded, “This move was supposed to be the last resort. I did not expect to use it this early.”

“Whether we’re controlled or not, you’re our leader anyway. So what’s the difference before and after the reformation?” East Perrin sat up, not bothered by the fact that Garen could see her naked upper body. “Go. We have long entrusted our fate to you.”

Garen sighed and stood up. East Perrin did save him once back then. However, he had a different attitude towards this girl and felt things differently when it came to her, just as if she was another Celine.

He could feel the heat of East Perrin’s gaze on him. Turning around to avoid her gaze, he left the bedroom to get out of this place.

After stopping by a few other bedrooms, sure enough, Fanny was sound asleep, drooling everywhere while the others were showing various degrees of symptoms of the radiation disease that was worsening by the second.

Garen gave them the choice, the decision to reform.

Not surprisingly, nobody objected. During times like these, even the most selfish young men were filled with gratitude towards Garen.

Everyone had their hearts focused on Garen.

Batch after batch of Distorted Seeds, the radiation disease was finally wiped out. However, everyone had become the host of the Distorted Seed Parasitism including the two children. As long as they do not trigger the Distorted Seed, nothing would go wrong. Besides the ordinary, their immune system and physique were enhanced three times. Strong flakes of resistance appeared and their Willpower increased by three times as well. They all had become terrifying monsters who could just lose their sanity and go on a killing spree at any moment.

Garen had warned each and every one of them on the ways to activate the Distorted Seed. It was very simple — just break down into utter despair and anger, then they would automatically activate the mutation and become killing machines. The other method was for Garen to activate the Distorted Seed’s mutation manually.

Once the hidden problem was solved, the people under the mountains returned to their ordinary lives. Malone stopped coughing and was back to rearing fishes all day. Under Garen’s command, a few lucky Big Wild Wolves brought back a mutated creature which was a type similar to sheep but had two heads instead. This was a mutation caused by the radiation. The two-headed sheep had stout horns, strong impact force when it ran, and an astonishing combat force. It managed to injure three Big Wild Wolves before it was brought back dead.

This enormous sheep was at least two hundred kilos heavy. Both of the children helped to skin it and air-dried a part of its meat so that it could be made into dried meat. Whereas the other part was given to Garen who used his Cold Radiation to freeze it before storing it temporarily. It was to be eaten in the future.

Yet, if it was before the reformation, it would have been worrisome to feed normal people with food which had undergone the Cold Radiation. However, they were now under Parasitism so it did not matter anymore. The Cold Radiation would actually benefit the hosts of Parasitism, causing them to feel more comfortable as if they had existed in an environment of their optimal temperature and humidity.

The Resonation Core Control that Garen made according to the control chip was completed by imitating the Crystal Derivator. Using condensed biological rubber, he made a transparent Rubber Ball Controller that seemed like a crystal ball. He named it The Black Sky to commemorate the Totem World’s contribution towards the technical core of The Black Sky Research Organization.

********************

East Perrin carefully marked a scratch on the wall. With this, she had kept track of how long they had been in the summit.

“This is our twelfth day here.”

In the basement, everyone was gathered there to listen to East Perrin speak, and that included Garen.

East Perrin was making a summary report of all aspects in this duration of time.

“After twelve days, our food supply should still be able to last us for another month. Whether if it’s the frozen water which was made by Mr Garen beforehand or distilled water from the lake, we have sufficient water,” She paused, “our biggest problem right now is that we are running out of energy batteries!”

“This is a problem I’ve been worrying about since earlier on as we didn’t bring much energy batteries in the first place. The flying ship was stored with too many essential supplies, so we had no choice but to cut down our burden by reducing the energy batteries on board. Having such a problem now is unavoidable.” Malone nodded in agreement in his seat.

“So how are we going to solve this problem? After our discussion, all of you can cut down on your electrical appliances and use just a few of the battery collectors to charge your energy batteries. However, this is just a temporary solution as energy batteries have their life expectancies — a limited number of charges. Moreover, we’ve been using second-hand batteries which won’t even last long. If going to the wasteland is still a choice, we’d still have a chance. There are so many abandoned energy batteries there, I’m sure we can find something decent and replaceable, but we don’t even have this path anymore. So, what do we do?”

“We did meet a few other groups earlier on. Is it possible to trade with them?” Fanny frowned, “Maybe search for the other groups that are gathering defense points and have a trade?”

“That would be hard, but still a plan,” Garen nodded.

“What about inside the ancient ruins?” Sinno asked in a hushed tone.

“Don’t bring up that hell of a place. Even the thought of it still gives me chills. If it’s just a mutated monster standing in front of me, I can still face it. But that creature didn’t know when to land a blow and it only ran! It was hell!”

“That bad?” Sinno asked in disbelief.

“You weren’t there so you wouldn’t know,” Fanny did not want to think about it anymore.

“There’s still one other way, in which that would also be our only last way,” East Perrin said lightly, “the Underground Rebel Army has not only the complete energy batteries’ Production Thread but an extremely powerful force. However, those people are exceptionally ferocious and their purpose is to fight against the domain. Also, not forgetting that they looked down on us radioactive people in this area. I’ve been there once. People like us are deemed as low-grade people. It was horrible. So after being there the first time, I never wanted to go back again.”

“Actually, there are some of the Rebel Army who are the nicer ones,” Malone spoke softly, “but the ratio is too darn small. This probably won’t work.”

“Seems like everyone is out of ideas…” Garen smiled lightly. “So let me add something right here. I may need a large amount of different biochemical fluid these days so I would need everyone’s help to come, help me harvest and store them.”

“You didn’t have to say that, we actually noticed it already. While we were out, we observed the distribution of plants and insects that you need. Malone has already transplanted some over here, on the summit,” East Perrin answered with a smile.

“Huh? Transplant?” Garen paused.

“Yeah, moved up to the summit together with the soil.” East Perrin nodded, “The drones I released reported that approximately thousands of Predators were seen in the distance. Those Predators seemed to have begun waves of transferring and their motive is still unknown. Therefore, to take precautions, we have already started various preparations.”

“What?” Garen asked calmly.

“Besides transplant, we have also used the Big Wild Wolves to investigate the population distribution of the Predators. One thing we can confirm is that recently, there has been almost thousands of Predators migrating towards our direction and it is very likely that they might attack us. The others are still moving towards different directions, so we’re still unsure of those that are further away but that’s all for the ones that are near us now.”

East Perrin simply explained.

“In our investigation details, we found out that the first wave of Predators that are most likely to migrate towards us is the Level Three Predators who had failed to chase after our Flying Ship.”

“Level Three Predators?” Garen frowned lightly. He had seen the powers that these creatures possess. Even just a human mutation could reach the level of a Level Three Pilot steering a Level Three Mech; they were not easy at all.

“Can we at least estimate their date of migration?” He raised his head and asked.

“That I’m not sure, but we shall investigate it ourselves,” East Perrin replied. The Big Wild Wolves had yet responded to such a complicated message. They could only send people over to investigate through the drones, but they were lacking energy batteries for the drones so they could only go over it personally. Although it was slightly dangerous, they could risk this bit just to evade a bigger danger.

“Water supply is not a problem at the summit. We can drink and rinse directly from the lake water. Food supply can still last for another month. Regarding warmth…” East Perrin laughed and everyone started laughing. They were no longer afraid of the Cold Radiation emitting from Garen, not to mention the cold temperature.

“So we’re safe for now,” she finally concluded.

“Let me know when you have news regarding the Predators then,” Garen nodded and said, “I will be busy, so East Perrin and Malone are in charge of everything. Everyone shall assist the both of them. That shouldn’t be a problem, right?”

“Of course,” East Perrin nodded whereas Malone smiled and signaled an “okay” with his hand — a hand sign he learned from Garen.

“Sinno, you shall be responsible for educating the two children then,” Garen cast a glance towards the two kids by the side. Both of them had gone through the pain of losing their home. They needed way more perseverance and guts than the other kids. With that, they should be considered as talents in the making.

“I have arranged a Willpower training method for you to study. Just remember not to leak it out to others. Of course, everyone in the summit is free to learn but this cannot be leaked to the public. If this was leaked, it would be a big trouble as some people might need to be responsible…” Garen straight away took out the training method of the Crouched Eagle Talon and placed it on the desk.

Since the Black Flood Party had given up on him, they had treated him as a sacrifice. Hence, he would not hold back anymore.

During mass productions of the chip and the breeding of the Big Bad Wolves, he did not have much combat power. If he could arm the power of his underlings together, the strength formed would actually turn out to be powerful.

In particular, East Perrin who had a Level Three Willpower herself. She just had no knowledge of some of the pure Willpower sudden assault techniques. However, all these were written in the book by Garen already. This small booklet contained all the techniques of the Crouched Eagle Talon.

With the Willpower sudden assault techniques, East Perrin’s combat force would not only surpass Garen but if they were to fight against each other, Garen’s Willpower would be destructed instantly. Even against Level Two Predators, one pierce of her Willpower and she could defeat the enemy instantaneously. This was the advantage of the pure Willpower technique. It

Chapter 955: Reform 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Now that Garen did not have his combat awareness and his usual Energy Machinist experimental platform, he was completely vulnerable in the hands of Willpower powerhouses. Just a powerhouse with a Level Two or Three Willpower Technique would be sufficient to defeat his Willpower. Even though his physique could still handle the impact of a Willpower attack below Level Three, he could not merely rely on his Willpower to defend himself from the enemy.

To fight against Predators who use Field Combat, Garen did not have much of a plan as well. If they were to fight upfront, they definitely did not stand a chance.

So he thought of training the underlings such as East Perrin and more. After all, they were still the elites of Leo Town. Leo Town was still considered as one of the safer regions in the radiation belt. Before they entered, everyone was required to go through an elimination before they entered the town. They had also experience brutal war, fighting against the Predators. The fact that they did not die upon the claws of the Stealth Predators proved that their combat skills were still decent.

Especially East Perrin and Sinno; if Garen was not mistaken, East Perrin was able to achieve Level Three Willpower even with just little training in the radiation belt. Whereas Sinno was able to finish such a cruel quest with just Level One Willpower. To become the strongest combat warrior in Leo Town was not easy at all.

East Perrin was probably extremely gifted in the area of Willpower. All she needed was a little spark to ignite her hidden potential.

As for Sinno, he should personally find out how it is possible for her to be this powerful.

At this moment, Garen wanted to enter the special ability space to work so that he could earn enough Spar Stones to purchase a flying Energy Mechanist Imprint. Now that he had the sufficient energy machinery skills, along with a little more training in Mincar to produce more functional energy machines, he should be able to raise his pay.

As long as he did not showcase too much talent, just a little bit, he should be fine.

“Alright, that’s all for now. Sinno, your case is different from East Perrin, come along with me,” Garen got up and walk towards the ground three basement.

Sinno cast a glance at Fanny who nodded to her, then followed quickly behind Garen.

Sinno was petite, her black hair draped over her shoulders like a shawl, nearly covering her entire face including the horrible scars. She was still wearing her clothes from before, her chest wrapped several times with simple white bandages. She was wearing an extremely thin pair of black shorts which displayed her slim and pale thighs which were full of scars. Although she seemed petite and adorable, her delicate proportions were slender yet full.

After the both of them left, Fanny looked at Malone suggestively in which he also returned the same look.

“Since when did the both of you started having such intense passion!?” East Perrin, who was by their side showed a nauseated expression.

She held up the small booklet of training methods and simply flipped through the pages. Immediately, she stood up. Even her arms were slightly trembling.

“This… This!!”

“What is it?” Malone asked with a frown, but he had sort of guessed the possibilities already.

The others were shocked by East Perrin’s action.

“This is the minimum superior level of the training methods! And it’s complete!” East Perrin took a deep breath and looked up to the others around her.

Hiss…

The crowd was instantly speechless.

Training methods retrieved from the radiation belt were mostly incomplete, some of them were even wrong. People from the domain were not allowed to pass on techniques to the radioactive people; that was a rule in which everyone obeyed by. After all, if the rule was ever violated, the region that leaked out the method would swarm out in full force to get rid of the radioactive people who might be practicing the training method. There had been a few cases in history and they always ended up with the annihilation of the radioactive people who practice it.

“It’s different now…” All the bystanders had nearly experienced death once, they were braver than the ordinary bunch. They did not bother about the catastrophe that might be caused by this certain training method. However, they were surprised by the hope and force that it would bring!

“You’re right, it is different now.” A middle-aged woman approached East Perrin and picked up the booklet from her hands. The woman was reading it cautiously as if it was the most precious treasure in the universe.

Nobody knew the amount of luck and bloodshed needed to acquire a decent training method in the radiation belt, which would not even be completed. However, the training method right in front of them right now was a superior leveled method which meant that there would at least be five levels of training methods. This was something only the military and the elites could get in the region!

If this was to be leaked out, perhaps the entire population of radioactive people of the radiation belt, except for the Underground Rebel Army, would go insane. This was something so valuable!

The middle-aged woman was shaking violently.

Suddenly, she screamed.

“There’s even the Pure Willpower Application Skill!!? Oh my God!”

“What!?” The smile on Malone’s face froze instantly. He expected Garen to be generous, but he did not expect Garen to be overly generous.

East Perrin was the one who gave the biggest reaction. For her to be able to reach Level Three merely by practicing through her broken training method was considered a close enough miracle. If it was not for her past few near-death experiences, she would not have accomplished it. However, her Willpower was born with a defect as well, which lack of activeness than the average person. Besides that, her body was lacking increment, so she was unable to carry out Willpower training and the usage of Willpower Attack to detach purely from a Mech. Aside from being able to defend herself from high-level Willpower attacks, as well as piloting a Mech with super speed and power, her Level Three Willpower brought her prestige and a healthy physique.

Now that she had the complete training method in addition to the Pure Willpower Usage Skill, all she needed was some time to rebuild herself, to convert all her Willpower into this training method’s Willpower. With that, she would be able to transform from a Pilot, who could be easily defeated by a Level One Willpower combat powerhouse like Garen into a powerful Level Three Pilot. East Perrin understood clearly how compelling the power of the pure Willpower attack. With just one attack, those ranked below Level Three Willpower with slightly weaker physiques would fall easily at the impact of the Willpower cells. They would be severely injured within seconds with no power of resistance. This would be purely inhibition only. They would stand no chance at all.

“Copy this at once and I want each of you to memorize this. Then destroy it on the spot! This cannot be leaked out or we will be in deep trouble!” Malone recovered from his initial shock. Although a complete superior training method was not something the Underground Rebel Army would be interested in, the Pure Willpower Usage Skill was the confidential core skill that they stressed on. If the army was to find out that they had their hands on something like this, needless to say, the army would kill countless of lives just so they do not lose their advantage.

Several people thought of this and became nervous. However, they swiftly started to get papers to copy it down in silence.

“Mr Garen, what kind of person are you? Why were you forced to hide in the missile compartment of a Mech? You’re such a powerful mysterious person. What kind of enemy would cause a mighty person as you to escape from the region?” Waves of confusion flooded East Perrin’s mind.

“Stop overthinking,” Malone said softly. “We are now Mr Garen’s strength, his blade, and his sword! Let’s all grow stronger and move forward together. The stronger we are, the stronger Mr Garen gets!”

East Perrin nodded firmly. Looking at the others around her, they might all have different thoughts, but right now they were all a strength that was strongly bound together. Perhaps some of them had goals of their own, and some of them were satisfying their egos to become stronger. Take the two children as an example, they even had the thought of seeking revenge on the Predators to become stronger. However, it was undeniable that they viewed Garen as their leader and had their hearts focused on him. The reformation and Parasitism that their bodies went through, the strong glimmer of hope they had in their hands, it was all given by Garen.

“Everyone, let’s work harder and become stronger!” East Perrin had a thousand words in her mind but she did not know where to start but in the end, everything came down to this one sentence.

The two children nodded heavily with a hint of sparkle in their eyes.

The middle-aged woman bit her lips lightly. She seemed to be recalling some painful memories, her expression filled with hatred.

The young man held his fist tight, a look of fierce ambition in his eyes.

Fanny remained silent and watched East Perrin. He used to have an adorable girl, but unfortunately, she was taken away by someone from the radiation belt. Now that he had the strength and a newfound hope, he would be able to find his daughter…

Everyone had their own desires, including East Perrin. Her goal was to protect everyone, to rebuild a safe environment like Leo Town so that everyone could live peacefully without worries. This was her number one goal, but everything seemed to have changed. After the Predators destroyed her home, she should be loathing the Predators and aim to seek vengeance, but the first thing she could think of was Garen’s lonely and exhausted back.

In all her life, this was the very first time a sight of someone’s mere shadow was enough to accelerate her heartbeat, to make her eager to help.

“Yes, I will become stronger. I will catch up with his footsteps and be strong enough to help him!”

She told herself firmly in her heart.

*******************

Ground Three Basement

Garen stood by the biochemical pool, staring quietly into the green sticky water. Behind him stood a curious Sinno.

She did not understand why Garen wanted to speak to her alone.

If he wanted to sleep with her, East Perrin had a much more beautiful body and she even took the initiative, but she had been rejected several times, everyone knew. So sleeping with her should be out of the way.

“Don’t think too much.” Garen said lightly, “I brought you here only because I have one question for you.”

“What question? Just ask.” Sinno straightened up, getting skittish because of the freaky Frankenstein environment.

“I heard you’ve been training on the basic training method for several years now, yet you still can’t produce more Willpower?” Garen asked softly.

“Yes.” Sinno nodded, “But I can still become stronger even without Willpower!” She answered tentatively.

Chapter 956: Reform 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“In terms of training your body, you’ve already pushed it to the limits, but can you fight against a Level Two Willpower Pilot? Not the ones from the radiation belt but the real Level Two Pilots who pilot a Mech and have Willpower attack techniques.”

Sinno was speechless as shook her head.

“Obviously, you don’t have tricks to break into defense. Even if there are another hundred of soldiers like you, one Level Two Mech Pilot would kill all of you in an instant, don’t you think?” Garen smiled and turned around to face her.

Even though she was not reconciled, what Garen said was just the truth.

Sinno had nothing to say, so she remained silent.

“You are very strong, but that is for an average person who doesn’t know Willpower attack techniques in the wilderness of the radiation belt. Ignore the Pilots from the domain or the Underground Rebel Army, you can’t even fight a Level One Mech Pilot. Am I right?” Garen was bluntly discriminating her confidence.

“I wasn’t born with Willpower, that is my fate,” Sinno said softly.

“Are you happy?” Garen smiled lightly.

Sinno remained silent.

“You’re willing to ruin the pretty face you were born with just so that you do not stir up trouble, not attract lust. Don’t you remember the pain you felt when you were destroying your face? And why was that? All because you couldn’t elevate your Willpower, you couldn’t protect your own beauty. Just to avoid being hoisted away to become a slave, you’d rather ruin your own face. All this just because you are powerless.”

Every single word said by Garen hit Sinno deep in her heart.

“What do you want me to do, just say it and I’ll do whatever you say!” Sinno clenched her fist hard.

“I need you to cooperate with me, to let me experiment on you,” Garen said.

“Is there a possibility that I might die?” Sinno asked.

“Yes, you might die, or you might become stronger. You might also become a mutated creature, neither human or monster. You better think it through!” Garen reminded her.

He had an ambitious experiment plan brewing in his mind. This experiment would be a continuation of the one he carried out back in the Totem World.

Maybe he would be able to path a new way of power.

“It’s alright, you’re right. I’m still far away from true strength.” Sinno took a deep breath to prepare herself. “Nobody gets something without reason, that is something I’ve understood since I was a little girl. If I want something, I have to give something in return.”

“Do you need anesthetic?” Garen asked with satisfaction.

“Will it affect the outcome?”

“Of course,” Garen nodded.

“No need then.” Sinno inhaled deeply, “What do you need me to do?”

Garen walked in front of her and pressed her head gently. A weak vibration was transmitted from his hand and towards Sinno’s entire body, swiftly checking through her body and muscular conditions.

“The Distorted Seed has fixed a lot of hidden injuries that you didn’t notice last time. Your body is now in good condition, which is suitable for the procedure. Alright, come here.”

Garen led her to an experimental platform that was built from stone.

Holding her hand, he placed it on the surface of the platform.

“I shall now run a skin allergy test, do tell me if you feel any pain.”

“Alright.”

Garen placed her hands flat on the table, then picked up a metal syringe which was prepared earlier on. From a sealed bottle, he drew out a small amount of red solution which was still boiling. Gently, he then dripped the solution on the skin of Sinno’s outer arm.

White smoke was still fuming from the red liquid, but once dripped on Sinno’s body, she held the urge to pull back her arm. She could only watch as the drop of red liquid dripped onto her outer arm, onto the surface of her skin.

Weird thing was, it did not hurt at all. It was just slightly chilly.

“This type of experimental solution has an extremely low boiling point, just twenty-five degrees. So even if it is boiling, you won’t feel it burn,” Garen explained.

Just when Sinno was going to nod her head, she felt a soft prick extending from where a drip of the solution made contact with her skin.

“There’s a little sting,” she said softly.

“Is that so? Well, the causticity is unavoidable.” Garen touched his chin, “You were reformed by my Distorted Seed though, so your body is able to adapt according to stimulations from the external environment. You should be alright.”

What he wanted to do was to achieve what he did back in Totem World where he successfully excluded all reaction and transplanted a stronger biological organ to attain a higher level of strength.

For someone who was born without Willpower like Sinno, who wanted strength and craved for power, but had the sufficient perseverance, she was the perfect experimental subject. If he succeeds on Sinno, then he could carry out the reformation on himself.

“Is the sting gone yet?”

“No.” Sinno was slightly frowning as she continued to stare at the drop of red solution on the skin of her outer arm.

After waiting for approximately ten minutes, with Garen repeating the question for five times, the sixth time, Sinno finally did not feel the sting anymore. It seemed as if her body had adapted to the corrosive solution.

“It doesn’t hurt anymore?”

“Not anymore.”

Garen nodded his head in pleasure.

“Now take off all your clothes. I will apply a layer of this solution all over your body and you need to mentally prepare yourself. Just now it was just a little sting, but now you will be feeling the pain all over your body. You have to hold on!”

Sinno nodded with no hesitation.

She ripped away the bandage around her chest and took off her black shorts. She was not wearing underwear. In the radiation belt, most girls had no underwear to wear. They were already worried about every meal and their safety, so it was no surprise that they did not bother to look for such hassling things like underwear. After all, water supply for baths was expensive enough. There were more girls like Sinno who just wrapped their chest and left their lower body naked, maybe stuff in some cotton sort of object.

The whole of Sinno’s bare body was presented right before Garen’s eyes, but what surprised Garen was the parts where her body was covered with clothes earlier on now revealed horrifying red scars. There were two of those that extended from her hips all the way to her thighs, almost ripping her bottom into half. If it was not for the coverage of her shorts, it seemed as if there were two blood-red centipedes trying to make their way into her bottom half. It was eerily horrifying.

“It’s very ugly huh?” Sinno covered up her three points and asked in a low voice. It was obvious that she was a girl who cared about beauty, or else she would not have purposely covered up all the ugly parts of her body and only showed parts of her without scars.

“Have a few more looks now, you might not be able to see them anymore.” Garen held out his hand and touched the scars on Sinno’s face gently. It did not feel like an ordinary girl’s smooth and delicate skin, but bumpy like a bunch of maggots heaped up together.

Crouching down, he carefully began to coat a layer of red solution on Sinno’s body.

Soon enough, Sinno was covered by a red layer.

Slowly as time passed, Sinno started shivering as the red solution was slowly stimulating her nerves.

“This is to let you adapt in advance so I didn’t use a large amount of it. Until you’ve fully adapted to it, then I’ll coat another layer of it with higher concentration. Lastly, I will then soak you in the real unprocessed biochemical fluid.” Garen explained, “Hold it in, this is to increase your resistivity towards the corrosive solution.”

Sinno nodded firmly but tears and snot were streaming down her face. The pain was spreading everywhere in her body, wave after wave of stinging pain that she was unable to resist. She felt as if her consciousness was slowly starting to bury itself underneath all the pain.

Garen began stacking small metal plates on her heart, abdomen and on her head.

The old quantum computer by the side was closely monitoring her body condition to avoid any accidents. Even though the adaptation of the Distorted Seed was relatively strong, it was only after it was activated. Now that it had yet to be activated, Sinno’s body was just like any other average person. Only thing was that her resistance, body health, and resilience was slightly stronger.

As minutes and seconds passed, Sinno finally stopped shivering and collapsed in a pool of sweat. The weird thing was, not one drop of the red solution was washed off.

Garen began to use a special form of liquid to wash away the redness on her body. After coating on a layer of blue solution, the redness was finally washed away. Then, the peculiar thing happened – the original scars on Sinno’s skin were faded.

The hideous scars were actually fading away slowly.

“This thing here has the ability to remove scars.” Garen stood up and smiled, “Alright, come again next time then. From today onwards, drop by once a day to do it. Come by around this time, got it?”

“Alright.” Sinno touched the scars on her face with astonishment. They really did fade and she could feel that they were lighter than before.

“Alright, off you go,” Garen waved her off.

Sinno got dressed and walked off on her own.

In the following days, Garen gradually increased the amount and number of the solution.

Towards the back, Garen even wanted to apply the solution on her most private place.

As Sinno slowly opened up and fully cooperated, Garen began making weird requests.

For example, he would request for her to dip into a sink filled with the solution. While she was soaked in the solution, she had to open her eyes from time to time to let the solution enter her eyes and also to purposely allow the solution to be poured into her ears. Besides that, he would request for her to drink a small amount of the solution, sometimes even heating the solution at the same time, or sometimes it was cool. Every time the solution was heated, it easily produced a vast amount of vapor and he would ask Sinno to inhale them.

He just had one goal which was to let the internal and external of her body adapt to this corrosive solution.

On the ninth day, there was finally a new change.

The concentration of the solution increased once again. As she made contact with the solution, she felt the same sting as she did the first time, the pain was maybe even more intense but she resisted.

This step, however, was the beginning of the nightmare which was to come. There seemed to be a new addition to the solution which made the itching everywhere on her body unbearable. But she was surprised to find that many of the scars on her body had actually disappeared. Her skin returned to its normal tone, becoming white and delicate. Whereas her original delicate skin became even shinier. She also felt that her lungs became more comfortable, her breaths were bigger and each inhale took a longer time.

This was the part where Garen reformed her lungs. Lungs are directly related to one’s biological hair. In addition to the corrosive solution that corrected her skin, it was no surprise that Sinno’s scars were disappearing rapidly.

However, all this was just Garen’s preparation work as Sinno’s body had just adapted to the new concentrated solution. Finally, the real reformation shall begin.

The biochemical fluid used for the reformation was a type of highly concentrated corrosive liquid that would immediately corrode any ordinary being who jumps in it. This was also why Garen diluted the solution multiple times to let Sinno slowly adapt to the special biochemical fluid.

Lastly, the only missing part was a powerful organ that needed to be reformed.

As to which organ and which living creature, Garen was still deciding.

Chapter 957: Alienation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the 13th day of Sinno’s reformation, Garen was working at the special ability space while monitoring Sinno’s body condition closely. East Perrin was in charge of the dynamics of their surroundings. Being the leader of Leo Town originally, it was no sweat for East Perrin to control such a small base with so little people. She handled things with high proficiency to the point that Garen need not have to worry a thing. Based on what Garen observed, this lady would have no problem even if she were to lead over thousands of people in a large compound. This allowed him to truly focus on what concerned him the most at the moment.

As he started to familiarize himself with the Energy Machine Imprint at the special ability space, Garen gave the Big Wild Wolves a slight reformation, layering another coat of thin bony scales on the surface of their bodies. This was the result of self-secretion of its own disposal frame and was able to increase the Big Wild Wolves’ self-defense mechanism.

Within 10 days’ time, the reproductive quantity of the Big Wild Wolves had increased to nearly 30. In reality, they could still continue to reproduce, but this quantity was the optimum because the surrounding grassland was not sufficient to supply mutated creatures such as the Big Wild Wolves. The Predators did not dare to disturb the big units while the smaller units of Predators were killed by Big Wild Wolves when they were hunting. Without food supply, the reproduction of the wolves would be pointless, and they would enter a state of weakness within a short period of time.

Materials were another problem. The raw materials used for the biochemical pool are finishing, that was the limit and they could not continue cultivating.

Garen straight away controlled the numbers by its whole and at the same time conserved some of the remaining materials for purposes of repairing the wolves. He could actually cultivate a few more but there was no point for him to cut it this close. If he finished up the materials, it would be a huge problem if he needed to cultivate more in the future. He searched all over for the basic biochemical fluid field and there was only this little left, so he had no choice but to search for them further from here.

Now that Sinno’s adaptation strength was growing, it was only a matter of time that they could reach the final step of completely submerging in the biochemical fluid, in order to be fully reformed by Garen as a biochemical creature. This was also the basic requirement to reform.

Garen also tried to search on the internet for information on reforming the human body at the special ability space but they were all classified as confidential information. Reformation of the human’s body was a taboo universally, so he ended up with not much information to begin with. All he knew was that a few energy machinery grandmasters were issued a killing order for experimenting with human reformation. They have disappeared ever since.

Garen could only test around the waters by himself. The good thing was he did some in-depth study on genes and biological structures back in Totem World. Although there were many challenges to overcome, he could still find other ways to circumvent the difficulties.

What troubled him now was what sort of powerful biological organ was he going to transplant for Sinno.

Sinno was not born with the gift of Willpower and that could be a disadvantage when it came down to her resistance against Willpower battles. Furthermore, she could not pilot a Mech. The only two choices were either strengthening her physique to achieve the level where mutated creatures in flesh were able to resist Mechs; or activating her inherence of Willpower so that she had the capability to use her Willpower.

Sinno definitely had strong endurance, and in addition to her excellent combat talent, Garen wanted to let her strengthen her physique instead of the latter.

As for the choice of organ, Garen did not have many choices. It was either the two-headed sheep or the Predator. In comparison, the structure of a predator’s organ may be more suitable. As long as he could find a high level predator, it would be a powerful one as it is currently the specimen that people from the region is very much afraid of.

Unfortunately, predators have a high concentration of pollution from its radiation virus. Garen had no confidence that he could take care of a virus that the entire region had no way of curing so long. Therefore, this plan would have to be put aside temporarily.

He first chose a special organ from the two-headed sheep – its intestines. In such grasslands, the two-headed sheep were creatures with the highest adaptation ability. Even if there were poisonous grass root plants, the sheep were able to just eat them as energy nutrients for the body. This was strongly related to their powerful intestines and their digestive systems.

Garen did not change the structure of Sinno’s mouth, but only strengthened her esophagus. He transplanted the intestines ‘ small cells into her body. Under the control of the quantum computer, Sinno’s body attained a new type of biological balance under Garen’s precise calculation. Garen continued to carry out depth replacements. After a deep coma of three days and three nights in the biochemical fluid, the first step of Sinno’s reformation had reached its desired result.

The strongest part of the two-headed sheep was its immunity towards virus – that was also successfully transplanted into Sinno.

But there was a price to be paid for it. Sinno has lost most of her taste sensory in her tongue. This was an after effect of the nerves not being able to correspond during the transplantation.

Receiving the powerful immunity and being able to digest large amounts of toxic may not seemed to do much in increasing Sinno’s combat power, but she did feel the effectiveness of the reformation. What Garen had to do next was to research on how to let Sinno unleash her most powerful potential under such resistance. To be able to succeed on his first try led Garen to be more confident for his next transplantation. Sinno and Garen firmly believed that if they could find a stronger biological cell, her strength would continue to increase.

In the meantime, East Perrin and the others were progressing fast in altering the Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower. East Perrin who was originally at Level Three Willpower was as fast as ever. While Garen was reforming Sinno’s body, East Perrin had already completely altered her original Willpower to the Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower. Both her arms were covered with an extremely robust translucent Willpower Field. This was the specialty of the Crouched Eagle Talon. Her explosive force also increased significantly.

Even though she had not fully learned the attack techniques of Pure Willpower, but at least she had a decent defense ability now if she would to encounter attacks. In addition to her complete post-consciousness, even if she was to face the same level of Willpower attack, she would no longer crumble at the first impact like before.

East Perrin could be considered a true Level Three Mech Pilot now.

During this period of time, the grassland outside the summit finally showed some signs.

********************

“Are the predators here?”

East Perrin asked solemnly as she was walked towards the temporary war room.

There were only a few words engraved on the war room’s door. Other than the two children and Sinno, all the other young adults were gathered in the room.

East Perrin, Malone, Fanny, and the impulsive young man whose name was Belebar, the middle-aged woman who was always steady and silent, Shangrella, were also there.

For a long period of time, Belebar went from constantly doubting Garen, to gradually being convinced by Garen. Just that this guy was not simple, and seemed like he had something more going on in his mind under that facade.

The five people present in the room were the only elites left in the small base. They went through hell and several near-death experiences, and were definitely the absolute exclusive fighters. Now that they are all gathered here, it was only natural to discuss and come up with a strategy.

Garen handed over the things used to control the Big Wild Wolves to East Perrin. Since the wolves were hosts of the Distorted Seed, it was impossible for all biological creatures to turn and attack Garen so it was safe to say that their safety was not a major issue now. He had also simplified the control method so that East Perrin could easily control them. There were about 30 Big Wild Wolves, each of them almost the same level as a Level Two Predator. That meant that they have a compelling strength in their hands.

East Perrin closed the door properly and looked at the people present. Instantly, her leadership prevailed as how it was in Leo Town.

“Fanny, tell us how’s the situation?”

Fanny nodded and cleared his throat as everyone sat down around the old table.

“When I was controlling the drone on patrol, I noticed that a small group of predators have appeared towards the West side. The downside was these predators seemed to have a certain disciplined formation with zero conflicts among themselves. After observing them for two days, I believe that this small group is probably from one of the larger group, and there could be approximately 2,000 to 5,000 of them.”

As soon as he finished his sentence, everybody’s faces changed. The number of predators that attacked Leo Town back then was about this number.

“I’m not done speaking,” Fanny continued gloomily. “According to my observation and Master Malone’s past experiences, the bigger the number of predators, the more the higher ranked predators there will be among them. With a group consisting of thousands, plus the high ranked predators that we faced the last time, this time there is likely to be more vicious and Level Three predators.”

“According to our experiment, the Big Wild Wolf is indeed strong, but its power is only equivalent to a Level Two Predator. Three Big Wild Wolves can only face one Level Two Predator, and we only have 30 wolves…” Malone continued.

“The summit is easy to defend and hard to be attacked so let’s just focus our power at the top.” The young man Belebar said in a hushed tone.

“With such a big group of predators, the food supply they need on a daily basis is not a small number so I don’t think they will be able to stay put for long. The only path leading to this summit is the canyon trail and that is what we need to defend. All we need are five Big Wild Wolves to block the path securely, and with the cooperation of our people we should be able to protect the summit safely.”

“You can put it that way, but what if they dawdle with us?” The middle-aged woman Shangrella asked lightly.

East Perrin frowned and pondered.

“There is no way we’re giving up this summit. There aren’t any other places around us that are suitable for defense. If we let the Big Wild Wolves guard the canyon, they should be able to hold up some time. What about our food supply at the summit?”

“We have enough food to last us for about a month, I froze all the dried meat so they won’t go to waste. Don’t worry about water too. We’re not concerned with the high concentration of radiation anymore so we can live safely on the top of the mountain. The fishes I breed are still not needed at the moment but after some time, they’d be able to provide us with a certain amount of meat. When the time comes, we just need to plant some edible vegetables and fruits and we’d be able to fend for ourselves on top of the mountain.” Malone said with a slight hint of pride, he was now fully responsible for the logistics.

“That is good.” East Perrin looked at everyone. “I have now fully converted all my Willpower. My body feels replenished but I’m not sure to what extent. I’ll be able to find out when I stand guard later on. No matter how we fight back, we just have to defend this one trail.”

As everybody nodded in agreement, she continued, “I shall immediately report this to Mr Garen, we will need his support to replenish and renourish the Big Wild Wolves.”

“I will go check the defense areas.” Shangrella stood up and said.

“I will go check on the two children.”

Everyone got up and left.

East Perrin went to Fanny and looked again at the recording of the predators and their formation. The situation was worse than what she imagined. The predators were not only big in numbers, but they were also approaching rapidly.

“It’s too bad we don’t have enough transplanted herbs medicine to have enough Big Wild Wolves, or else we wouldn’t have to be this afraid of such lowly!” East Perrin sneered. Her home was destroyed by these monsters. Even she herself was almost killed by them. Everyone in the base had unspeakable hatred towards the Predators.

“Bring the recording and follow me, we’re going to see Mr Garen.” She motioned towards the disk containing the tape.

The both of them turned and left the war room, walking towards the third ground basement.

They descended the basement steps and pushed open a heavy, stone door. A stone grey corridor appeared. A Big Wild Wolf was crouched right in the middle of the corridor passage, its eyes were closed and it was snoring. Hearing sounds, it got up immediately and stared intently at the two people who walked in. Recognizing them, he lazed back down on the floor.

East Perrin and Fanny walked past the Big Wild Wolf and down the corridor, and entered a small, empty room. There was a sour stench in the room.

“Every time I enter this sterilization chamber, I feel as if my nose just breathed in a mouthful of chilli powder…” Fanny forced on a wry smile.

“There’s nothing I can do, this is Mr Garen’s order to ensure that the biochemical room does not face any disturbance and achieve its best efficiency.” East Perrin did not like the smell as well but there was nothing she could do, this was a disinfecting gas they had to go through.

After staying for a couple of minutes in the room, the both of them approached a small door in the corner. Pushing the door opened, they enter a wide stone hall. Right in the middle of the hall was a pool filled with blood-red biochemical fluid. There was a fragrant smell in the air with a slight hint of blood in it.

Chapter 958: Alienation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was only wearing a pair of shorts. His naked upper body displayed his well-sculpted muscles and body physique. He was rinsing a pale red solution onto his body, while Sinno was lying completely naked in a smaller basin on the side, her body curled up as if she was asleep.

There were a couple of strangely shaped tables and countertops by the room with different apparatus and computers connected with several grey tubes to the biochemical pool in the middle. With sucking sounds from time-to-time, the liquid was constantly being sucked up by the tubes before it passed through an unknown black machine, and entered into another tube leading back to the pool. There was minimum motion, and almost zero waves and swirls in the biochemical pool.

“You guys are here, is there anything important?” Garen sensed the arrival of both East Perrin and Fanny earlier on and turned over to look at them. They have not met for a while, and his skin seemed so much fairer, his lips were slightly darkened and there was a faint, unpleasant look in his eyes that gave people an uneasy feeling.

During this period of time, Garen started his own adaptation process. With the vast amount of corrosive biochemical fluid constantly triggering his body, his body had to adapt to it invariably.

Now that he had fully given up on taking the path of a Combat Willpower Pilot, he took the time to try out a few combat techniques on his own. Unfortunately, all he had was an inhumane painful experience without achieving any further outcome.

There was no way he could get rid of the Seventh Divine Wind General Willpower within his body, so the only way was the Energy Machinist Combination Secret Technique. As he slowly tried to comprehend this pathway in this short period of time, Garen knew that such powerful Energy Machinists do exist, that Inherited Leveled Energy Machinists were definitely scary and they were nothing lesser than a Pilot.

And so he made up his mind to take this pathway.

The third level of the NIS training method allowed him to handle different low levels of reformation. But in order to achieve the next level which is the fourth level of the Energy Machinist Realm, it was not something doable within a short period of time.

“The Predators are here.” East Perrin said solemnly.

“How many of them?”

“At least 3,000 and above, around 5,000.”

“3,000…” Garen did not give much of a reaction, “What do you have in mind?”

“We stand guard at the summit because it is easy to defend and hard to be attacked. We can hold our ground for a period of time and with the help of the Big Wild Wolves, we should be able to drag on until the Predators leave. They are a big army, and won’t be able to stay long here because we’ve already searched for all possible edible creatures in the surroundings. As long as we can uphold our front for just a few days, it should not be a problem.” East Perrin replied.

“Then let’s do according to what you have planned then, don’t disturb me until the very last moment. Sinno, you go along too.” Garen commanded.

Sinno opened her eyes slowly. Although her powers did not increase much, her body’s resistivity towards poison and the corrosive liquid has definitely increased. Even her body fluid was sensing corrosiveness in her reformed intestines.

Standing up naked, Sinno caught the shirt that Garen threw to her and dressed herself. East Perrin was in awe that Sinno’s skin was now so much better than before; the scars on her face had faded to the point that they could be barely seen. Her beauty was slowly revealed once again.

Both of them got dressed and left the underground hall. Garen closed his eyes, trying to focus his vision on the NIS training method.

He had fully understood the function of potential points, and that was only during the accumulation phase where one can use potential points to accelerate the stage. But once there was a stage that required a certain special requirement to pass, then potential points would be of no help.

He was about to enter the accumulation phase. Even though his computing power was considerably strong, what he lacked was not something substantial energy could accumulate, but his knowledge on the different computing powers. He was not sure whether potential points could accelerate such a thing, but he could try step by step.

Energy Machinist was merely just a fighting process of computing power. The stronger the computing power, the stronger the Willpower, the more it is able to relate to Energy Machinist Skills.

“However, if an Energy Machinist’s Willpower is able to affect the increment of computing power then…my potential points might be able to increase my computing power.”

Garen’s sight returned to the NIS Energy Machinist training method.

He paused for at least three seconds.

No reaction… The NIS icon only shivered slightly, but after that there was no more movement.

Garen still have a small glimmer of hope due to the little reaction, hence he never stopped trying almost every single day.

“Is it possible that the other Energy Machinists also did not find a way to quickly increase their Willpower and their computing power?” Garen was lost in his thoughts.

All he could think of at the moment was how to break through Level Four Energy Machinist. He was not sure whether the Predators were going to send flying units, so he had to increase his Energy Machine Imprint to find a flight unit to cultivate. Furthermore, as the Predator Waves increased, more and more high levelled Predators would continue to appear to the point that even the domain would not be able to avoid this matter. Even big domains with Inheritance Level powerhouses like Central Academy had to retreat.

If he did not improve himself soon, he was afraid that soon enough everyone would be defeated and die.

Trying the Level Four computing Energy Machinist model once again, the results were still not achieved even halfway through. The difference was too big. A Level Four Energy Machinist was considered qualitative changing, already being one of the backbones of the Energy Machinist force. A lot of people took nearly 10 years to reach this level while Garen over here wanted to achieve such a high level in such a short period of time. This seemed highly impossible in the eyes of an average person.

“Seems like in order to break through Level Four, I’d have to pay a visit to the special ability space to search for clues…or else if I continue to calculate from now, it’d take another 10 or more years. Such calculation speed will make it entirely impossible to breakthrough.” Garen calculated the time mentally in his head and started to feel helpless.

He had no clue how long the outbreak of the Predator Wave would last, so increasing his strength as soon as possible was just something he had to do.

********************

At the edge of the small black mountaintop, East Perrin and the others stood at the peak and looked downwards. Groups of Predators were slowly emerging like a dense ant colony in the large greyish brow prairie at the bottom.

The five adults on top of the mountain stared hard at the enemies; a few of the Big Wild Wolves arched their heads to the side as they howled.

The sky was just starting to turn bright. The sun radiated soft reddish rays of light, coloring the clouds a faint shade of red.

The wind blew strongly into their hairs, as if tugging on their hair roots wanting to pull it out.

Woo…

Sharp whistling sounds came from the packed Predators group below, but it was unclear which level Predator led the outcry.

The densely packed Predators were all humans who used to be alive, and they were forcing their way up towards the mountain.

“They’re coming…” East Perrin whispered. “The Big Wild Wolves are in position already, now we just wait and see what kind of formation they will use to attack us.”

“So we just wait and watch?” Sinno asked.

“Going out there would be suicide.”

“What if we can distract the Predators?” Sinno pondered and asked.

“There’s no way we can distract that many of them, at most just a small unit of them.” East Perrin thought of this idea long ago already.

Suddenly as the Predators closed in, everyone stopped talking and just lowered their heads to watch the big group fast approaching below.

All of a sudden, a few units of Predators split up amongst the crowd and started dashing up the mountain.

“Incoming! Prepare for battle!!” East Perrin shouted.

The five of them instantly rushed to defend the only trail that led up the summit.

Four Big Wild Wolves were already standing guard along the way in front. They could feel the incoming threat closing by. The wolves got into position and let out an aggressive howl.

Whiz whiz whiz!!

About ten or so black shadows suddenly appeared on the trail, running towards the Big Wild Wolves at top speed.

The wolf kicked its hind legs strongly and rushed forward.

One of the shadows suddenly flipped in the air and managed to avoid the wolf’s bite, then rushed towards East Perrin and the others who were at the back.

“It’s an advanced Predator!!” East Perrin took one glance at the enemy and she instantly realized that this creature was the Level Three Predator who chased after them in the flying ship the other day.

The Predator’s body was covered in pus and it was extremely hideous. With a ferocious expression, it roared and dived towards East Perrin.

“Be careful!!” A few people by the side called out at the same time. They wanted to come over to help but the Predator was too fast and they could not react on time.

In shock, East Perrin did not have time to retreat. However, she arched her body and rushed out fiercely, crossing paths with the Predator. Both of them seemed to exchange their positions just nice.

“Cha!”

East Perrin let out a low growl, barely using half of her Willpower Pierce, shattering the Predator into shivers. At the same time, she advanced and with a short blade in hand, her Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower caused her explosive force to reach another level which was at least double of her previous level. The strength in both her arms was incredibly strong too.

With a clank, the silver blade flashed.

With this attack, she could feel how completely different it was from before. Previously, her dodging the attack in the first place would have been awkward hence don’t even talk about counterattacking.

Now with a wave of her sword, she could feel the strong powerful force slicing through the air.

Taking advantage of the Predator’s delayed movements, she sliced her sword again.

Clang!!!

The short blade swiftly landed on the Predator’s arm, making harsh contact with the Predator’s tough skin. With a tear, the blade continued to impact a force and drew a palm-sized wound at the side of the Predator’s waist and blood came gushing out.

The huge impulsive force caused both Predator and East Perrin to bounce back.

East Perrin found out in pleasant surprise that both of her arms felt numb instead of the expected painful tear. If she had made such a move earlier on, she would have torn her ligaments and then have her bones broken.

“So this is the true power of a Level Three Pilot?!!” A sense of indescribable joy overwhelmed East Perrin. The strength that she was experiencing was nowhere near her previous Level Three Willpower state. The reformed her could easily defeat four of the old version of her.

Chapter 959: Light 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Blackboard Region

Blackboard Academy Headquarters

“What’s the situation now?” Dean Cruz von Shaw stared at the three-dimensional model of the floating star in front of him. The white model had scarlet patches spreading all over its surface.

“The Predator Wave has reached the end of its first phase. It is expected to end soon. There are three more years before it enters the second phase. We only have such a gap period to find the Forbidden Core.”

The other two professors appeared as virtual images in their seats. One of them, Vice Principal Simis, said.

“Your disciple is still training outside. Aren’t you afraid that something will happen to her?” The old woman Babar looked at Simis. “There is also that old guy who couldn’t stand to be left alone. He even personally led a team to go out a few days ago. What a joke if people were to know about it. One of the great three professors of Blackboard actually led a team to catch two less than 30 years-old youngsters?”

“Didn’t Dean’s Black Star go too? At this critical time…who doesn’t want to get that thing?” Simis sneered.

Other than the chief dean, it was just them three great professors. Among the three great professors, only two of them present here were eligible to run for the position of dean. The other person was weak. Unwilling to be overlooked, he took the initiative to seek out the Forbidden Core. In fact, he did not report to the academy in advance. This caused both of them to be greatly astounded.

“There is a gap period between the Predator Waves. Not only our academy knows it, other academies will definitely send their manpower also. The fluctuations sensed by the planet detector indicate that location. Central Academy will probably intervene this time,” Chief Dean Shaw murmured. She looked almost like an average, middle-aged woman. No one would have imagined that she was already over two hundred years old.

“It probably would be fun if anyone comes across a piece of it.” Babar laughed.

“Huh!” Simis snorted. The manpower force he sent out was the weakest among the three of them. Led only by Medero, the situation was naturally unfavorable to him.

He glanced at Chief Dean Shaw.

Black Star, the disciple sent out by this old woman, his strength was now unfathomable. In the early years, he had reached a point where he was only a little weaker than these old professors. Now, it was even more difficult to know what level he was at…seeing the old woman’s calm face, he probably…

His heart felt defeated when he thought of this. Although their disciples were taught by both of them, he was far less than Shaw. The aptitude of Medero and Black Star were almost the same at the beginning. But now, Black Star’s strength was far more than that of Medero, reaching an abnormally powerful state. (Was this difference the reason I failed to obtain the position of dean back them?)

Beep beep…Beep beep…

Suddenly, there was an electronic sound in the hall.

“What happened?” Babar asked with dissatisfaction.

A soft electronic female voice sounded.

“Three presidents, the latest information from the intelligence department.”

As the voice travelled, a white carrier pigeon flew out of nowhere and gently landed on Dean Shaw’s shoulder.

With a boom, the white carrier pigeon instantly exploded into white powder pieces, which then automatically reorganized in the air and turned into a white letterhead paper. It gently fell onto Shaw’s opened palm.

After taking a quick look at it, Shaw toss the notepaper into the hands of the other two.

When both of them read it, their facial expression changed slightly.

“Central Academy is sending somebody over…” Babar mumbled with a solemn face.

“As the leader of the academy alliance, it was impossible for them to not have any response until now.” Simis nodded. “What surprised me was that they actually sent Sun Scorch. That’s their strongest elite organization strength.”

“Just relying on Black Star and the others, I’m afraid…” Babar had just resented the force sent out by the chief dean was too powerful. Now, he was worried that they would be too weak and be supressed by Central Academy.

“It doesn’t matter.” Shaw maintained her composure. “Let them hone themselves. It would be best if they can grab the core. If they can’t, there’s no need to force it…”

The notepaper flew back into her hands, silently breaking into a whole lot of white powder and disappearing into the air.

How easily said by the old woman!

The other two were scolding in their hearts.

“Who from Sun Scorch is coming?” Simis asked.

“It is still unclear,” the electronic female voice replied. “But the intelligence department analyzed that it is most likely to be led by Sun Scorch Hunter Whale Harpoon.”

“How troublesome…The position of Hunter Whale Harpoon has always been known for its strength and range of attack. The effect of clearing the site is terrible…” Simis frowned.

“Don’t worry about it. Encountering such a situation when going out for missions are inevitable.” Shaw shook her head. “Alright, that will be all for today. Dismiss.” Her body dispersed in one shot and disappeared from the projection stage.

“Must send back-up!” Simis said firmly.

“The question is who?” Babar shook his head slightly. “We can’t compare with Central Academy…”

“Then ask Royal Region. The strength of Central Academy is too strong. We can only go against them if we join forces together,” Simis said coldly. “This is the territory of our four major regions. We can temporarily suspend the battle with White Light.”

“That will do too,” Babar agreed.

********************

Whoosh!!

A number of white Mechs produced twisted fluctuations as they dashed across the blue sky. They were in a natural herringbone formation and they uniformly emitted blue flames behind them.

They were headed by a white Mech whose arms were crossed in front of his chest. He had behind him a spiked tail like a lizard and his forehead was inlaid with a green diamond crystal. He looked mysterious and powerful. The rest of the white Mechs were shockingly a large group of Great Light Mechs. All of them were actually the most powerful Inherited Level pilots from White Light Organization!

At the white machine base below, the White Light workers at work looked up at the Mechs flying across the sky.

“Oh wow! What a vast battle array…” A staff dressed in a white suit who was tightening a screw could not help but sighed. “Six Great Light Mechs, even Lord of Lights has been dispatched…”

“Focus and do your job well! We are not qualified to know the matters above!” Another foreman came over to pat him on the shoulder.

“Looking at their direction, it seems that they are preparing to go out into the radiation belt… Looks like a battle is about to begin again…” The foreman sighed and turned to continue his patrol.

**********************

Outer space

In the starry black sky, a silver metallic aircraft like a hedgehog was slowly encircling around Mother Planet. On top of it, spots of silver light flashed from time to time.

On the side of the aircraft, a pop-up metal plate was projecting the ground conditions of the Mother Planet below. The image of the entire Mother Planet rotated slowly on the metal plate and a red dot was clearly shining on it. This dot was continuously sending out water-like ripples to its surrounding.

The location of the little dot was the Seventh Ruins where Clint and others had entered…

*********************

Special ability space

Garen pushed the Cultivation Sphere skillfully away from his hands. A hint of fatigue flashed across his face.

Looking at the finished cultivated new Wild Wolf Energy Machine Imprint in the Cultivation Sphere, there was a satisfying look on his face.

“Not bad. This is the fifth imprint you have successfully produced this week.” Mincar nodded by the side and smiled. He had always had an apathetic and distant stone face. But upon seeing Garen’s achievements, he gradually began to show more and more smiles.

This made Garen, who had purposely slacked off a little, knew that he might have still somewhat overdid it.

Mincar reached for the Cultivation Sphere that Garen had finished nurturing and opened it. He then gently removed the Energy Machine Imprint from the inside.

“As a novice Energy Machinist, you have done well enough, Garen. At least in my past several years as an Energy Machinist, I have only met a dozen or so talents like you.”

“A dozen or so?” Garen was a little surprised. He could only acquire such terrific computing power through adding points to his intelligence, but others would not have such a good condition. Even so, there were more than a dozen of them? This world of Energy Machinist was no ordinary deep!

“Yea, I only saw one or two in a year during the most glorious time in my teacher’s shop. Not to mention now, after so many years it’s just you alone,” Mincar mused. “Our point is just a virtual little point in the special ability space. Your talent shouldn’t be buried at our place here. You should go to a bigger place to showcase your talent. I had originally planned to have you stay with us. But now, I know that asking you to stay will only be holding you back,” Mincar said sincerely.

Patting the shoulders of Garen, the two had gotten along well with each other during this period of working together. And so, these small moves also appeared natural.

“Come with me. As you’re a newcomer, I’ll tell you the true side of the special ability space…” He turned around and headed out of the lab.

“The true side?” Garen narrowed his eyes and followed.

The two men walked along the corridor and went deeper into it.

While walking, Mincar explained quietly.

“The special ability space is a huge overall space that is formed by units of space points. The space point is the basic unit of the whole special ability space. Ours is the smallest type of space point and there are more advanced virtual space points, even the highest level of real space point!”

“Real space point?”

“Yes, it simply means that that space had actually left the scope of virtual network and had become a real, massive dimensional space which can be inhabited by human beings. Everything in it is real. If you wanted to go in, your physical body has to enter together as well, unlike the virtual points like ours which only need our mental essence.” Mincar nodded as he explained and continued to walk forward.

“There actually exist a real special ability space that can be occupied by people?” Garen was astounded. This was equivalent to the technology of turning unreality into reality. Only those who really understood the difficulty of it can understand how terrific the technology is needed for it.

“Yeah… Historically, the two Energy Machinist Master who claimed to be the strongest in history have opened up and discovered this strange space. They then altered and modified it to finally form a special space unique to us Energy Machinist — special ability.” Mincar quickly crossed the corridor and entered into a cloister which had a pool fountain.

“Also, apart from us, pilots have a space that is entirely theirs. This you will know eventually. No need to mention it here. Simply put, from any of the points that are covered by the special ability space, regardless of any virtual points, you can enter into the real point, which is the real existence of the special ability space, at any time.”

“Entering the real point…”

Chapter 960: Light 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Yes, this is the crux to me saying all these to you.” Mincar nodded and finally came to a white door with a silver bat handle. He gently pushed the door open.

Inside was a white screen of light. There was nothing else and nothing could be seen.

“This is the gateway to the real point. It’s the teleporting point to one of the three main cities in the special ability space. Once you enter it, your spirit and body will enter that space together.” Mincar said nonchalantly.

“How big are the three main cities?” Garen asked with a slight curiosity.

“Huge. Each main city is almost as big as a region on Mother Planet. Not all who live in it are Energy Machinists. There are also aborigines but many of these aborigines make a living by providing services for Energy Machinists. You will know how it is once you have gone in.”

“Why would you think of helping me to enter the main city? It should be very costly, right?” Garen asked.

“That is for sure. It did cost quite a lot, but I also have my own interest at heart.” Mincar was frank. “My teacher is seriously ill in bed. There is no way for senior and junior sisters to take up the burden. Keeping you here will only delay your progress, so why not send you to a better platform. Maybe when you have reached greater heights, you can come back to help us a little. That is my only hope.” He forced a smile. “Regardless of how small we are as a tiny sect, we are a registered place. There are two recommended spots an annual basis. It would be a waste not to use them. I have already recommended no less than ten people to go to the main city before you, awaiting the same hope from them.”

“You are just casting a widespread net…” Garen shook his head and was speechless.

“I can’t help it. We will not be able to maintain this point any longer. Perhaps it will not be long before this point will completely collapse and vanish. My junior sisters and I will also leave here then. So, it’s better to send you there in advance while there are still places available,” Mincar spoke frankly.

Garen was also able to understand. During his time as a helper here, although he was able to produce Wild Wolf Imprint, there were increasingly fewer people entering the shop. This was not something that he could help now.

“It will collapse soon here and we will leave. If you want to go to the main city or metropolis, it is best to let me know in advance.” Mincar finally said.

“Which metropolis is it?” Garen remembered that the Energy Machinist space had three main cities on Mother Planet.

“This is directly connected to the City of Nagadako, which is also the main city of Central Metropolis. It is the most prosperous place,” Mincar answered. “It has the most comprehensive and capable Energy Machine Imprints and the greatest self-modification energy machinery technology.”

“Self-modification?”

“Yup. That is retrofitting oneself. The modification of other human bodies is against the law but no one would care if you modify your own body. The City of Nagadako is very skilled in this respect. This is because the most powerful metropolitan City Master of all time is a Naga Energy Machinist with a double snake tail. They have transformed their ordinary human body to a pinnacle state. Even if they don’t use biochemical cannon fodder and elite units from the experimental platform, their individual strength is powerful enough.”

He turned to look at Garen.

“I see that you seem to be taking this path of self-modification, so going to the City of Nagadako would be your best choice. What do you think?”

Garen was silent for a while.

“This is indeed the case.” The change in his body could easily be noticed by Mincar this type of senior Energy Machinist.

“When you want to leave, let me know in advance so that I can prepare the application,” Mincar concluded.

“Yea, I will.” Garen nodded. In fact, he knew that he was sure to leave, but it was just a matter of time. After all, the radiation belt was not a place to stay for long. He did not find Clint and Baylon either, so he could only drop it. The issue now was how to place East Perrin and the others.

“Does the main city of the real space point take people in?” he asked.

“Yes they do, but it’s not what you and I can afford now. Only the top powerhouse can afford such expenses.” Mincar revealed a smile. “If you want to take someone with you, I have no way of helping you with that.”

“Actually, I’m in the radiation belt now. If my subordinates left me, their survival will be…” Although Garen did not finish his sentence, Mincar could guess what was coming next.

“The radiation belt has a secret region of Energy Machinists. Don’t you know?” He was slightly surprised. “It is not only you who have radiation people subordinates. Many of us Energy Machinists come into contact with radiation. There are many of those who have radiation people as subordinates. Although they cannot be brought into the region, there is a single place near the region that accommodates these people. These people are regarded as followers. Later on, when they have become high-level Energy Machinist and have their own advanced Biochemical Pool, they can get rid of their radiation disease. Although the cost is not little, it is better than having no hope at all, right?”

“Such a place exist?” Garen was also hearing this for the first time.

“Yes, otherwise where do you think the anti-radiation protection technology in other regions come from? It came from us. A biochemist and what not could do it if it was thousands of years ago, but right now… hehe.” Mincar seemed to be displeased with Biochemists and sneered.

“What are the conditions for bringing people in?”

“There’s no need for that as long as you prove that you are an Energy Machinist. Oh right, if you can work up some military credits there, it will be very helpful for you in relation to an Energy Machinist’s way of actual combat. It would be best if you can befriend other Energy Machinists. Humans are social creatures after all. It is impossible to embark to a higher level if one doesn’t communicate with others and just stay behind closed doors…”

“That’s right…” Garen seriously considered this. Although he felt that there was some deeper meaning to Mincar’s proposal, his main consideration for now was the placement of East Perrin and the others. At the same time, he had to go to other points to inquire carefully whether the information mentioned by Mincar was true or not.

After leaving Mincar’s special ability point, Garen went directly to the other two nearest points. The flow of people inside was very large when of course, compared to Mincar’s Coco Energy Machinery shop. Garen had been working during this period of time so he had earned some crystal stones. Sending some crystal stones as inquiring fee, he found a few people and asked about the details of the information provided by Mincar.

He learned that Mincar indeed did not lie to him and everything he said was truthful. The surrounding radiation belt truly had a gathering place for radiation people who were followers. However, every Energy Machinist could only bring two people in accordance to each level. In other words, as he was now a Level Three Energy Machinist, he could bring six people in. There were six spots. At the base, there was East Perrin, Sinno, Fanny, Malone and adding on two children, a total of six people. Including the two remaining adults, Bar and Shangrella, that would be eight people.

Unless he could reach Level Four, there was no way of bringing them all in. This was not mentioned by Mincar.

One of the Energy Machinist who took Garen’s money was kind enough to provide him with additional information. After learning that he was in the depths of the radiation belt, this Energy Machinist reminded him that each major region, for the first time, had dispatched powerhouses during the gap period of the first and second Predator Wave for some reason and advised him to be careful.

“It is said that they are looking for some core. This news has now spread all over the place. Tsk tsk. Being able to cause the regions to send out so many powerhouses to grab it, this thing must be no ordinary powerful!” These were the original words of that Energy Machinist.

“I have heard that there are now powerhouses who have gone to the Seventh Ruins.”

Garen suddenly thought of the mysterious Red Moon that was with Clint and Baylon. Reminiscing the series of major events that had occurred before, they seemed to revolve around Clint and others non-stop and even more so now. If he did not infer wrongly, the Forbidden Core definitely was related with Red Moon. These powerhouses going out definitely meant that they had found the whereabouts of Red Moon and the others.

“The Seventh Ruins…” He had been to that place. It was strange, mysterious and extremely dangerous. But now, he had yet to take revenge on Seventh Divine Wind General and there was still that Fila and that mercenary Teacher Van Doe. Also, the residual Willpower in his own body had not been eliminated. Just by depending on the number of Big Wild Wolves, he could do nothing about it at all.

The four major regions and White Light people, as well as Central Academy, had sent their people there. All the powerhouses gathered together as if they were all affirmed that there must be something they need in the Seventh Ruins.

After some deliberation, he decided to send East Perrin and the others to that secret Energy Machinist’s base. He would then leave to go to the main city to develop. Otherwise, staying in this small place would not enable him to come in contact with the higher-level knowledge of Energy Machinists.

He now could feel more strongly that Energy Machinists had a complete system for training and education. It was not something that a self-learned person like him could attain. If he could receive formal education, adding on his conditions and advantages, he would definitely achieve greater heights.

After all, he was a monster who could increase his intelligence computing power through potential points. The intelligence of an average person was limited. No matter how much they trained, they still had an inherent natural restriction and physical bottleneck. But if Garen could find more potential points, there would certainly be a breakthrough in the limit!

After setting his mind, Garen got a map to the secret point from Naga, and at the same time, he began to send East Perrin and the others to patrol further into the surroundings and investigate the flow pattern of the Predators.

Although the recent small-scale Predators attack was repulsed by East Perrin and the others, who had a great increase in their strength and fully demonstrating their capability, this time was different. He wanted to take these people to a farther place, at least a distance of hundreds of kilometers away. The danger level was different from before. It required careful planning.

*********************

“What? You all don’t want to go!?” Garen frowned as he stared at East Perrin.

Clearly, this woman represented the opinion of the others.

“Yes, we don’t want to leave this place. With the presence of Big Wild Wolves, we can totally guard this place firmly. With the training method, we can also have the hope of advancing through communicating with one another. This place is secretive and suitable for living. The old man had transplanted the plants and the small fish reared were already starting its cycle of breeding. We are able to live well here.”

East Perrin said firmly.

“There is still a second-stage Predators Wave coming up next,” Garen said solemnly.

“I know, but there is still the basement. We are doing modification works so it’s okay to stay underground all the time. We just have to reserve food in advance!” East Perrin responded with a definite affirmation, apparently having thought through it.

Chapter 961: Rescue 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Reserve food in advance… easily said. Have you calculated thoroughly the amount of food you need? And how long will the aerial Predators be out in the air? Do you know? The Big Wild Wolves will no longer have the opportunity to replenish after I leave. You lose one of it, the number will be one lesser. With such a small bit of strength, can you say that you can be safe?” Garen frowned.

“It doesn’t matter. We have worked it out. If the food is properly stocked, we can hold out for more than a year!” East Perrin nodded and her eyes flashed with a fierce light. “If it is really not enough, we have alternative methods.”

“What methods?” Garen narrowed his eyes.

“Since our current physique has been modified, we could even eat Predator meat…” East Perrin said in a low voice.

Garen was quiet, but he could comprehend it. Now that everything in the wild had been eaten up by the Predators, once the food was not enough, the only thing that could be used as a food source was the Predators themselves. In the radiation belt, there were many cases of people eating people. What was more, Predators were no longer in the category of human beings.

“Are you all worried about the training method and training techniques?” he asked.

“Yes.” East Perrin nodded fiercely. “What you have given to us is too precious. Once people find out about this, it might be more dangerous in the wild. The radiation concentration here is very high so most people would not come here. It is the best natural barrier to completely isolate outsiders’ view.”

Garen pondered carefully. The others did not matter to him, but East Perrin saved him before. He could not completely abandon this debt of gratitude no matter what. He must consider her future moves clearly.

He asked about the arrangements and plans of East Perrin and the others here, the farming situation, and so on. After careful calculations, perhaps they might be able to survive here, provided that there were no accidental, unforeseen incidents.

“Since you have already decided, I won’t stop you then. But, I’m sure to leave. You must understand this.” Garen said quietly.

“We know. From the time you appeared in Leo City, I know that you would not stick with us for long.” East Perrin nodded.

“Sinno can follow me. Her modification has not yet been completed. Of course, this has to be on her own accord. The modification thus far has been successful and she now has a strong resistance to radiation. But, there will also be more risk if we continue it.”

“I have no opinion.” Sinno slowly entered from the outside. The doorway gradually revealed the appearance of others. Clearly, everyone had arrived. This was a critical moment that would decide the direction of their future development. Garen’s departure was a very serious matter. This means that from now on, they would have to protect themselves with their own strength rather than relying on the number of Big Wild Wolves. Of course, thirty Big Wild Wolves were enough for them to protect themselves for a period of time. There would not be any pressure in encountering small scale of Predators.

Garen had long heard their voices outside. He glanced at them and slowly nodded.

“Since all of you have reached an agreement, then I too…”

Boom!!!

Suddenly, there was a thunderous roar in the distance. The whole mountain seemed to shake violently.

Ah~~Ah! ~~~~! !

A piercing screaming-liked sound travelled from far to near, penetrating the rock formations of the mountain and drilled into everyone’s ears.

Immediately, there was a painful expression on everyone’s faces.

A vague music rang in the air, as if many people were singing psalms or chanting. Layers upon layers of choruses kept on sounded non-stop.

Garen’s face changed. He rushed up and knocked out everyone. Sure enough, once fainted, the crowd’s faces quickly became much more normal. This kind of voice belonged to a mental attack.

He rushed out of the basement, passed through the third and second floor at the fastest speed and jumped out of the exit.

Whoosh! The sound of wind… sound of singing… a sharp whistling sound from the battleships swishing past the in the sky above!

A glaring white light approached and came into view. In the distance was a multi-colored, transparent, illusory huge tree. It was slowly extending into the sky and those layers of ballad seemed to be coming from there.

From far, the tree looked a few thousand meters tall. The thick trunk was constantly flowing with illusory translucent colored energy liquid. It was surrounded by a large number of Mech dots that were tinier than ants.

The eruption of energy fluctuations by these Mechs looked like the size of a fingernail from far. Time to time, some Mech dots would explode in the sky and fall. Fleets of warships farther away were flying towards the giant tree. Countless Mechs continuously darted out of the battleships. At first glance, there were thousands of them, almost covering the entire sky.

“What a spectacle…” Garen suck in a breath of cold air. Looking from afar, the battle situation was divided into three powers: black-white logo, gold line logo, and a completely silver force.

The Mechs and battleships of Blackboard and Polar Region had a black-white round pattern. The black-white symbol on them represented a force.

The combined fleet of Maria Region and Royal Region had gray-gold lines flowing on the surface of their battleship and Mech. Among them were powerful White Light Mechs. The gold line was their signature.

There was also a force that was entirely silver, whether it was the Mech or the battleship. The barrels on their body were far longer than that of others. Just a humanoid Mech would have no less than a dozen large barrels, looking savage like spikes. Among them was a leading Mech with a round silver rotating disk behind its back. On it were full of sophisticated and complicated mechanical structures. It was not known what its usage was.

The strangest thing was that the Mechs of this force was generally larger than that of the two major forces. They gave off a kind of inexplicable, peculiar aura.

The power situation of the three forces was very strange. Both Blackboard and Maria-Royal seemed to have only dispatched ordinary general pilots to fight and exhaust one another, whereas, the real powerhouse were still waiting and watching. There was no big move between them.

Similarly, the silver force was motionless here. Although they had the fewest number of people with only hundreds of them, they seemed to be taken seriously by all.

Garen looked up at the distant sky. The Mechs collided with each other and exploded, bursting out yellow-red flames like the blossoming of flowers in the sky. The sound of the explosion could be faintly heard, but more were the sound of muffled thunder rumbling. That was due to the infrasound vibrations formed by a large number of explosions together.

In the sky, hundreds of Mechs and dozens of huge battleships fired at each other, entangling in battle.

Under the blue sky and white clouds, black missiles fell down like meteoroids from time to time and left deep, empty pits of various sizes on the ground. White laser beams flickered and disappeared, like a flash of the sword which was quickly extinguished instantly.

Only a few laser beams would last for a while. They first gradually became thicker and brighter before they slowly thinned out and darkened.

Garen stood on the edge of the hill. Occasionally, dark colored battleships would break out of the clouds above him and flew towards the battlefield at high speed. At the same time, numerous Mechs would fly out of the battleships. Looking up to the sky, there was not a spot that was not occupied by the Mechs or battleships. The entire sky was slightly dim, even the light was obscured by these war machines.

Nobody bothered about the hills below, not to mention a little person on the top of it. Garen stood on the edge and looked at the battlefield. The leaders of the three forces seemed to be negotiating about something. After a while, the colorful giant tree began to move slowly and swayed its branches around. It seemed like something new had happened.

The three powerful forces suddenly became excited. Garen saw a Mech from the silver force headed straight towards the other two coalition forces.

“Central Sun Scorch, Hunter Whale!” A deafening deep groan burst forth from that Mech.

“Maria, Zero Rifle!” The gold line side flew out a slender, feminine white female Mech. Unmatched with her figure, she carried a huge heavy rifle several times longer than her body, looking anomalous.

After the two Mechs had revealed their names, there was no nonsense and they immediately engaged.

Now and then, Zero Rifle would shoot out beams of golden lines. The strange thing was these rays were actually able to bend and round the corners on their own. Their speed was extremely fast. From a distance, they were like golden nematodes, twisting and turning, constantly trying to penetrate into the body of the silver Mech on the opposite.

The silver Mech seemed to easily wave back and repel the attack of the golden lines. Occasionally, he would take a step forward. Behind him, several of the golden lines would automatically collide with each other and melt away as he closed in step by step. Zero Rifle was easily forced to move back bit by bit.

“How strong…” Garen watched from a long way off. The Mechs appeared as small dots due to the great distance. And yet, the energy attack that they broke out was actually the size of a palm. The proportion was astonishing. Even as Garen stood here, he could feel a slight sense of pressure, like a strong wind blowing on his cheek.

“Zero Rifle is being suppressed… truly the powerhouse of Central Academy!” It was also Garen’s first time seeing the Mech pilot from Central Academy. All these pilots were gathered together at this time and seemed to be fighting madly for some secret treasure.

At this moment, a branch on the giant tree discharged a spot of white light.

This light spot was like stirring up a hornet’s nest. Instantly, the entire three forces of Mechs had no difference in faction. All of them rushed madly to the light spot tossed out by the giant tree, as if that was an extremely powerful treasure!

Even Zero Rifle who was still battling Hunter Whale, the Central Academy’s Mech, stopped fighting and darted straight to the light spot.

Unexpectedly, the light spot could automatically dodge. It twisted and turned, evading all the Mechs. Not even one of them could successfully seize it.

Pew!

Suddenly, the giant tree spitted out a white light spot again, followed by the third and fourth. More and more light spots appeared, flying everywhere. All the powerhouses were dispatched to catch the light spots.

In particular, the Inherited Level powerhouses. Looking at each one of them from afar, their characteristics could be noted clearly. The ones that were covered with an unmatched Willpower shield and were rampant were of Inherited Level.

They appeared to consciously avoid colliding with one another that were of the same level, and shuttled around the general Mechs to catch the white light spots.

Garen soon found Seventh Divine Wind General from Blackboard Region. That blue long-barrelled gun Mech with its obvious characteristic had a mirror-like outer shell as blue as the sky. There were other similar blue Mechs around him. All of them emitted with a strong force field, directly clearing the site they were at.

Obviously, these were the four great Divine Wind General of Black Flood Party. They all wore the same one-shoulder cloak and a large word, Wind, was written on it.

“Hahahaha!! Black Flood Divine Wind General? Let me see if you are worthy of your title!!” Another acquaintance from White Light appeared in Garen’s vision. Ice Dragon! His familiar tone had always been very characteristic. It was difficult for Garen to forget after he had heard it once, or one could say that it was difficult for anyone who have heard of his distinctive tone to forget it.

A large Great Light Mech from White Light emerged and bolted straight towards the four Divine Wind Generals.

“Ice Dragon! Don’t get in the way!!” A Divine Wind General rushed out. With the two knives in hand, he gave a cross-slash and was entangled with Ice Dragon.

“Four, don’t get caught up with him!” The Divine Wind General leader bellowed, “Six and Seven, go force back that mad lunatic together!”

“I’ll use resonance skill, hurry!” Seventh Divine Wind General shouted. A dark cloud of black mass appeared in his hand and was gradually getting larger and darker. Very soon, it turned into a cloud of black airflow mass and was suspended between his palms.

Sixth Divine Wind General hurriedly darted out without saying much and provided close support. His single-broadsword was slashing out non-stop. The terrifying force field between the Inherited Levels constantly clashed together. Ice Dragon was only at a disadvantage for a moment.

“Resonance skills, Ice Cicada!! Hahahaha!!” Ice Dragon did not retreat but was even more fanatical. He seemed to be in full excitement and hysteria.

His Mech suddenly spewed out four white insect-like objects. The four things automatically turned and pierced towards two Divine Wind Generals. The speed was so fast that the two could not react. It was just a moment and those things were already in sight.

“Six, Four, don’t get entangled!” The Divine Wind General leader roared.

“Resonance skill. Black Dragon Sword!!” Seventh Divine Wind General incorporated the long spear pike in his hands with black mass and brought up a large gust of black wind. A huge force field power distorted the airflow, whirled and emerged before him, and then madly…struck the back of the Divine Wind General leader who was beside him.

Boom!!! Black gas tumbled all over.

The Divine Wind General leader’s body was pierced through from the back and the sharp tip of the spear pike penetrated the cockpit at the chest. The huge force thrust his whole body forward.

“You…!”

He looked down at the tip of the spear pike unbelievably.

Chapter 962: Rescue 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Third brother!!!” Sixth Divine Wind General’s eyes widened and his jaw dropped when he looked back and saw this scene. Wanting to turn around to rescue him, his back so happened to be hit by Ice Cicada. His whole Mech was covered with white frost and his action became slow.

At this moment, Fourth Divine Wind General who was having a close combat with Ice Dragon suddenly spun around and struck Sixth Divine Wind General’s back with his two knives.

He acted extremely fast. Despite being hit by Ice Cicada, it was as if nothing had happened. Needless to say, it must be some kind of trick that he and Ice Dragon were playing.

Bang!

Sixth Divine Wind General forcefully raised his arm to use a backhand with his armor and deflected the blade and avoided the danger of being cleaved at the cockpit. But because of this, one of his arm was also cut off by the two knives. He crashed to the ground like a kite with a broken string.

Meanwhile, Third Divine Wind General, who was pierced through, slowly and silently disintegrated into a mass of black particles. It seemed that there was something weird about the weapon used by Seventh Divine Wind General.

At this time, the giant tree discharged several white light spots again. Numerous Mechs were snatching it madly. The situation became increasingly chaotic.

Fourth and Seventh Divine Wind General exchanged a look with Ice Dragon in the sky.

“Don’t bother about him. Grabbing the thing is more important!”

Fourth Divine Wind General spoke in a low voice.

The three broke up and darted straight towards three light points.

The change of events here was only a small one among the three forces. Not only here, there were also powerhouses from Polar Region who rebelled. Under the circumstance where several of the Inherited Level powerhouses were unprepared and did not completely activate their force field, they were sneakily attacked by their own powerhouses, injuring and killing many.

Even Black Star spun around and battled with Medero and the many powerhouses from the same region. He seemed to be at ease as he strolled about, clearly a traitor in this operation!

More than half of the powerhouses in Blackboard Laser Coalition rebelled and fell apart.

The battle situation in the sky was chaotic.

On the top of the hill, Garen narrowed his eyes slightly and looked at the direction in which Sixth Divine Wind General fell. With a thought in mind, a Big Wild Wolf slowly stepped out from behind and knelt beside him.

Reaching out, he gently stroked the head of the Big Wild Wolf.

“Sixth Divine Wind General…that’s him?”

************************

Below the giant tree, nearby the Seventh Ruins.

Wreckages of battleships and Mechs of all sizes were scattered all over the ground. Pits of different sizes were formed as they crashed into the ground. Some places still had fire burning slowly. Occasionally, there would be a loud blast caused by the explosion of the kinetic furnace.

In a larger dark pit, a dark blue humanoid Mech with its right arm broken was lying silently in it.

Du…

The Mech cabin opened automatically and a human body wearing a black combat suit and a helmet rolled out from the inside. His entire body was bundled up tightly and there was a white word, Wind, on his shoulder.

He weakly rolled over to the bottom of the pit, unable to move at all. He forcefully turned over and looked up at the complex battle situation in the sky. His vision gradually began to blur.

‘Body health index dropped to twenty, warning, warning! Peripheral nerves damaged in large areas, Willpower cannot control the body, Willpower core is seriously impaired. Please send a distress signal immediately. Please send a distress signal immediately!’ The built-in intelligence of the combat uniform continued to sound.

“Hehe… Can’t control?” He smirked. The sharp pain in his body came wave after wave. That sneak attack and direct hit from Ice Dragon’s Ice Cicada had heavily injured him completely. His consciousness became more and more blurred and unclear at this time.

‘Warning! Warning! Please send out a rescue signal right away. Sixth Divine Wind General, Your Excellency, your physical condition is very bad. Failing to get help in half an hour’s time will lead to permanent paralysis!’ The sound of built-in intelligence kept on ringing.

But he could not hear it clearly anymore. The voice in his ears seemed to be getting farther, and farther…

Send out a distress signal? Now the people of Blackboard and Polar were being hunted down. It was already difficult for them to protect themselves. Who would come and help him? Could help him? Sending out a signal would only draw the enemy.

“Not-falling Level…” He finally managed to raise his hand and with his last effort, pressed the intelligent system switch on the combat suit to completely shut down the system. The noisy warning sound disappeared completely.

His eyelids continued to drop and become heavier and heavier, heavier and heavier. The light in front of him was also increasingly dimmed.

“Finally… found you…” Vaguely, he heard someone talking.

Is it the enemy? This thought flashed through his blurry mind.

The view before him moved, like someone was helping him up.

Pap pap! Pap Pap.

A few slaps on the cheeks, but no pain was felt.

“Still alive? That’s good!”

His eyelids finally closed completely. This sentence was the last sound he heard.

*******************

No idea how long it had been…maybe a day, maybe two days or maybe more.

He began to awaken and his body felt warm. The sun was shining on the skin of his body.

“Sun? How can there be sunlight shining through the protective clothing onto the skin in the radiation belt?” His brain was still somewhat chaotic.

“You’re awake?”

A man’s voice sounded around him.

At the third floor of the basement in a gray-black single stone room, Garen hands were in his pockets. He had changed his clothes at this time to the ones stripped off from the Mech pilots who died in the battle. His previous clothes were tattered since long ago. So he grabbed a few more sets back during the chaos in the battlefield. Unfortunately, there were a number of others who were also searching the corpses like he did. The rest of the Inherited Level corpses were seized by others. Since he was now physically injured, his strength was too weak. Being able to bring this guy back was considered good enough.

He looked at the guy on the sickbed who was wearing a tight-fitting black combat suit with a big word, Wind, on his shoulder. His head was wrapped in a helmet and there was no way to see what he looked like.

In order to avoid any misunderstanding from the other party, he did not touch anything on this guy’s body, not even his clothes.

“Have something to eat.” Garen gestured with the fish soup in his hands. It was just cooked and was emitting steam and aroma. The thick fish soup had fish and dissolved fishbone in it, making the whole soup a pale white.

Sixth Divine Wind General tried to move his arm but there was no response.

“It was you who rescued me?” He asked in a small voice.

“Who else?” Garen shrugged and placed the fish soup on the stone table.

“Let me introduce myself. My name is Garen, the newbie who was once rescued by you, the one who offended Seventh Divine Wind General and was almost gotten rid of. Remember?”

Six immediately recalled that he had indeed rescued a beginner-level genius. His name was Nonosiva?

He looked at Garen, eyes puzzled and alert.

Garen smiled.

“Nono was my name. Now, I’m called Garen.”

Six nodded after a moment of silence.

“I remember you.”

“Things will be easier then.” Garen laughed. “Since you have regained consciousness, is there a good way to treat yourself? You are a Divine Wind General, Inherited Level top pilot! You would have some means, right?”

“…”

The smile on Garen’s face could not hold out any longer.

“You don’t have? You’re Divine Wind General! Inherited Level top pilot? Don’t tell me you don’t have any first aid treatment method!?”

“…”

Garen was baffled. Looking at the silent and pitiful Sixth Divine Wind General, he sighed.

“About your physical condition, you should be clear about it, yea? Same as mine, being injured by residual Willpower. Most of your Willpower had to be used to resist the opponent’s Willpower. If you want to recover, the duration has to be counted by years.”

“I know.” Six nodded. His head was the only part that he could move freely for now. “The entire body’s nerves had broken down, the body and Will had been separated and most of the Willpower is being suppressed. I am basically a useless person now. My strength is not even half of what it was during my peak period.”

Garen was speechless. This guy knew everything and his situation was even worse than himself back then. At that time, he was only hurt by the little Willpower released by Inherited Level. This guy was attacked by the enemy who wanted to completely kill him. If it were not for his powerful Willpower, the general person in his condition would have exploded and die any minute. He was simply a human bomb.

The Willpower remained in his body was constantly trying to blow him up from the inside so that he was in a kind of internal tearing pain at any moment.

“What are your plans for now?” Garen asked. “I saved you merely because you have saved me back then. One for one.”

“One for one?” Six repeated and did not speak.

Time passed slowly. He did not speak for a long time. His eyes looked misty and he seemed to be recalling something.

“They won’t let me go. They will definitely come here to search for me. It is better for you to throw me out. Otherwise, even if it’s in the radiation belt, you will also die.” Six said plainly.

“I certainly know that powerhouses like you will not be easily let go, different from me back then.” Garen said naturally, “So I intend to leave immediately. From the looks of it, Blackboard and Polar are bound to be chaotic.”

“You can’t escape.”

“I have my way.”

“The strength of the regions is not what you can imagine. Even in the radiation belt, you and I can’t run. We are dead,” Six said plainly.

“No, we’re not. My way can definitely avoid them!” Garen said assuredly.

“What do you know…? You’re just a little guy who hasn’t even touch the barrier…” Six sighed. “In the five levels of Inherited level, the third Non-falling Level powerhouse’s strength is beyond your imagination. No matter how we escape, we are sure to be dead. It is only a matter of time.”

“Little guy? What right do you have to say that I’m a little guy?” Garen laughed and was not angry. The way of Energy Machinist could not be simply leaked out so naturally, the other party was unclear since he did not know.

“I have lived for more than 500 years. You tell me, do I have the right?” Six answered calmly.

“500 years old!” Garen was shocked. Even though he had now travelled through a few worlds, but whether he was 500 years old was still in question. From this point of view, besides having richer experiences than the other party, this guy truly had the right to call him a little guy.

Chapter 963: Departure 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Alright, even if you are more than 500 years old and are older than me, what about that?” Garen exhaled. “The key question now is, what are your plans for the future?”

“We will not have a future.” Six faintly closed his eyes. “I advise you to better leave this place immediately. Stay further away, then perhaps there would still be chance of living.”

“Can high radiation levels prevent their search?” Garen suddenly asked.

Six opened his eyes and gave a puzzled look.

“Don’t you feel any difference in the environment here?” Garen smiled.

Only then did Six felt that something was amiss. The radiation concentration here was denser than that in the outside world, at least twice as much as outside.

Garen did not elaborate but let him sense the situation here quietly. He went out and started packing. High radiation concentration could indeed cut off various searching signals, but this was not certain. It could only extend time. The key now was to arrive as quickly as possible at the secret region where the Energy Machinists were located. That was where outsiders could never enter.

Six Divine Wind General had once saved his life. Repaying any debt of gratitude he owed was Garen’s principle. It was impossible for him to give up and flee on his own. Therefore, the most urgent thing now was to prepare to leave as soon as possible.

The distance to Secret Region from here was not close.

He kept the Biochemical Pool away properly, took some food packs and placed them on two Big Wild Wolves.

East Perrin and the others from the top floor of the basement were waiting at the entrance of the second floor. They had already helped Garen packed some necessary equipment, such as a one-time toxin detection capsule, which was used to detect poison in water sources and food to identify whether they were consumable. They did not use it when they came here so it was given to Garen.

There were also some remaining low-radiation pieces of meat and water from the base. This was what Garen specifically wanted for Sixth Divine Wind General. He did not need it for himself.

In addition, some miscellaneous small things were also being packed by the crowd.

“You…really want to leave?” East Perrin approached him and asked in a low voice.

Garen signalled to Sinno to pick up the bundle and nodded.

“This time, all of you staying here must utilize the high radiation concentration to hide yourself. Do not expose yourself. The next Predator Wave will be more violent. Be careful.”

“Yes, we will.” East Perrin nodded. The rest of the people were in a tacit understanding and did not disturb the two. East Perrin liked Garen and everyone felt it. But now, she could not go with him.

Truth to be told, at the bottom of her heart, East Perrin wanted Garen to ask her, but…she could not leave behind these last few people of Leo City. There were also two children and she was the strongest powerhouse here. If she were to leave, their survival rate would be very low even with the Big Wild Wolves here. Moreover, them staying here was the best way as compared to going away with Garen. After all, there were many people in that Secret Region. Once the training method skill they acquire was exposed, it was hard to predict the consequences.

After carefully consideration, as long as this place was hidden properly, it was entirely possible to build a small, self-sufficient base in the hills. Living on for many years would not be a problem. It would be much safer to wait until years later when their training method had reached a certain level before going out again.

“Alright, Sinno. Let’s go.” Garen patted East Perrin’s shoulders. During this period of time here, he had successfully managed to avoid the threat of Predators by borrowing the strength of Leo City. Of course, he had also helped them to survive and preserved a remnant. As all good things must come to an end, it was time to leave now.

Sinno carried the bundle and walked behind Garen. They returned to the room where Sixth Divine Wind General was lying in and put him on a simple stretcher placed on the back of a Big Wild Wolf. Garen and Sinno each rode a Big Wild Wolf.

They headed towards the exit of the second floor of the basement.

Sixth Divine Wind General also saw this strange group of people. He was surprised that they were all doing fine in this area of high radiation level. However, the people’s attention were all focused on Garen and Sinno.

The three people rode the Big Wild Wolf to the second floor. Others also followed to the second floor. Upon reaching the exit of the first floor, the basement slate was pushed upwards and the three Big Wild Wolves went out one after another. Their movements were slow and steady.

“Will you still come back?!” East Perrin suddenly shouted after Garen from behind.

Garen waved his hand.

“If it is destined.”

He went down along the hill. East Perrin and the party stood on top of the hill and looked down at Garen the three who were slowly descending. Malone clutched East Perrin’s hand tightly.

“He is just a passer-by. This place is just a brief stopover in his life. We…are two different kinds of people…” Malone sighed. He had witnessed too many separations in his life. He was clear that although East Perrin had an excellent aptitude, she could only advance to the vertex of Level Five and at the most five. This was the limit in radiation belt. Without a Mech, even the strongest talents could not break into the resonance level. What was more, he had repeatedly checked that the aptitude limit of East Perrin was indeed at Level Five. This is a limitation by the genes.

About Garen’s aptitude, he was not able to see through it. Although he did not check it, the future of Energy Machinist could only be known by the Energy Machinist themselves. From the look of Garen’s various performances, Level Five would not be his end.

East Perrin looked at the three people below from far. The three Big Wild Wolves gradually could only be seen as little spots.

She felt a little melancholy. But with Garen gone, life had to go on still. She also had to lead the last remnant of Leo City to kick-start and regenerate into a new and stronger Leo City!

Fanny stood behind the two. Watching the firmly-forward moving Sinno, he sighed softly. He had always treated this girl as his own sister. Now that his sister was leaving, he could no longer continue to follow her back and protect her…

Pat.

One hand rested on his shoulder. The middle-aged woman, Shangrella looked at him with a comforting gaze.

“Sinno will live well, even better than us, because she followed Mr. Garen.”

Fanny nodded heavily and did not speak but only sighed deeply.

*********************

Night fell. A red moon hung in the sky. Beside it were two blue and white satellites that were smaller in size. They were releasing a faint light in the night sky.

On the grayish black grassland, the three persons rode the Big Wild Wolves and headed steadily towards a direction in the grassland.

The three Big Wild Wolves were arranged in an inverted-V formation. The one Garen rode was on the front. Sixth Divine Wind General was tied on a stretcher with a rope to prevent him from falling. However, the continuous undulating back of the Big Wild Wolf was not suitable for lying down, making him extremely uncomfortable.

Sinno’s gaze was steady as she followed behind Garen. She was constantly alert of their surroundings and its movements.

The grey-black grassland looked endless. The wind blew through the grass from time to time and made a buzzing sound.

“Where do you want to go?” Six asked in a low voice, but the sound was clear enough for both to hear.

“Can’t say for the time being, but you can be assured that I will do my best to protect you.” Garen answered without looking back. He was not only moving forward currently. At the same time, he was working on the calculations of Energy Machinist Level Four. Big Wild Wolf already had the direction to the destination in its mind. He only needed to sit firmly on its back.

“Was that Willpower transmission?” Garen noticed that the voice just now was unique.

Six nodded.

“This is a simple skill that can be used once Willpower achieve resonance skill. Some talented ones do not even need resonance level.” He sized up the Big Wild Wolf underneath his body. “You are also an Energy Machinist. I overlooked that.”

“This is the basic reconnaissance unit that I developed myself. How is it? Not bad, right?” Garen knew that the other party was well-informed and probably also knew much about Energy Machinists.

“I don’t know much about your profession, but I have seen some reconnaissance cannon fodder creatures. Yours can sustain for a very long duration. As a reconnaissance force, it is almost the same as the regular Level One combat army unit.” Six nodded slightly and gave a good evaluation. “The speed of some Level One combat army unit, like the more powerful poisonous bees, eagles-type, or leopards-type, is just like yours. Combining with other qualities, this wolf can be considered as medium-low class of Level One. Considering it is only a reconnaissance unit, this is very good.”

“Oh? Just medium-low?” Garen looked back at him. “Then what’s considered as medium and high class?”

“I have not come across many. Most of the Energy Machinists stay on their own sites. The average person would not provoke them. This group of people is known to be notoriously difficult to deal with. They deal with radiation a lot and are feared by many. Generally, they also won’t randomly go to other pilots’ places.” Six shook his head slightly. “But I’ve heard that only Level Four Energy Machinists are capable of creating the official combat army units. Official combat army units. The Level One combat army elite units developed by some Energy Machinists who took the elite path could fight with Level Two pilots. That is terrific. Some who took the group route are able to nurture a multi-headed combat unit. Their joint attack and array tactics are all very strong. If the same level Energy Machinists can hid properly, they would be invincible. If they can’t win, they can flee and escape once the situation turns bad.”

Garen nodded. He had also found out about these from Mincar’s internal network, but they were not as clear as Six’s systematic description.

“Also, some Energy Machinists are part-time pilots. Although they are not strong, they are not without combat strength. Utilizing some group-influence props is of no problem. Of course, this kind of prop is expensive, but Energy Machinist is not a profession that lacks money,” Six calmly said. “I can probably guess where you are headed.”

“Oh?”

“Is it Secret Region?”

Garen smiled and did not deny it.

“If it is Secret Region, indeed it is possible to avoid the other party’s search. However, the premise is that we can get there.” Six looked up at the night sky. “They are here.”

Whoooom!!

A red meteor suddenly descended down from the sky and flew in the direction of Garen them three. Even though it was a few kilometres away, the powerful and terrible energy field was so apparent that Garen and Sinno could scarcely breathe.

“Inherited Level again!!” Garen’s face stiffened. The last scene in which he was suppressed by Seventh Divine Wind General once again came to mind. In this moment, the situation was completely the same with back then, except that the place had changed to the grassland in radiation belt.

“It’s Four…he is still a few kilometers away, He had only preliminary sensed my direction but hasn’t really found me yet. Go quickly!” Sixth Divine Wind General calmly instructed.

Chapter 964: Departure 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen nodded hard, and ordered the slightly panicked Big Wild Wolves to pick up the pace and run as though their lives depended on it.

“What on earth are they doing to determine your location!?” he roared without looking back.

“Willpower, we Divine Wind Generals are connected to the Black Flood Holy Pillar by our Willpower, it will give us a larger boost in power, but it will also be able to track our general location.” Sixth’s expression remained impassive as he looked up at the red shooting stars in the distant sky. Right then, the three of them turned to the left and spun rapidly, slowly leaving the direction that the shooting star was coming from.

Only then did Garen and Sinno heave a sigh of relief.

The two of them realized that their hearts were pounding extremely quickly. In that moment just now, Garen even felt as though he might have to use the trump card that he had been saving to keep himself alive. All this time, in order to increase his chances of survival, he had created a single trump card according to the standards of the Energy Machinists. But this thing was single-use only, once he used it, it would be gone. He had modified it based on the Instantaneous Paper Box that he had used up back then, although its function was gone, its shell and materials remained. These were all precious materials, so Garen used the Energy Machinist’s internal network to find a small tool that could accumulate Willpower. He inserted the Willpower that he had accumulated for a long time inside it, it was probably ten times as concentrated as his current Willpower by now. If it weren’t for the resilience of the Instantaneous Paper Box’s materials, such a small tool would have been destroyed a long time ago.

But precisely because of that, Garen could barely just make a small item with great single-use explosive power. If he could ignite that Willpower once, it would form a short-term Impact Storm. Its power would probably be considerable, but he really could not be sure against an Inherited Level.

He just had to pray that the Cold Radiation coming off from him would be enough to hide their scents, and could influence the Inherited Level’s sense of direction to a certain extent.

If the opponent really caught up to them, their imminent doom was almost certain.

Although they would very likely die if he caught up to them, the Sixth Divine Wind General had saved Garen before, so he did not give up or abandon him in his time of need, and the results were very clear.

The Divine Wind General knew that as well, that was why he kept asking Garen to leave him and save himself.

“If you have any tricks you can use to save yourself, better get them ready now,” said Garen without looking back. He did not believe that the Sixth Divine Wind General would have nothing of the sort.

“I’ve already used it,” replied the Sixth Divine Wind General calmly. “Look above you.”

Garen and Sinno instantly looked up, and saw a slightly black semicircular defense shield covering the tops of their heads. This shield was translucent and barely there, vaguely hanging above them, and moving as they moved.

“This Willpower Barrier should be able to block off our scents to a certain degree, but I can’t hold it for long,” said Sixth softly.

He seemed to treat everything with indifference, no matter how serious the matter, he still used this calm and cool tone.

Be it losing the most precious thing to a pilot, his personalized Mech; his own grave injuries, to the point of paralysis; or the fact that he was running for his life, and could die at any moment. He did not seem to have many variations in his emotions, as though he was forever this calm and collected.

“How long can you hold it?” Garen asked in a low voice.

“Twenty minutes, I need to rest for half an hour in between.”

“That’s enough!” Garen calculated the rough distance, and found that it should be fine.

He looked up, and saw the red shooting star crash into the ground hard from the distance. Even the plains were shaking slightly, making a loud wailing sound.

Garen turned around, and looked at the Sixth Divine Wind General.

“I have one last plan, I can rapidly heal your injuries, but without Mechs, the chances of us surviving aren’t high. The only way is to go Berserk, but there’s a high chance that you’ll become something like us, and your mind will be under my control. If there’s no choice…”

He let the Big Wild Wolf approach Sixth, and stuffed a handful of something blue at his left chest.

“If you really have no choice, then release the automatic Willpower protection over your heart. But when that happens, there will be no more turning back. You must remember, unless you’re desperate, don’t use it,” Garen kept reminding him.

Sixth looked down at the thing in front of his chest, it looked just like a plump blue ball of flesh, fist-sized, completely blue, and covered with tiny blue tentacles that twitched slightly. Strangely, as soon as it touched his chest, it immediately attached itself to him, as though it had a mind of its own.

“It’s very odd, but also a very fascinating power.” For the first time, there was surprise in his eyes. Even with his level of Willpower, he still could not analyze what this thing was made of! And this was coming from an Energy Machinist who could not even reach Resonance Skills.

This kid…

For the first time, he began to have a bit of faith in his young friend, Garen. At first, he thought that with the ambush and betrayal to him, as well as the murder of Third Brother, the Black Flood Party and Blackboard were more or less done with. He thought it was over, and there was nothing left but inevitable death, but he never thought there might still very well be a chance here.

He was just lucky, to be saved by the young one he had saved once before. Just like that, he escaped the misfortune of being caught by the enemy at the first chance, and now he might actually have a hope of escaping this completely.

An Energy Machinist with merely Level Three Willpower…

He looked at Garen in front of him again, a ray of hope finally rising in his eyes.

Suddenly there was a flash of red, and a group of Predators appeared from underground abruptly, pouncing straight at the three of them, who were still running.

Roar!

Garen flicked his fingers several times in succession, and with a few soft whooshes, his powerful physicality meant that the sharp stones he had shot out as secret weapons nailed themselves into the Predators’ heads, wiping most of them as soon as they were in sight.

“They’re just Level One Predators! Don’t delay!” he roared, and drew a long sword that had been hanging beside the Big Wild Wolf. Bending over and slashing once, he cut fiercely at a Predator right in front of him following the Big Wild Wolf’s assault.

Sinno also learned from him, and blocked one of the Predator’s pounce attacks with her sword.

The three of them hastened up and quickly left the few remaining Predators behind, rushing forth without even looking back.

Although Garen’s current Living Secret Technique, the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, was not the type for head-on attacks, he still had his foundations from his original fighting techniques, as well as his own Ten Thousand True Technique, a summary of everything. If he just relied on his foundations in secret techniques and was not hit face-on by Willpower impact, even a Level Five pilot would die if Garen ambushed them. But if it was a direct confrontation of Willpowers, he would only be able to take a Level Three pilot’s impact at the most.

The head-on fighting power of the seventh grade Hellfrost Peacock Technique was really not that strong. After all, he mostly created forces such as his squads, in the world where secret techniques were everywhere, practitioners of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique were mostly targets to be protected…

Kekkekkekke…

A piercing laugh came from ahead, and a pale grey shadow quickly pounced at Garen, who was at the very front. It was very fast, much faster than most Level One Predators, so it had to be at least Level Two.

This Predator had waited for the other Predators to rush out as scouts before it made a move itself, so it evidently had the makings of sentience.

It wore grey rags on its body, and they could tell that this was probably once a woman with a decent body. But now its nails were sharp, just like knives, and it somersaulted in mid-air as it clawed at Garen. If these claws landed, even the external armor of a Level Two Mech would crack.

Naturally, Garen’s body was nowhere near as hard as Mech Materials, but his speed was not something Level Two pilots could match.

He watched the claws come at him, this was his first time fighting a Predator above Level One himself, without relying on the Big Wild Wolf, and just purely using his own fighting power and the quality of his Living Secret Techniques.

“Eagle Stream!” Garen barked, and used the move he was most familiar with from the Crouched Eagle Talon, his arm accurately diverting the claws from the side, and then both arms blocking the Predator’s two claws tightly.

Die!

He suddenly used his explosive force, and actually jumped up from the Wild Wolf’s back, charging into the Predator’s waist and hitting it with his knee.

His knee just happened to smash upwards from the Predator’s knee, ker-chak!

Amidst the intense noise, the Predator opened its mouth in silent agony, its waist almost broken in two. It crashed hard into the ground beside them, and was motionless.

Garen floated lightly back onto the wolf’s back, his knee bleeding slightly. Although he has used the hardest part of his body, his knee, to hit the softest part of the enemy’s waist, the hardness of a Level Two Predator’s body was still beyond his expectations, so he still hurt his right knee.

But he had also objectively tested his current fighting power, using his own abilities and quickly finishing off the opponent in the instant before the Level Two Predator could use the Void Mind Force to attack. If the opponent used that power, however, he might be in trouble. And as for Level Three Predators, unless his body was strengthened up another notch, and he could also get the first advantage, there was no other way for him to break past the surface of a Level Three Predator’s defensive skin.

Thankfully, the Hellfrost Peacock Technique was the best at recovering from injuries, and add that to the help from the potential points, it meant that as long as Garen was not dead, he would be able to heal from even the severest wounds on his own. However, when it came to injuries in Willpower, the secret techniques and potential points would be powerless to help, this seemed to be a completely different thing.

“Nice technique!” praised the Sixth Divine Wind General from behind him. “Your fighting skills look like that of an expert, not a bit more and not a bit less, precise and accurate.”

“You flatter me. No matter how strong my fighting skills are, if my Willpower can’t even break past others’ force fields, it’s all pointless,” replied Garen with a laugh.

“I hear that there are powerhouses among the Energy Machinists who strengthen their own bodies, they absorb martial arts powerhouses, and if they can withstand the strengthening, their future potential would be boundless,” said the Sixth Divine Wind General, shaking his head. “Of course, you’re also an Energy Machinist, so naturally you would also know that.”

“Yes, I do know a bit about that, but that form of strengthening can only be done by oneself to themselves, if you modify someone else, that’s illegal.” Garen nodded. Of course, he was not worried about his modifications of Sinno, because radiation people had no rights… and were not protected by the law. By that he meant normal people, those without radiation.

“Illegal? Stuff like the law depends on who decided it. Haven’t you heard of a rule called special treatment? The law changes according to special situations as well,” said Sixth meaningfully.

“Are you saying that according to the law, certain people can be modified by other Energy Machinists?” Garen asked. “True, this stuff happens all the time, it’s no surprise.”

“But there must be a high standard of selection for fighting skills like that, right?” Beside them, Sinno spoke softly for the first time in a while.

“It’s a very cruel selection, I hear only one out a thousand gets chosen. The thousand of them must be free from any previous genetic strengthening, and they’d all be thrown into a ring to kill each other. Only the final survivor can receive the special treatment and be modified,” said Sixth calmly.

“What if the last two kill each other?” asked Sinno.

“Then they wait for the next round.”

For a moment, all three were silent. Even Sinno never thought that there would be a group of people even more tragic than the radiation people. Only one survives out a thousand, such cruelty evidently could not be on the right side of the law.

The rest of the journey was relatively safe, after the three of them avoided a large group of Predators and the Search Mech team occasionally scattered around the sky, they quickly realized that the many Search Mechs were starting to retreat, while the number of Predators just kept increasing. Sixth decided it was because the Flying Predators would be here soon, and once they appear, the advantage the Mechs had in the sky would be instantly reduced to nothing. In order to avoid too many casualties, the Mechs had to retreat quickly.

And they just happened to use that short period of calm to finally reach the Secret Region of the Energy Machinists on Garen’s map. And when they saw this region, none of them could have guessed that this place actually looked like this.

Chapter 965: Close Call 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There was an oppressive flock of black flying birds in the sky, with eagles, gulls, and even tiny sparrows, or strange-looking colorful birds. There were countless translucent strings connected to the bottom of the birds, and these strings were all connected to a huge, enormous shadow at the very bottom.

It was a giant oval-shaped platform, like a silver moving castle made of silver. It even had some things that looked like chimneys sticking out, constantly spewing black smoke.

Garen and the other two rode on the Big Wild Wolves, looking at the huge moving castle platform in the sky ahead of them. They were all kind of stunned, and completely at a loss for words to describe that big guy, which was at least several thousand meters large.

“Just those few birds would actually be able to move such a big thing?” Sinno murmured, she could not believe that merely several thousand birds would be able to tow such a terrifying castle. It had to be at least several thousand tons, and it was made of metal to boot.

“It probably has an anti-gravity device, the birds might just be there to lead the way,” said Sixth in a deep voice, it was also his first time seeing the Energy Machinist’s Secret Region. He glanced at Garen, and noticed that the key-like item in front of his chest was glowing slightly. That was the logo of the Energy Machinists, without that thing, they would not be able to see that large thing even if they were even closer by. The whole Secret Region only showed itself automatically when Energy Machinists approached, or rather, it was always in an invisible state to start with. Only those who were shielded by the force field of the Energy Machinists’ key deserved to see that huge castle.

“I know we can already see it, but in truth it’s quite far away. That’s because the Region itself is too huge, and the weather is good today, without any fog or clouds, that’s the only reason we can see the whole thing clearly. Alright, let’s continue on our way, it should still be about an hour away,” said Garen softly.

The other two nodded, and the three of them rested slightly, towed by the Big Wild Wolves, before they continued to rush towards the gigantic flying castle.

****************************

“Damn it!! You sure run fast!”

Barroom!

There was a huge sound accompanied by an explosion of red light, and a dark blue humanoid Mech holding twin swords slashed at a decently-sized hill in front of it, as though venting its anger. The red light and energy virtual attack shattered the hill into pieces, earth and grass flying everywhere. But before the spray could get too far, it was rapidly melted by the black smoke, turning into ash and vanishing.

“Lord Fourth, according to the test results, they probably did not get far. The Sixth, Masanra, was grievously injured, and he would surely be unable to move unassisted, so someone must be helping him! Not only did they rescue him from the battlefield afterward, they should still be taking him away from the area through the night, wandering around everywhere,” a soft voice said from one of the two slightly paler blue humanoid Mechs standing behind the Fourth Wind General, it was the one on the left.

“What do you suggest? Sixth has the Willpower barrier that can prevent tracking, Illusory Light. Even in the whole Blackboard Region, his Illusory Light is among the best skills to block Willpower. Even I can’t track him,” Fourth asked with a cold snort.

“It can block Willpower waves, but it won’t be so easy to block other signals,” said that subordinate darkly.

“Aura and Biological Radiation don’t work well in the radiation belt,” said Fourth coldly. “Lingering Willpower will also be blocked off by the barrier.”

“Not those usual ways, I mean… deduce it using the highest possibility.” The subordinate chuckled. “My lord, think about it, the Flying Predators will be coming any time now, and at this point, even we have to retreat into the regions to defend ourselves. And there are so few of them, so if they want to survive, they only two possible choices.”

Fourth’s eyes instantly lit up.

“You’re right, I’ve been relying on technology too much, I forgot that even basic deductions could lead us to clues. Not bad, you!”

Fourth nodded, his tone becoming considerably more gentle.

“If they want to avoid the Flying Predators, one option for them is to find a place and hide themselves completely, hiding their scents and falling into deep hibernation, so that they would have a certain chance of avoiding the Predators. And the other option, would be to hide in a secret area that’s even safer.”

“As expected of my wise lord!”

Fourth laughed coldly.

“And now we have people guarding all the large regions, plus they’re too far from here. They’re in a rush, so they would not possibly choose somewhere too far away, it has to be somewhere nearby. And there are just two safe spots around here, both belonging to the Underground Rebel Army.”

“The Underground Rebel Army’s secret spots have already been closed down completely,” said the other subordinate softly.

“Oh? Are you sure?” Fourth looked at his other trusted aide.

“Certain!” replied the man steadily.

“Then this might be slightly troublesome…” Fourth touched his chin in the cockpit, deep in thought.

“My lord… There might be one more thing that you seemed to have forgotten,” the subordinate who had spoken first said again, a hint of a smile in his voice.

“Oh? Do you mean…” Fourth paused slightly. “The Energy Machinists’ Moving Castle? Could the person he rescued him be an Energy Machinist? Is it really such a coincidence? Energy Machinists are few and far between, at such a critical moment…”

“According to our observations, there weren’t any footprints or similar trails left behind, but we found many marks that looked like they came from a pack of wolves. Evidently, there might be surviving groups of some wolf-like creature around here. If the opponent is an Energy Machinist, they always have had many tricks up their sleeves. It would not be impossible for them to temporarily tame a few Wild Wolves to help them escape using chips. After all, these Wild Wolves are no more than Level One creatures at best,” said the man with extraordinary confidence. “Besides, according to my observations just now, among the wolf tracks, three of them were headed straight for the general direction of the Moving Castle, without any hesitation. This, together with your general sense of direction from before, sir…”

“Let’s go! No matter how unlikely it could be, let’s go to the Moving Castle!” Fourth humphed coldly. The Mech leapt from the ground, blue flames shooting from its back, making the cape on the Divine Wind General’s shoulder flap in the wind. He flew like the wind towards the direction Garen and the others had run in.

The other two followed closely, leaving only the debris and chaos as a result of his venting behind.

***********************

The Moving Castle moved slowly. From afar, one could only see how slowly it was floating, and as they grew closer, the details of the Moving Castle began to gradually appear in front of the three of them.

Silver-white walls, complicated carvings that looked like electric circuits, blue electricity pulsing through it, and the occasionally buzzing vibration.

As they got closer, underneath the huge Moving Castle, there was a projection of a translucent, illusory green pillar of light. The pillar of light was like an empty cylindrical pillar, as though a green stick had descended down from the underbelly of the Castle and embedded itself into the ground, becoming the connecting apparatus for others to enter the Castle.

When Garen and the others were about to arrive, even from a distance, they could see at least several dozen people, some with more followers than others, lining up to enter the Moving Castle.

There was a large clock counting down on the green light pillar, indicating that there were only 32 minutes left, and the number kept decreasing.

The people lining up all wore different clothes, but they all had one thing in common, which was they all had an Energy Machinist key, either in their hands or hanging conspicuously somewhere on their bodies. They all had at least a few followers standing next to them, most of the followers were dressed neatly, and many of them had outstanding appearances or body figures. The male Energy Machinists were mostly surrounded by extreme beauties, and the female Energy Machinists had beautiful or handsome men standing around them. But the thing that surprised Garen the most was that these followers mostly had strangely dazed gazes, giving off a feeling of dispirited despair. They even wore black dog-like collars around their necks.

Garen’s arrival was not eye-catching at all, two more Energy Machinists had arrived at the same time, also rising a panther and a lion respectively. Jumping off the Wild Wolf, Garen lined up at the very end of the line, slowly waiting for his turn to enter.

The person in front of him was a fatty, who was currently lowering his head to play what looked like a high difficulty counting game on the small game console in his hand. Two other thin and tall people lined up behind Garen’s group, their eyes dark. They each wore a red bangle, one on the left hand and the other on the right, and it seemed like they were brothers.

The wind grew stronger, time passed slowly, and people entered the pillar underneath the Moving Castle one by one. After each one entered, there was a short waiting period, presumably for registration and verification of some information. It was not going very fast.

It was also Garen’s first time seeing other Energy Machinists in the real world, and as he observed the others, he found that most Energy Machinists dressed completely differently, and there was no rhyme or reason to them.

The fatty in front of him looked like a rich merchant, all meaty like that. He seemed to have noticed that Garen was watching him as well, and turned around to give Garen a friendly smile. His followers were two extremely seductive and beautiful young ladies, even if they wore long white robes, Garen could still vaguely see their sexy bodies and beautiful faces.

And the two brothers behind had their arms crossed in front of their chests, closing their eyes and resting, acting arrogantly as though ignoring everyone. They did indeed have the right to be arrogant, their Willpower forces seemed to be Level Four, the panther and the lion they were riding were both half-machinized elite units, which meant that they were evidently rich enough to own an experimental platform. Only by owning the other necessity besides the Biochemical Pool, the experimental platform, would they be able to properly modify a cannon fodder creature in depth, so that it would not disappear immediately. Other than lasting longer, its fighting power and other abilities would also be greatly increased.

The two of them also noticed that Garen was watching them, and the one that seemed to be the older brother opened his eyes coldly. He glanced at Garen, and then his gaze instantly locked on the Sixth Divine Wind General, who was lying on the wolf’s back. A hint of wariness flashed past his eyes.

“Hmph!” With a cold harumph, he closed his eyes again and ignored them. Evidently, the Sixth Divine Wind General’s Willpower forces made him exceedingly wary.

Garen knew that his own Willpower was too weak, so he would be noticed if he stared, so his eyes stopped wandering. He just stood quietly in line, waiting his turn.

Time passed slowly, and soon two more Energy Machinists joined the line. No one said anything, they were all here to leave their followers, those without followers could have left a long time ago.

“You have to fulfill your promise!” Suddenly, a cold woman’s voice came from the back of the line.

There was a young girl with one of the newly-arrived Energy Machinists, she had pitch-black skin that looked just like coal, and her body was unnaturally seductive and sexy. Even so, she was not the type that Energy Machinists here would go for. It was practically a miracle that the Energy Machinist took her in as a follower.

The Energy Machinist had a tiny black goatee, a bit like a middle-aged academic scholar from the ancient Hua-Xia dynasties, his aura calm and collected.

“Do not worry, I will naturally keep my word,” he replied to the girl’s question calmly, his expression unchanging.

The girl hmphed coldly, as though disbelieving, but she had no choice but to let it slide.

The Energy Machinist who looked like a middle-aged scholar also only had Level Three Willpower, like Garen. And he did not have any cannon fodder creatures with him either, having apparently arrived here through other means.

Chapter 966: Close Call 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen looked at the duo a little longer, and that middle-aged scholar turned around to smile at him, his expression gentle and extremely amiable.

After waiting for a little longer, there were only ten people left in front of them in the line, but just then, a giant White Snake-Necked Dragon came flying from the distant sky. It had large meaty wings like a bat, and was completely white, its long and graceful snake-like neck occasionally making some clear and slightly hoarse roars.

There were five or six people sitting on the Snake-Necked Dragon, all dressed completely in black, wearing black metallic helmets on their heads, and overall looking very mysterious.

The Snake-Necked Dragon, more than ten meters long, landed on the ground, and automatically began to shrink with a whoosh, turning into a ball of white light that flew into the ring of the leader of the black helmets.

“Space Equipment!” gasped an Energy Machinist from inside the line.

Garen was shocked too.

Among the Mech pilots, only Inherited Level pilots could use Space Equipment. The standard was naturally high for Energy Machinists as well, unless you were a Level Five Energy Machinist, you could forget about using one of these. And even among the Level Five Energy Machinists, only the rich and powerful could afford one of these.

As soon as this group descended, they did not even line up, and walked straight towards the round pillar entrance.

“Are you trying to cut the line?!” roared an Energy Machinist in the line who had been intercepted.

“Scram!” One of the black-helmeted people glared, and an invisible force field immediately exploded, sending someone flying out from the line.

“This force field!” Garen’s eyes dilated slightly, this force field reminded him of the Mind Force Field that Level Two Predators used the most often, the two were extremely similar in quality!

“You guessed right, the formation of the Predators might have something to do with Energy Machinists…” said Sixth, talking to him through Willpower.

“Don’t tell me that the Predator Tide was because of Energy Machinists…” Garen guessed.

“A lot of people have that conjecture, but be it on the Mother Planet or the other galaxies around, Energy Machinists are the most powerful, this is not a world revolving around pilots. The pilots’ territory is near the edge of the war with the Finite people, there are too many elites and peak-level pilots there, or even Regent Level ones. This is the inner region, it has always been Energy Machinist territory. So even if people are guessing that they have been experimenting on radiation people, nobody is willing to provoke the Energy Machinists,” explained Sixth calmly.

“Are we Energy Machinists very powerful?” Garen was not very sure about how peak-level pilots looked at Energy Machinists, so he asked somewhat curiously.

“Very powerful?” Sixth shook his head. “You’re not very powerful, you’re extremely powerful! You guys made the Mother Planet radiation belt, and not just here, but the radiation belts on other planets and in other galaxies, they were all once experimental sites for you Energy Machinists. In recent years, especially, with the Regent Level pilots falling one after the other, the Energy Machinists have been developing with unstoppable momentum, and with no balance or restriction. They’ve been getting terrifyingly strong, and exceedingly brazen.

“Then why haven’t I seen many Energy Machinists before this?” Garen said with a frown.

“That’s simple, because this is the territory of the Academies Union, but it’s still only a small piece of land. Once you leave it, you’ll find that Energy Machinists are king, every merchant fleet has an Energy Machinist in charge. An Energy Machinist of the same level is equivalent to several pilots, and powerful pilots also need Energy Machinists to fix and maintain their Mechs. That’s why the position of Energy Machinists aren’t threatened at all, and instead, most of the pilots will even protect them for sure. This is reality,” replied Sixth calmly. “The strongest ones on the Mother Planet are the Level Ten Perpetual Motioners, and at least half of the Perpetual Motioners are closely related to the Energy Machinists, in fact sometimes they are Energy Machinists themselves.”

“Perpetual Motioners… Level Ten…”

It was Garen’s first time hearing about even higher levels among pilots.

“Be it pilots or Energy Machinists, after a certain level, they will reach the point where their fighting power is unaffected by numbers. And after we break past Level Five, and go through the Resonance stage, that’s Level Six. The so-called Level Seven is what we call the Non-falling level, this is a drastic and fundamental change. Non-falling means that, in a war, when these fighters appear, they practically will never fall. Their power is strong enough for them to just bulldoze through, if an army has just one of these level fighters, unless the opponent has a powerhouse of the same level, they’ll just have to retreat. Non-falling Levels are absolute powerhouses even among the Inherited Levels.

Sixth explained it to Garen patiently.

“Of course, you’re just merely Level Three now, all this is way too far away from you. Level Ten… Perpetual Motioners might even live up to a thousand years. They are one step away from Regent Level, and that’s practically a living legend, living history… You have to understand, Non-falling Levels are already kings of an area, with one hit, they can easily destroy the balance of a planet, or a huge battleship. The rest is too far away from us, so there’s no need to think about it.”

Garen was quiet inside. Undeniably, forget Regent Level, even the Non-falling Level was way past the highest point he had ever reached. The Non-falling Levels could boss their way through space, and had already surpassed the peak-level destructive power he had in the Totem World. It was common to destroy a large battleship or the balance of the planet with just one hit. So it seemed that the Ancient Endor civilization might actually lose to how scary this world is. In any case, they could not match this world in terms of pure destructive power.

“The Non-falling Levels can destroy the balance of nature, so won’t it be easy to destroy all life on a planet?” Garen asked.

“It’s very simple, but with Energy Machinists around, they can fix and maintain the balance. Stronger Energy Machinists can even repair a planet. Non-falling levels usually were not allowed to fight on the surface of the planet, so most people went into space. Alright, let’s talk about something, it doesn’t matter even if you know now, so just treat it as listening to a story.” Sixth smiled, the Non-falling level had always been his life’s dream, and it was once right in front of his eyes, but now there was no more hope left for it. Even if the kid in front of him now had that potential, he still did not know how much he would have to go through to make it possible. If he was lucky, he might be able to see a glimmer of hope after a hundred years. If he was unlucky, even if he lived several centuries, it might be decent for him to have even reached Inherited Level.

As you went higher up in levels, the harder it got, and the larger the gap between stages, it was beyond the imagination of normal people.

As they chatted, they were soon at the front of the line, with only one person left in front of them.

Psst!!

Suddenly, a long crimson arc shot out from behind them.

“Sixth, where are you trying to go? You left on your own without telling your Big Brother, did I do something to offend you?”

An icy cold voice full of killing intent echoed through the sky.

Sixth’s and Garen’s expression changed drastically, and they turned around to see that long crimson arc headed straight for the three of them.

“He actually chased us all the way here!”

“Is that your enemy?” The fatty in front of them turned around and saw the long crimson arc as well, his gaze looking shocked. “Well I’ll be, it’s the Divine Wind General… An Inherited Level powerhouse, you boys sure know how to get in trouble!” His eyes turned, and he made way to the left.

“Hurry, you first! This is a matter of life-and-death, it is!”

“Go!!”

Garen blanked out for a second, but then he immediately picked up Sixth with one hand and Sinno with the other, rushing towards the pillar ahead without another word.

“Thanks, friend!” Garen quickly tossed him those words. “I’ll be waiting for you on the inside!”

“No problem! I’ve made friends with the five biggest troublemakers so far, and they’re all talents! Haha!” Strangely, the fatty patted his round belly, and laughed in a frank way. “You, brother, are the sixth!”

When Garen heard the last bit, he felt slightly exasperated too. He was lucky to have met such a wonderfully weird one, otherwise it would not be so easy, he would surely get into a fight if he tried to cut the line.

The fatty watched Garen and the others rush into the pillar, his eyeballs turning everywhere.

“Hehe, he dares to provoke a Level Six powerhouse even though he’s only Level Three, that guy must surely be a talent as well. If those boys and girls got together, then that would be really fun, they’re all troublemakers, and they’re all dastardly characters. With such a long line of enemies lining up behind them, they’re all people with big and powerful people out for their blood.”

“What do you mean by calling us characters, that sounds awful. We’re prodigies, prodigies, you hear me!?” A small and slender hand appeared at his waist, it was the pretty young girl that had always been on his left who had reached out and pinched his waist hard. She had also disguised herself as a Follower to escape with the fatty.

“Yes yes yes, prodigy, prodigy! You are the most dazzling prodigy in the Mother Planet, no, the whole galaxy! Beautiful, majestic, unrivaled, even your fart can kill off the best of the elites just by how good it smells!! No one else can, I mean, they don’t have the right to be mentioned in the same breath as you…” The fatty hurriedly flattered her against his will.

“You sure got a sweet mouth on you, but I like it.” The girl pulled her hand back. “You said it so well, does that mean you want to smell my fart?”

“Urk…” The fatty was shocked too, he did not think this girl would have no sense of shame at all.

“What? Are you telling me everything you said just now was fake?” The girl laughed coldly.

“I wouldn’t dare… I… I…” The fatty began to sweat, even if the lady was a beauty, that was still a fart! Who the heck would be willing to smell someone else’s fart? But he knew that this lady was never one to go back on her word, if she said she could do it then she would. What if…

“Are you trying to run!!”

All of a sudden, the Fourth Divine Wind General behind them yelled unabashedly, his Mech running straight for the green pillar. Inside the cockpit, his eyes were cold.

“Do you think I can’t get to you just because you went into the Teleportation Pillar?”

“Damn you! Who the heck do you think you are!! You dare interrupt me just when I’m building up the mood here, do you have a death wish!” The fatty turned around decisively and swore, changing the topic.

The Divine Wind General could not be bothered to reply, the Mech pulled out a long sword from mid-air, and directly swung it at the fatty. There was roiling black smoke on the blade, just a touch, and unless you had an Inherited Level defense protecting you, the only fate awaiting you was instant death.

“This is the Energy Machinists’ Moving Castle! It’s not your Black Flood Party’s backyard, Fourth Divine Wind General.” An old, white-haired woman appeared out of nowhere behind the fatty, and she stuck out her tongue, her bright red tongue instantly lengthening and shooting out like a sharp sword. It morphed into a metallic thorn, which crashed into the Divine Wind General’s long sword together with an immense Inherited Level force.

Bam!

The sword and the tongue collided, the blade swerving and losing its mark before it was pulled back into its sheath by Divine Wind General, as fast as lightning. At his level, he did not hesitate at all in attacking or retreating, and his every movement was as smooth as water.

“Inherited Level modification?” said the Fourth Wind General coldly.

The old woman was hunched over, looking so weak it was like she already had one foot in the grave. She stood in front of the fatty protectively, not saying a word, and just took out a small and delicate pale golden insignia, showing it off. It was like a pale golden patterned badge, hexagonal in shape.

When the Fourth Divine Wind General saw this badge, his expression changed slightly as well.

“Sir…” His two trusted aides behind him also saw it, and the smarter one reminded him softly.

“I know!” Fourth nodded slightly. “Sixth is useless now, he won’t be able to recover without more than ten years rest, so it does not really matter to the bigger picture if we kill him now or not. With a powerhouse from that family protecting him… I bet the Boss won’t blame me either.”

“A wise decision, my lord.”

Fourth narrowed his eyes, and was silent for a moment. He locked gazes with the old woman for a while, and even through the cockpit, it was as though he could sense that terrifying bloodlust, like a wild beast or a flood, hidden under her seemingly old and weak exterior.

Although she should be slightly weaker than him, it was still not worth it to offend that faction of power for someone like Sixth, who did not affect the bigger picture.

“Let’s go!!”

He turned around without another word, leading the two of them away quickly, turning into a long arc again and vanishing into the distant sky.

Inside the pillar, Garen and Sixth finally heaved a slight sigh of relief. They knew that this time, they were probably safe for real now.

Chapter 967: City of Nagadako 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

When the situation took a sudden turn for the worse, the fatty’s mysterious offer of help also confused Garen, Sixth, and Sinno slightly.

Even if he had a powerful background and protector, it should not be enough for him to offend an Inherited Level powerhouse for a complete stranger.

Inside the pillar, a person dressed in black robes, his face covered, stood in the middle quietly, looking at Garen and company coldly.

“If you want to go in, hurry! There are still people waiting behind you!”

“Alright.” Garen also knew that this was no time to talk, and he nodded at the other man, taking out his key.

That person reached out his hand and pointed at Garen and company.

Suddenly, there was a burst of bright light, and there was an intense white light everywhere. This phenomenon only lasted for less than two seconds.

By the time Garen and the others recovered, their surroundings were slowly growing dimmer, and returning to the regular level of brightness.

They were surrounded completely by a large semicircular barrier made of a blue membrane, and the floor was made of a grey-white metal. There were many semicircular bunkers all over the place, all squeezed together. These bunkers were like tumors growing on the ground, all of different heights and sizes, but they were all uniformly black hemispheres, with different titles and names hanging outside.

The three of them glanced across and saw that it was completely empty around, with not a soul in sight, and only the occasional blue line streaking across the sky above them.

“Moving with teleportation alone, how lavish!” The Sixth Divine Wind General sighed slightly. “Energy Machinists are rich and powerful indeed.”

“Welcome to the home of Energy Machinists, please walk forward to the teleportation point, you and your Followers will be teleported to a bunker room that was automatically assigned to you. In there, you can don your everyday living and exchanges, but if you wish to go to the battlefield to earn military credit and crystals, you’ll need to take three steps back. Thank you for your cooperation, this is Surveillance and Management: The Fifth Energy Machinist Star Tower.”

There was a sweet and lovable voice coming slowly from the sky.

“Let’s go.” Garen led the way out of where they had begun, leaving the Big Wild Wolf behind, because it would follow them back by itself. Sinno, on the other hand, struggled to carry the Sixth Divine Wind General, following closely behind Garen.

The three of them took three steps forward, and suddenly their vision blurred. In an instant, they had arrived in a pitch-black hemispherical room, and the ceiling above was made of a hard material that looked like stone. It was another meter above the tops of their heads, and underneath it, there was a secret trapdoor on the floor that led underground. Evidently, there was more space underground.

Garen went down for a look and found three more rooms, a large hall, and a washroom there. There was something that looked like a quantum computer in the hall, a large black metal shelf installed beside the computer. As Garen approached, words of welcome appeared on the computer screen, and the metal shelf beside it beeped twice before opening automatically. Inside, a mechanical table offered them fragrant dishes. Fish, meat, chicken, duck, vegetables, fruits, there was everything you could ask for.

There was even the option to choose what kind of food you wanted on the computer screen.

“This place is not bad,” Sixth said with some admiration.

“You might have to stay here for a while.” Garen nodded in agreement, this place was pretty good, the Energy Machinist Region was in charge of food and drink, and the living area was well-hidden enough. Even they did know which bunker they lived in, there was a teleport option on the computer, so everyone could come and go using just teleportation, which made things very convenient.

This also proved that most Energy Machinists stayed at home, cooping up at home to research things was evidently their favorite pastime, otherwise this place would not be designed like this.

“Most Energy Machinists are researchers, of course, if you meet a Modified Berserker, that is the direct opposite,” said Sixth softly. “They are the only group of Energy Machinists who like to fight, they feel that war is the most basic motivation for the evolution of creatures. Among the Energy Machinists, they have at least more than half of the power.”

Garen nodded.

“Alright, you guys go rest for now. Sinno, take better care of Sixth, I’ll go look for that little fatty who helped us.”

“Mn, okay. If possible, try to make friends with him,” Sixth told him quietly.

Garen nodded and stood in front of the computer in the underground lab, choosing the option to get teleported out.

With a swoosh and a blurring of his vision, he was instantly back on the platform he was previously on, and it was still quite empty around him, with no one sight.

The little fatty that helped him just now seemed to be waiting for him purposely, standing at the teleportation point as he chatted to the person beside him, grinning widely. When he saw Garen appear, the little fatty instantly approached him with a laugh.

“Gad.” He stretched out his hand.

“Garen.” Garen stretched out his hand shook Gad’s. “Thanks a lot for your help just now, or else I could have been in danger.”

“It’s no big deal, I just waited a little longer, that’s all, it’s nothing. I’ve always admired young people with potential who can get in trouble!” the fatty said with a chuckle. “So you don’t have to worry about it.”

“You helped me, and I’ll remember that,” said Garen calmly. “Tell me how to contact you, maybe next time I’ll have a chance to help you.”

“Aw, it’s no fun to say it like that.” The fatty waved his hand. “My favorite thing to do is make friends, my logic is that if anyone who can get in trouble and not die, then they are surely elites who can stand the trials of life.”

“That is a very interesting theory you have there,” Garen chuckled.

“Alright, let’s go, no more delaying,” said one of the pretty girls next to the fatty.

The fatty seemed to be slightly scared of this girl, and he nodded quickly.

“Alright, I’ll be on my way, you do whatever you need to,” he said softly.

Garen could tell that he had no intention of getting too close to Garen, and he would not even give his contact details, his helping Garen was a spur of the moment decision. So Garen did not say anything more, and gave way to let the three of them pass.

Together with the two beautiful girls, the fatty took a few steps forward, and they quickly faded and vanished with a whoosh, instantly transferring into the bunker and out of sight.

Garen stood on the spot and looked around him, and indeed, he did not see anyone else come out. Everyone stayed in their own bunkers, the whole area under the light blue protective barrier was completely quiet. Evidently, even the bunkers were soundproof, so that the whole place appeared to be deserted.

Garen stood on the teleportation point and looked around. There were countless bunkers around, squeezed together, at least several hundred if not a thousand, by rough estimates.

With a whoosh, that tall and thin middle-aged scholar showed up this time, and he still had that girl with coal-like skin beside him. The two of them maintained a strange distance, they were not too close, but neither were they too distant, so Garen had no idea what their relationship was.

As soon as the two of them appeared, they saw Garen next to them. The scholar smiled at him politely, and quickly took a few steps forward, disappearing from the spot with a whoosh.

Garen watched a few more Energy Machinists who were teleported there, each of them had Followers, and quite a few of them looked troubled, their expression dark. They were all evidently the type to consider every possibility, but at the same time they could maintain the basic pretenses of manners on the surface, and put on blatantly false masks.

He examined his surroundings for a while, and tried to walk out of this small teleportation point, but unfortunately it did not seem to work. The teleportation point was about five meters in diameter, and it was not a very large area. As soon as he stepped out of this area, he would be instantly sent back to his bunker. Garen did not dare to step back recklessly, and kept stepping forward instead, walking in circles. If he stepped back, that would mean going to the battlefield to earn military credit. He was not going to just rush into the battlefield without any prior knowledge of the situation there.

Since he had gotten all the information he could here, Garen went back to his own bunker, he just had to simply walk forward and out of the five-meter diameter to do that.

There was a computer in the underground room for searching information, and this computer was very strange. It was connected to a teleportation drawer, he just had to choose what he wanted on the computer, as long as it fell within the free one crystal range. Converted to the standard currency, one crystal could be exchanged for a hundred thousand Mother Planet Universal Units. A hundred thousand Universal Units was enough for an Energy Machinist to live here on the bare necessities for several years, given that they did not simply waste the money, of course.

Garen checked his account, the computer had been automatically connected to his own account. This one crystal was a free gift from the Energy Machinist Secret Area’s Fifth Star Tower to all the Energy Machinists who entered here, but other than this one complementary crystal, he had also earned a bit in the shop. After all, after entering Level Three, his status had changed. A Level Two Energy Machinist earned two hundred crystals in salary every week, and Level Three Energy Machinists earned five hundred crystals. Garen had just paid off the debt he owed for the advance payment of the Energy Machine Imprint, and now he still had three hundred crystals left.

“Three hundred crystals left, that’s enough.” Garen took out two hundred crystals directly, and put them into his designated account in this bunker computer. He was going far away, into the special ability space, and it might be a long time before he could come back. On the other hand, the Sixth Divine Wind General needed to heal his wounds, so he had to stay here to avoid the dangers outside. These two hundred crystals would be enough for the two of them to live here for a long time, after all, this was equivalent to twenty million Universal Units outside, as long as they did not buy things without thinking, it would be enough to last them several decades or even a century.

“You’re leaving?” Sixth was laid down on the black leather sofa in the hall by Sinno, quietly. He turned his head, and his eyes behind the black metal helmet stared straight at Garen, who was sitting in front of the computer.

“Yes, I need to know more about the way to progress from here as an Energy Machinist, my training method only goes up to Level Five, and I’m still missing a lot of basic prerequisites, it is way too hard to be self-taught in this field,” replied Garen determinedly.

The Energy Machinist’s Secret Area was only a temporary resting point for him, but to Sixth, this was the safest hiding spot. The Energy Machinists were unbelievably powerful, even the powerful factions among the pilots would never be able to oppose the Energy Machinists in this part of the galaxy.

“I will find a chance to take you with me,” Garen told Sinno. “But I can’t do it now. If you take care of Sixth here, though, he might be able to give you some tips.”

Sinno always had plenty of faith in Garen, and when she heard that, she looked at Sixth. Along the way here, she had also noticed that this mysterious Sixth person was evidently very powerful. When he was in full health, he had even saved the mysterious Garen, anyone who could do that was basically untouchable and so high above her in her eyes. Now she had the chance to be taught by him, this was naturally an unprecedented opportunity for her!

“After you leave, I’ll have to rely on her to take care of me. Don’t worry, I’ll help teach this child, but you better move fast. I’ll be fully healed in ten years at the most, and if you don’t return before then, I won’t wait for you,” said Sixth calmly.

Chapter 968: City of Nagadako 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Feel free to leave once you’re recovered, that way we’ll be even,” replied Garen calmly. “I’m only helping you because you saved me before, anyway.”

“That’s different, back then I didn’t go all the way to save you, so I still owe you one.” Sixth was very calculative in this respect.

“Whatever, it’s up to you how you want to think about it.” Garen turned around to look at Sinno. “But if you really feel like you owe me, then help me teach this child. Although she has no talent in terms of Willpower, her own determination and battle instincts are both extraordinary.”

When Sixth heard that, he properly looked at Sinno for the first time. “That is your request? If I train her properly, I’ll have returned the favor?”

“Yes.” Garen nodded in affirmation.

“No talent in Willpower… That is indeed a tad difficult, but as long as she’s not a complete Insulator, any so-called lack of talent is merely a fallacy. Most people can’t do it, but that doesn’t mean we Inherited Levels can’t,” said Sixth with a hint of pride. “Within five years, I’ll have her on the path of Willpower.”

As soon as he said that, Sinno was utterly shocked, but even Garen was slightly surprised. If he dared to say it so decisively, that meant that Sinno definitely had a chance of breaking past her limitations, and truly becoming a practitioner of Willpower!

“I– I can actually–!!!??” Sinno instantly stood up in agitation. She had previously been completely silent, but now even she was abnormally flushed and agitated.

“If I say you can, you can!” Sixth replied evenly. “Do not doubt it, just follow my instructions, and I guarantee that you will be able to break past your limits within five years.”

“Great, then it’s settled.” Garen was smiling slightly as well. Rather than have him undergo to modification and the mutated organ transplant, Sinno was better suited for this path. He was also happy for this strong young girl. And once he settled matters with this young one, he could properly focus on entering the Central Metropolis.

********************

Several days later…

Energy Machinist Region, the Follower Registration Tower

The tall black tower was surrounded by faint wisps of white clouds, and above it was the pale blue barrier. Outside the barrier, there were large flocks of countless flying birds.

There were many people going in and out of the black tower, and now, at the registration counter on the second floor.

In front of the black wooden table, a few Energy Machinists were standing and writing their departure time as well as their Followers’ approximate time of residence on the virtual screen, using their fingers in place of pens.

Garen quickly wrote down how long he planned to let his Followers stay here, it was about a hundred years. The free accomodation here stopped at ten years, and for every decade after that, it cost ten crystals in fees as a form of rental.

Although he had not anticipated that there would be rental fees here, the two hundred crystals he left for them would still be enough for them to use.

In the end, Garen took out his black key, and pressed it hard against the end of the completed registration form.

With a buzz, the key left an impression of its shape on the screen, and a complicated wolf-shaped image appeared on the screen as well.

As for the place of contact that he was leaving for, Garen directly wrote down the City of Nagadako.

“My friend, you’re going to the City of Nagadako too?” a slightly familiar voice appeared beside him.

Garen turned around and saw that it was that plump and fair fatty. He had approached Garen before Garen knew it, and there was a white screen floating in front of him as well, the words City of Nagadako written there as well.

“That place is the haven for learning modifier techniques, I’m very interested in modifying myself, so naturally I would want to go there.” Garen nodded. “What about you?”

“My home is there, I’m just going back.” The fatty scratched his head. He had changed into an intricate and bright red long robe, and he wore seven or eight gold and silver jeweled rings on his fingers, looking a bit like a villager who struck it rich. The blonde hair on the top of his head had been braided into many tiny braids, but the very middle of his head was completely bald, without a single strand of hair.

“I say, is this your first time going to the City of Nagadako?”

“Yes, it is.”

“Then don’t forget to visit the Star Core Plaza!” the fatty said, licking his lips.

“Star Core Plaza?”

“There’s the stone monument left behind the Regent Level at the very top there, and there’s a Royal Area as well, with the Nilan tree left by the Milky Way Empress there. The Selection Plaza underneath Nilan tree is specially dedicated to selecting talents for low-level Energy Machinists in the main city, and countless people participate in the selections there. A lot of the different sects, big and small, have people stationed there all year long. If you want to get the best and most legitimate Energy Machinists education, you have to join a sect,” explained the little fatty quietly.

“I have to?” Garen was slightly perplexed. “I’ve searched it up online before, the City of Nagadako should have libraries and teachers for a fee, right?”

“Of course there’s that, but there’s no way those self-taught independent Energy Machinists can progress as quickly as those cultivated in parties. And most importantly, only the sects have the two most crucial materials,” said the fatty mysteriously.

“What materials?” Another Energy Machinist who was filling up the form beside them also approached them, looking very interested. Evidently, not many people knew about the things the little fatty was saying.

“I mean the Star Cores and Set Secret Tactics!” the little fatty chortled.

“Star Cores and Set Secret Tactics?” It was Garen’s first time hearing about these two things.

“Most people don’t really know why the Energy Machinists in the sects usually have their own powerful abilities, and be it their own fighting power or that of their cannon fodders, they’re all much stronger than average Energy Machinists. They can even take the normal ones three-to-one easily. And the key behind all this is the Secret Tactics.”

“Then what about the Star Cores?” asked the Energy Machinist beside them, frowning.

“The Star Core? That is a necessary item for entering Inherited Level.” The little fatty raised a finger and wagged it. “Without it, no matter how talented you are, you won’t be able to reach Inherited Level. This is a natural resource, only sects have it, and if a regular civilian Energy Machinist wants to reach the Inherited Level, they only have one choice, and that is to join a sect.”

He reached out his hand and patted Garen’s shoulder.

“Brother, since your face is basically saying you’re clueless, I suggest you search it up on the Eliminet.”

With that, he turned and walked away, carefree, the form in front of him completed a long time ago.

That Energy Machinist who looked just as clueless as Garen exchanged a glance with him, and both of them clearly meant to go back and immediately search it up on that so-called Eliminet.

Garen returned from the Registration Tower, but he did not go back into the bunker, and went straight into the special ability space instead.

And finally, he got a reply to the message he had sent Celine through the special ability space. Everything was fine on Celine’s side, since she was growing stronger by the day, her family had retrieved her from the Blackboard Region ahead of schedule. In order to avoid the ensuing chaos, Celine had used her special rights to fetch Nono’s parents and younger sister away too. It was a stroke of fortune amidst the misfortune that they managed to avoid the chaos of the battle in the Blackboard Region now.

Garen quickly gave her a reply, telling her where he had been, and at the same time, he told her that he was going to the City of Nagadako soon.

Then, he arranged all the things he had prepared in advance.

He still had a hundred crystals on him, and since he could not increase his Living Secret Technique without the Red Peacock Stones, he decided to put that aside for now. It would take a long time to reach Energy Machinist Level Four, so he had no hope of that for now. Right now, the only way he was stronger than other Energy Machinists was in terms of his close combat skills, as well as the strengthening effect his Distorted Seed had on the Imprint Creatures.

It was the same creature, but Garen could use the Distorted Seed to strengthen it to three times its original power. In every other aspect, he was pretty much the same as Energy Machinists at the same level, and in fact, he was much farther behind many of the richer Energy Machinists. But the regular cannon fodders than had been tripled in strength would be enough to power up the elite creatures that could only be produced for the experimental table. This would give him an immense advantage. If used well, he should be able to gather a large number of resources quickly.

Upon hearing that little fatty’s suggestion, Garen went onto the website called the Eliminet. Its main business was in assassination and intel, and it was very easy for him to log on using the Energy Machinists’ intranet, but it would not work through the internet outside. There was a lot of information on it, and Garen bought a few things according to his needs. He did not spend too much, just over ten crystals.

After all the preparations were complete, he was without any worries for now. Garen sent a message straight to Mincar.

More than ten minutes later…

In front of the clear white door of light, Mincar had his hands tucked into his wide sleeves, standing there, straight as a pencil and as quiet, as he watched Garen.

“Are you all ready?”

“Yes, I am.”

“Once you get there, there are a few paths you can take. Firstly, you can join the selection and get the opportunity to join a sect, but that’s still too early for you right now. Secondly, you can find a place to work part-time, to earn your living fees, which are extremely high in large cities like this, so you should be mentally prepared. And once you go, it won’t be so easy to come back,” Mincar advised him.

“I understand.” Garen nodded. He had to go, if he kept messing around here, he may not be able to return to his original peak power of Level Five even if he did wait another few years. Unless he went to a large place, he would not be able to get more resources. And then finishing off the Seventh Divine Wind General and Fila would just be a foolish dream.

“In that case, I wish you the best of luck,” Mincar said softly at the end. He gave way, and took out a pink crystal gently, tossing it lightly into the door of white light.

Boom!

A beam of intense white light burst forth, turning into an illusory white image that gently moved forward to envelop Garen, who was in front of the door, into its embrace.

*******************

Outer space, on the surface of a desolate pale yellow planet.

There were many tall brown-yellow volcanoes standing on the surface of the planet, all of them glowing with a metallic sheen, thin and sharp. Beams of clear white light kept shooting out from the peaks, rushing into the sky like so many white pillars.

On the surface of the ground between the many volcanoes, many brown-yellow buildings were stacked up like pieces of junk, scattered without any rhyme or reason. Some were skyscrapers shaped like rectangular pillars, and many others had roofs shaped like scythes. There were also many airships of different colors and sizes ascending and descending in the sky, or else flying forward slowly.

Throughout the whole city, there were many white lights sparkling. When each light lit up, someone somewhere appeared or disappeared.

A long flow of people rushed out from the airship that had landed, while others walked out from the elevator at the bottom of the volcanoes. As soon as they came out, the many cab drivers waiting there would pounce. Each of them entered their respective cabs.

On the wide pale yellow road, the levitating cars flew away with their passengers, and more cabs took their place, offloading their passengers.

At the bottom of one of the metallic volcanoes, inside the huge yellow arch-shaped door, another wave of arrivals walked out of the large black door that looked like a veil of water.

These arrivals were all dressed differently, as though a large group of actors had mixed together before they could change out of their costumes. Some looked like rich merchants, others like students, there were workers, soldiers and commanding officers, some that looked like housewives, and even those who looked like beggars.

Of this crowd, among those on the left near the main door, there was a well-built young man dressed in a white skin-tight pilot’s costume, his long black hair falling over his shoulders, and his eyes constantly observing the situation from behind his hair.

His hair had covered up most of his face, and he looked disheveled. As he walked with the crowd, he was soon targeted by a cab driver as well.

Chapter 969: Star Core Plaza 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Good day sir, to where are we headed?” Asked the driver as he squeezed over, looking particularly brawny.

Garen looked at the filthy street around him, it was completely unlike the urban main city which he imagined, instead, it felt more similar to the time when he was going to the train station during the New Years back on Earth.

The street ahead of him was an unorganized mess. It was completely fenced up by a light silver metal bar, forcing those who wished to leave the street to go through two big inspection gates.

All the people within the fence were seemingly squeezing against each other. Shoulder-to-shoulder, Garen was completely surrounded by the crowd. It wasn’t just the energy machinists who had come out, but also a lot of taxi drivers who squeezed their ways in along with them. These drivers were abnormally passionate, some even doubled as a tour guide.

The man on his left was excitedly and loudly introducing the attractions of the city while simultaneously guaranteeing that he offered the best prices around as he pounded his chest.

However, there were multiple others doing the exact same thing all around the area, all with the same weird accent, as if they were reciting a badly translated script.

The comparably wider street ahead was even more chaotic. There were some people frantically sorting out their luggage, some holding their children’s hands outside while waiting for someone. There were even a few of them speaking on the phone through a holographic screen projected right in front of them.

The people in the crowd were moving all around, most of them were using a hovering trolley to port their luggage. Some had a scrolling screen floating above their heads as they moved, exhibiting some seemingly illegible red texts.

A cacophony of shouting could be heard. They were shouting out names, calling for their family members, yelling to maintain the order of the place, and much more, all blending together to form a disorderly mess.

It gave off the feeling as if he had arrived in a distant world.

Garen narrowed his eyes. Leaning on the door as support, he narrowly avoided being squished by the moving crowd.

“Bring me straight to the Star Core Plaza.”

The burly driver nodded, revealing a bright smile.

“Star Core Plaza? You must be one of the people taking the Selection Test, right? Coincidentally, I am going to bring two others just like you over there. Follow me, dear customer, we can take the express pathway over there.”

Garen followed the driver as they squeezed through the crowd, swiftly maneuvering themselves through the masses, exiting the street over the gap in the metallic alloy bar. There was an old-looking taxi parked over there. The car did not have any tires, but it was visibly spurting out a white flow of particles.

The driver opened the door and sat in the driver’s seat as if it was his second nature, Garen followed suit as he opened the door to the backseat. As he motioned into the car, he saw two others already seated inside, they were a boy and a girl. Both of them looked very young, looking no older than 20 years old.

The boy looked seemingly average. He looked meek and wore glasses, giving off a nerdy and frail vibe, despite having a more tanned skin tone. He seemed to be the introverted, silent-type.

The girl looked even younger, she was at most 17 years old. She looked extremely pretty and had a thin, lovely figure. Wearing a female white silk T-shirt, a micro mini skirt, and a pair of high denier black leggings, her chest perked up into two bulges under her shirt. Along with her pale and blemishless face, and her clear, watery eyes, she gave off the impression of a pure and beautiful young girl.

Looking at Garen who just sat in the car, her eyes suddenly brightened up. Quickly tidying up her hair, she had her hair styled in a short ponytail and long arched bangs that dropped down to her chin level, making her appear even more charming.

Without a doubt, even if Garen’s hair was even messier, his well-toned body figure and sharp facial features would completely blow the other guy out of the water. In addition to that, in this world, Nono was barely in his twenties, he was still extremely young. His neat combat attire only served to complement his charismatic aura.

He immediately gained the attention of the girl.

“Since you’re all going to the Star Core Plaza, y”all don’t mind if I grabbed one more passenger, right?” The driver chuckled as he turned his head over to the passengers in his backseat.

The three of them had no objections.

Once again, the driver left the car and started soliciting for customers. It seemed like he tweaked the translation system, for the language in which he was shouting happened to be one which Garen could not understand.

After a brief moment, he brought over a bespectacled girl. This girl did not utter a word, she merely looked at her watch and moved to the front seat of the taxi without even glancing at the three other passengers seated behind her.

“Alright, let’s head out!”

As the driver went back to the driver’s seat, he turned back and said out loud, “Let’s just get this out of the way, I’ll charge all of you a fixed price of 2 crystals each for the one-way journey.”

“No problem.” The glasses girl nodded, while the other two agreed as well, implying that the price seemed reasonable. Naturally, Garen nodded in agreement as well. Based on the reactions of the other passengers, this was a normal rate.

As the car slowly started to move, the green symbol next to the drivers’ window turned red, signaling that the taxi was no longer accepting passengers.

“The distance of the trip is 442 km. The fare is monitored by Flying Traffic Management. Please direct all complaints to the company support site along with the number plate of the taxi.” A sweet sounding female voice rang out loud.

Garen looked out to see the buildings they were passing by. Most of the buildings were constructed with a combination of light-yellow bricks and metal. As they moved further and further away from the volcano station exit, he could only see the vague shape of the huge volcano and the light pillar coming out from it.

Along the way, no one spoke a word. The girl was fiddling around on her phone, whilst the guy was doing some light reading.

As time passed by, they started to feel sleepy, all of them started to yawn. Only Garen was still completely energized, showing little to no sign of fatigue.

Bang!!

The car suddenly started to shake violently. A strong magnetic field suddenly passed by, one strong enough to disrupt the willpower energy field of the passengers.

In the midst of the screams, the passengers in the car got knocked into each other.

The people in front weren’t affected too heavily. The bespectacled girl knocked her head on the car door, causing some slight red flushing on her face.

Unfortunately, the people in the back were not so lucky. Garen was still fine, even if he lost control of his willpower, he still had his abilities as a martial artist. This amount of disruption and shaking was not enough to knock him off balance. However, although he maintained his balance, the girl by his side desperately grabbed on to Garen as a pivot point. Pulling his wrists with both her hands, her entire body limped onto Garen.

As the car stabilized, the driver in front started apologizing to his customers. He said that it was due to the magnetic storm in the air, he had no way of avoiding it. It was a natural disaster that would range from a few days to a couple hours. It was a very common occurrence in this area.

“I’m sorry…” Realizing that her body was stuck onto Garen’s, the girl suddenly flushed red in with embarrassment.

“No worries.” Garen gently smiled.

The girl let go of one of her hands, her face still blushing. Looking like she was still a baby, she frantically used her free hand to tidy up her mini skirt, whilst still holding on to Garen’s wrist tightly with her other hand.

Just as she let go of her other hand.

Clang!

With a loud sound, the car started to shake again once more. It was a second wave of the magnetic storm.

The inside of the car suddenly fell silent.

The girl screamed out once more. This time, Garen did not manage to maintain his balance fully. The magnetic storm seemed to affect a human’s balance as well. If he was alone, he should have no problem maintaining his balance, but now, one of his arms was being pulled by the girl, throwing off his center of gravity. With a tug, Garen felt his body being dragged off-balance to his right.

Garen exerted strength with both his arms, but he noticed that his muscles were losing strength. Looks like a magnetic storm was not something to be underestimated, it did not merely affect one’s willpower. However, as he started to lose strength, his life secret technique started to kick in within his body. His arms suddenly felt a surge of strength, flailing around looking for their respective centers of gravity, stabilizing his body at once.

“Ahh!” At this moment, a feminine moan sounded from his side.

Garen felt something wrong. Looking to his right, he immediately felt embarrassed.

As it turned out, while trying to maintain his balance, his right arm, still being held tightly by the girl, fell directly onto the girl’s thigh right below her mini skirt. He could feel the gentle warmth her thigh was emitting. As that was happening, the girl frantically pulled onto her skirt with her other hand, trying to push away Garen’s hand. However, unexpectedly, as she was trying to cover herself, it made it look like Garen had reached his hands under her skirt, touching her between her legs.

“Err…” Garen quickly pulled back his hand. As someone who has lived as long as him, this was the first time he had accidentally taken advantage of someone else in this manner.

No one noticed the scene that just happened between the two. Everyone else was busy trying to sort themselves out. The silent bespectacled boy was in a corner holding onto his head in pain, panting out loud. The driver in front was swearing out of frustration. The bespectacled girl took out a hand mirror and was touching up her make-up.

“Sorry…,” Garen muttered softly.

“It… It’s okay.” The girl shyly lowered her head.

After those two incidents, the trip continued on without a hitch, the four passengers also found a common topic of discussion. With the topic of the magnetic storm in mind, the four slowly started to open up and chat with each other.

A round of self-introduction occurred. It turned out that, save for the bespectacled girl in front, all three of the backseat passengers were here to participate in the Selection Test.

The girl’s name as Liz, the bespectacled boy’s name was Accord. They didn’t state where they were from, but from the looks of it, they were both at the standard of a Level 3 energy machinist. However, that was normal, participants in the Selection Tests were most commonly Level 3 energy machinists, Level 4s would be considered rare, and Level 5s were almost never-before-seen in these tests. All Level 5s who were aged below 30 would have no doubt gotten themselves a guaranteed entrance, they did not need to bother with these sorts of selection tests.

“There are a lot of participants for the selection every year, but I heard that the judges this year were all veterans of void battlefields, they are from the standard Actual Combat Faction. They most likely will put more attention towards the actual combat prowess of the participants.” The bespectacled guy frowned. “My weakest area is actual combat, this is not looking good for me.”

“I think most people aren’t that well-versed in actual combat either, so we’re all essentially in the same boat.” Liz seemed to have recovered from her flustered self earlier. She continued, “Looking at the past few years, the tests were largely focused on the participant’s abilities in calculation and analyses. From my perspective, a greater emphasis given to actual battles might even make it easier. After all, most people have trouble with actual battles… Most of the participants of the selection test are energy machinists from the theory faction. If we do engage in actual battle, we’d all be on even playing grounds.”

“Logically speaking, that would be the case. It’s just that my Flowerbird’s Prison is still far from perfect yet…” The bespectacled guy said, rather regretfully.

“It’s the same for my Rainbow Chicken as well. How many of us Level 3 energy machinists do you think have fully developed a skill perfectly?” Liz comforted him; it seemed like she was a pure-hearted young girl with a kind and gentle personality. “Don’t worry too much about it. There’s probably some guy out there who’s even more worried than you. Don’t you think so too, Big Bro Garen?”

Garen nodded.

“Actual combat isn’t actually as hard as you guys think. However, if you lack the actual experience, you have no choice but to compensate for it with a stronger concentration. As long as you’re not the one making a mistake, you will win. It’s a slow process, don’t rush it.”

Out of the three, he had the greatest stamina and also a great physical condition. His physical appearance had utterly overshadowed the bespectacled guy. He spoke with sheer confidence, giving people no reason to doubt his words and easily managing to convince others.

“Big Bro Garen, can you give us some tips on which areas we should pay attention to during an actual battle?” The bespectacled boy softly, but sincerely uttered.

As he brought up this topic, the girl Liz also shifted her gaze towards Garen. Although she was still slightly blushing from the incident earlier, it seemed that she had calmed down a lot.

Chapter 970: Star Core Plaza 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“For actual battles… The most important thing to focus on would be the weak points. The weak points I’m speaking off aren’t just the simple flaws of a person, but rather, it’s the difference in ability between you and your opponents in different aspects. You may have a high speed, but if your opponent has a faster speed than you, then your speed would still be a weak point in that particular battle. Similarly, if you have enough strength, but your current opponent is still stronger than you, then even if your strength was your best attribute, it would still be a weak point, and vice versa. Thus, in a duel, the most important key is to test out the waters first, trying to measure your opponent’s average stats and how it compares to yours. Then, using this information, you can maximize your advantages over them to target their weak points. In theory, this is common sense, but it’s not as easy as one might think in actuality.”

“True, the theory behind it seems simple enough, but to be able to do that, we must first know how to do it as well as disallowing your opponent to see through you first. In addition to that, there are also issues about hidden abilities and other issues to worry about. How troublesome.” The bespectacled boy meticulously pointed out his concerns as he nodded in agreement.

Garen nodded.

“You’re a sharp one, well this will all be down to the methods and strategies you use against your opponent in an actual battle.” Looking at the earnest attitudes of the two, they definitely were not your average energy machinists. Being able to reach Level 3 at their age, they were undoubtedly geniuses in their own right. Even for Garen, if it was not for his unusually high level of intelligence, he would not have been able to reach the level of a Level 3 energy machinist so fast. Making some friends in this place would not be a bad idea.

He started to teach them some basic and easy-to-understand actual combat tips and techniques based on his experience.

During this trip that barely lasted 2 hours, Garen had answered countless queries from the two. Though the bespectacled boy seemed to be clueless about actual battles, his theoretical knowledge was unbelievably vast. Even for areas where Garen did not have a solid grasp on, he could easily break it down into simple explanations, displaying a strong analyzing capability. The girl was comparably more average, but she would still be considered a genius under normal circumstances.

The three decided to participate in the test together and became friends.

As the taxi continuously moved forward, the crowd density in the street also started increasing; the same could be said about the number of cars on the streets, leading up to a traffic congestion. Looking at the front, the roads were filled with cars closely packed due to the backed-up traffic. However, the driver seemed to be unconcerned by the situation.

“Only slightly more than 10 minutes more till we reach the plaza, that place is full of selection test arenas, with fifty-one big arenas and ninety-nine small ones, to get a grand total of one hundred and fifty arenas each hosted by their respective sects. These sects are spread through the major continents of Planet Naga, where they have an extremely low population and high amounts of resources. The bigger arenas are built by the bigger sects, whilst the smaller ones are built by the smaller sects. Every year, this place would have a huge inflow of foreigners, all coming for the selection tests, creating a strong and prospering consumer chain. There are hotels and inns all around the place, finding a place to stay shouldn’t be an issue. The fees are also quite affordable, considering the ease of accessibility to food and other services which can be found everywhere around the area. There are some shops that even sell selection test preparation booklets.” The driver introduced.

“One hundred and fifty sects. Why are there so many sects on Planet Naga?” Garen just realized the City of Nagadako referred to an entire planet. According to the explanation by Accord, it was located in a two-dimensional space separate from where the Mother Planet was.

“There is more than just that, Planet Naga has thousands of sects. As long as you reach Inherited Level, you will have the right to apply to form a sect. The etymology of the naming for ‘Inherited Level’ comes from this system, the word ‘Inherited’ refers to the permission to let your skills be inherited by the next generation.” Accord muttered. “The ones that were able to build arenas over here are all at least Overlord level sects in at least one aspect.”

Garen nodded. In a blink of an eye, ten minutes have passed, they had finally escaped the traffic gridlock and disembarked from their ride.

They alighted at a crowded street and moved towards the sidewalk on the left. Looking at the direction the taxi drove off in, they saw rows of tall pale yellow buildings on both sides of the road.

In front of them was what seemed like a park surrounded by a black, human-height fence. There was a flashing red light installed on the fence, on top of it was a sign. The sign had the phrase “temporarily unavailable” written on it in five different languages.

Peering in from outside the fence, one could see a few cylindrical structures being erected from the ground, with different patterns and images drawn on top of them. Some were complex and pretty, whilst others were minimalistic and abstract. It gave off a grand, yet at the same time elegant feeling.

There were a lot of people taking photos with their friends in front of the fence.

Garen noticed that in this city, not everyone was an energy machinist, most of the people were just your average joe, with no willpower control at all. Only one third out of all the people had some form of willpower wave emitting from themselves, Garen was secretly keeping count of the ratio as he walked past the crowds. Out of this group, there were approximately half of them who only have the willpower of a Level 1 or 2 energy machinist. The remaining people were mostly Level 3 or 4, with the youths being Level 3s and most of the Level 4s being at least in their 30s. He also observed a few extremely rare cases of Level 5s, with most of them being seniors, with even the youngest one being in his 40s.

“Are there really no younger Level 4s?” Garen muttered in disappointment.

“Of course there are, but most of them would have already been recruited as elites by the major forces. A lot of them would also already have met the requirements to aim for the Inherited Level. These people wouldn’t usually come around these areas filled with commoners. Even if they did, they would at the very least come disguised, we probably wouldn’t even manage to recognize them.” Liz shook her head.

The three walked up to take a closer look, besides the “temporarily unavailable” text, the sign also displayed that the opening day was tomorrow.

“Looks like it’s not open today, why not we come back tomorrow then. I’m going to talk a walk at Figures Plaza, you two want to tag along?” Accord asked softly.

“Figures Plaza? Why not!” Liz nodded. “I’ve long wanted to see the stone plaque left behind by the Regent Level Greats of the past!”

Naturally, Garen did not object to this plan. He had nothing planned for the day anyway, and there was no harm in going over to take a look.

Figures Plaza was located at the right of Star Core Plaza, following the flow of pedestrians along the street through a dark alleyway, they soon arrived at a wide area filled with white plaques.

There was an oval signboard floating in the sky above them, displaying the names of each of the figures and their respective plaque location.

There seemed to be a lot of tourists walking around here, most of them were carrying their backpacks and pulling their luggage, whilst others were like Garen and company, carefreely walking around the area.

Some distance away, there were a few minotaurs in black uniforms around the area as security guards. These minotaurs all had the head of a bull and a body of a man, wielding Mountain-splitting Axes. Their body was completely pale yellow, in a similar shade as their weapons. They stood still without even budging slightly, almost as if they were statues. If not for them slightly puffing up their chest and exhaling a white gas occasionally, no one would even think that they were living creatures.

These minotaurs were all clad in sets of yellow armors, the huge axes they were wielding was at least 3 meters in length, erected on the ground like a pillar. What stood out the most in this scenery was the rows of clear advertisements etched on the side of the axes.

‘Silver Hawk Battleaxes, Ever Triumphant.’

‘This product is fully sponsored by El Processing Division’

‘Additional Sharpness Level 2 – Sharp-Edged Gazette’

‘Alice-brand Chocolate, satisfaction with every bite…’

Lines and lines of advertising slogans completely ruined the intimidating image of the huge minotaurs standing at a height of more than 2 meters tall.

There were even some people getting close to the minotaurs and talking photos beside them.

There was even a beautiful young girl who went forward and placed her arm around one of the minotaur’s shoulder for a chance to take a photo.

“Look over here, big boy!” She loudly shouted.

The minotaur slightly tilted his body towards the camera, his gaze was sharp. In an instant, his bulky muscles started to tense up, as he let out a small smile.

Snap!

With a flash of the camera, the girl happily gave the minotaur a crystal as payment before running back to her friends.

“This is painful to watch…” Liz said while her eye started to twitch.

“At this day and age, even guards have to make a living somehow…” Accord said as he readjusted his glasses.

The trio followed the crowd as they walked through the entrance guarded by the minotaurs, entering a sea of stone plaques. They were all erected at around five to six meters in height, with little to no blemishes on the surfaces.

Garen was originally quite interested in this, he planned to carefully look through the plaques left behind by the great Regent Level figures. Unfortunately, just as he walked in, he was completely stupefied, he couldn’t recognize any of the plaques, and he had could not read anything engraved on them as well. On the other hand, Liz, who displayed a great linguistic foundation, was even able to read a few of the plaques out for the other two.

A lot of other tourists were facing the same problems as the trio. To them, these Regent Level plaques were no different from any random stone plaque, there were no visibly different parts, leaving them disappointed,

A lot of the tourist just swiftly took a few photos before leaving the place.

Garen originally thought that there would be some remnants of the Regent Level figures that he would be able to sense, but after noticing that the stone plaques had remnants of being artificially restored before, he was completely disappointed.

The three also stumbled upon a record stone plaque. According to the records, this place has been destroyed and rebuilt a total of 4 times. It is now used merely as a symbolic landmark for Nagadako, representing the union and alliance between the Regent Levels here back then and the beginning of the Nagadako’s golden age in history.

After a tour of the area, the three found their efforts to be fruitless. They just took a group photo and went to the nearby photo-printing shop. After receiving a photo each, they left the area as well.

While they were pondering where to go next, they stumbled upon a tour group that seemed to be checking their headcount. The trio decided to just follow the group to find a place of accommodation.

They soon arrived at a row of small inns a short distance away.

Outside the inn, there were countless colorful flyers posted all around the area. There was also a small group of hover-motorcyclists waiting outside, chatting with each other whilst taking a smoke.

The three of them walked into the inn, Garen decided to take a single room. This showed him how expensive the cost of living here was. Even for a simple and unsightly inn like this one, it cost him 50 crystals a night. He only had 100 crystals left on him at the moment, so after this transaction, he would only be left with 50, and that had yet to take into account his expenses for his meals.

Fortunately for him, the boss gave him a complementary meal consisting of what resembled a braised meat. It was sweet and sour, and did not taste that bad.

The people in the opposite room from Garen’s room seemed to be having an argument. The walls lacked a good soundproofing, and so the noise made its way into his room. He could hear various noises, and even occasionally the sounds of babies crying loudly.

Under these conditions, he might as well start on his calculations for his Level 4 model while waiting for the opening of the selection tests tomorrow. He originally did not plan on staying the night in this inn, but he did not expect Star Core Plaza, which boasted to be open every day of the year, to be temporarily closed.

Chapter 971: Arena 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After some time, Garen was awakened by the sounds of a heated argument.

“My stuff isn’t something anyone can take,” a seemingly young male voice rang out loud.

“The stuff I want is not something anyone can deny me!” A cocky female voice calmly said.

What followed was a loud and violent shockwave.

Garen was awakened from his calculations. He let out a big sigh and looked up at the ceiling that was flaking dust. The shockwaves continued one after another, seemingly never-ending.

He stood up, walked to the window, drew open the curtain and looked down where two small silhouettes were standing facing each other on the street below. In between the two silhouettes, a red and a blue shadow kept rapidly colliding with each other. From the looks of it, the blue shadow seemed to be at a disadvantage because every time it got hit it would let out a loud moan.

It could clearly be seen that the two silhouettes were both below the age of 20. The boy was in a blue shirt, with a silver bracelet around his wrist, emitting multiple spots of silverish light. The blue shadow in front of him seemed to be getting forced into a corner.

On the other hand, the girl was waving a golden can in her hand, giving off a prideful aura. She was instructing the red shadow to attack continuously, almost as if the waving was conducting the red shadow’s every move, like a whip continuously whipping forth.

The willpower shockwaves from their battle caused ripples that were at least Level Three in strength. Looking at the core of the battle where the strength was most intense, it was even at Level Four degrees of power.

There were many Energy Machinists surrounding and watching the bout. In this location, it was impossible to bring out large-sized Self-Defense Evolved Creatures. One could only carry super-small-sized strong types or utilize space equipment, but both of these methods were far too expensive. Even if this was the city of Nagadako, a super-small-sized evolved creature was not something the average energy machinist could afford.

This was comparable to having a person earn tens of thousands bucks per month when the average monthly income was two or three thousand bucks. Everyone would be using a cheap ten buck wallet, whilst the person would be using a pure leather wallet worth thousands.

It’s the same in this situation. Those who own super-small-sized evolved creatures would at the very least be from a wealthy household. It was considered a brand and a status symbol after all.

However, at this point, the two were displaying an unmovable arrogance in their actions. The boy was being suppressed so much that he had started to lose his breath. His blue shadow started to move slower and slower, becoming clearer and clearer. Slowly, the shape of the shadow could finally be made out, it was a tiny hummingbird that was completely blue in color.

As the hummingbird’s movements slowed down, the other red shadow also slowed down its attacks in response.

Surprisingly, the red shadow was a palm-sized red skeleton. The red skeleton was floating in the air, with a pair of red wings flapping rapidly on its back.

“Hand out the stuff,” the girl put out her hand. “Your hummingbird is no match against my skeleton.”

“Red skeleton! Hmph!” The boy coldly sighed, his face pale. Finally, with a toss, he threw a brownish ball to the ground, turned around and left.

The figure of the hummingbird slowly started to fade away, then disappearing into the boy’s body.

“Looks like you at least have some tact!” the girl chuckled as she picked up the brownish ball. She glanced around at the surrounding energy machinists, then returned to her cold emotionless expression as she turned around and left the area.

Garen let out a breath in amazement.

“This is indeed the central city, where the energy machinists are the most advanced. The elites from all around the universe have gathered here. To be a Level 4 energy machinist at the age of 20, this degree is far crazier than me.”

Garen did some calculations and it would take more than 10 years for him to successfully get to Level 4. However, in this 10 years, there’s no telling how far these geniuses would have already progressed.

“This time, the body I got was certainly average in the willpower aspect…” Garen let out a sigh, closed the curtains and continued his calculations. All achievements relied on slowly accumulating small steps.

Word of the battle between the hummingbird and the red skeleton started to spread. Soon, a recorded video of the two’s confrontation got uploaded to the Internet. Garen took out some time to use the inn’s public computer to watch the video, but he couldn’t learn anything from it. The skills used by the two were one tier higher than his capabilities so it wasn’t something he could learn at this time.

The elite evolved creatures they used were at least Level 4 or 5 in terms of combat power. He might not even be able to withstand their attacks even back when he was in his strongest state and in a mech.

After all, he was only testing the waters.

After an uneventful night, early in the morning of the next day, Liz and Accord came over and knocked on his door. Garen had already washed up earlier. The three then proceeded to make their way towards the selection tests.

At the time, plenty of youths planning on taking the selection tests had already gathered at the Star Core Plaza. Almost all of them were below 20 years old, with barely a handful of people in their 20s.

Walking amongst the crowd, Garen and company did not look anywhere out of the ordinary.

Bong!!!

A melodious clock bell sounded from within the Star Core Plaza.

The fence started to vibrate and instantly faded away, almost as if it was never there in the first place.

At this moment, a mustached man in what seemed to be yellow royal garbs walked out from inside. He pridefully surveyed the people in the crowds who were eagerly awaiting their entrance.

“Routine maintenance inspection has just been completed. Please prepare to enter the arena. Today, we will open five big arenas and all small arenas, so please make your choice wisely. Let me give you a word of warning, do not be overambitious. Try to select an arena of a sect that is most appropriate for your personal growth, and not based on the overall strength of the sect. Of course, stronger sects will naturally give you more advantages and benefits, but you will also have to take up the corresponding duties. If you do not have the mental preparation to take up these duties, you may leave.”

He paused briefly.

“Everyone will only have the opportunity to select their arena of choice once. In the end, the combined ranking competition will be held.”

After he finished talking, he slowly raised his hands, turned around and shot up into the sky, disappearing into the distance in a flash.

At the gate of the Star Core Plaza, the crowd stood there briefly in shock, before slowly funneling themselves into the plaza. Everyone who entered the premises would have an internal map of the plaza appearing in their hands.

Garen also received one, the map clearly stated all the specialties and characteristics of the arenas, what sect they belong to and where their actual location was.

As the three walked through the masses of people whilst Garen was looking down at his map, Liz suddenly patted him on his shoulder.

“Look, it’s the hummingbird user!” Liz said softly, looking at the direction of the person on her right.

Garen and Accord, followed suit to see that it was indeed the hummingbird user from the battle yesterday. The boy in the blue shirt had a cold and sour expression, his silver bracelet looked matte and dull, it was not as bright and shiny as it was in yesterday’s battle. It seems like it wasn’t activated yet.

In front of him, there was naturally a small sized area being created as he moves. This was not because people were intentionally making space for him out of respect but rather because his body was emitting a slight willpower energy field that forcefully parted the crowds in front to him like the red sea.

“It’s a Level 5 energy field… There’s no doubt about it, he’s one of the big three seeded participants in our competition area,” Accord said as he adjusted his glasses once more.

Garen nodded, he could also feel his opponent’s strength. For him to attain a Level 5 energy field at his age was amazing. Moreover, it seemed like he was not a Level 5 energy machinist, but rather just a Level 4. He used an experiment platform to create his own evolved beast to reach Level 5.

“He was the one who fought against the red skeleton girl yesterday night right below where we stayed. He lost the match though,” Liz muttered softly.

“You guys saw it too?” Accord asked. “Him, the red skeleton user and another person, they are considered the prodigies of our competition area. We need to be cautious of them during the combined competition.”

Garen and Liz nodded in agreement.

These types of geniuses amongst energy machinists all have terrifying calculating prowess. A lot of the tactics used by them would be very hard to be assessed by their opponents and all of them would already have a fully prepared a counterplan and battle tactics. They most likely have already been through countless simulation battles. So in that battle, they’d much rather skip all the tactics and just fight through a clash of strength.

In these situations, for rookies who have to face the hummingbird user, they would be out of luck.

After assessing his current strength, Garen came to the conclusion that if he faces this person, his chances of winning were extremely slim. The speed of that hummingbird was too high, there was no conceivable way for him to dodge it. Furthermore, that Level 5 energy field was not something he could break through easily.

“Let’s go,” he said with a frown on his face.

“Mmm.”

The two others followed closely behind as they proceeded to the arenas deeper in the Plaza.

The Star Core Plaza was filled with countless dry and withered trees of all shapes and sizes. The dark blue color of the dried tree bark made the trees look like weird evolved creatures, neatly stationed at two sides surrounding the plaza.

In the plaza, there were also a few minotaur guards patrolling the area. They looked the same as the ones from Figures Plaza, with the only difference being the lack of advertisements on their axes, giving off an intimidating aura.

The crowds slowly separated into the respective branching roads in the plaza, the people walking around Garen and company has also visibly decreased.

“Where are you guys planning to go? Which sect do you plan to choose?” Accord asked while seemingly recording something into his PDA.

Liz grinned, “I’m headed to the Dragon Light Sect. I’ve been admiring the Dragon Light of the Dragon Light Sect for ages now, it’s very pretty and strong.”

“I still haven’t decided,” Garen shook his head whilst looking at the major sects listed on the plaza map. The list was completely filled with the names of countless sects.

Accord kept his PDA and chuckled.

“It must be fate that the three of us would be here together today. I’m planning on going for the Star Cloud Sect. I don’t know if I’ll be able to make the cut or not, but this has always been my dream since I was young.”

“That’s one of the Big Three Sects… How ambitious!” Liz said in admiration. “Too bad I don’t have the confidence to try it. We don’t have absolute God-given talents, our willpower is also not strong enough, the odds of getting into one of the Big Three Sects are too low.”

“Well, that’s still better than me, I still have no clue about what sect I want to join,” Garen chuckled bitterly. He looked towards Accord and asked, “Do you have any suggestions for me? Accord?”

In this trip, the three could be considered fellow students of the same level. Accord had great knowledge of theoretical aspects, Garen was filled with combat experience, and Liz was good in a linguistic aspect. With that, the three managed to help make up for each other’s weak points, forming a decent bond through their interactions. Energy machinists are mostly rational people, there would not be anyone who would want to decline these types of mutually beneficial relationships.

Chapter 972: Arena 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“My only suggestion for you, Garen, is to choose your own path that you think suits you best. Don’t focus on the strength and size of the sects. Of course, the strength of a sect can have a positive impact on your growth, but during the distribution of their resources, those who lack the prerequisites would naturally receive fewer study resources, as it would just be a waste of time and resources. It’s not worth the candle,” Accord answered sincerely.

“That’s true. I’m more suited for Frost Radiation style energy machines. Are there any in this list that belongs to that type of style?” Garen asked once more. If he just goes by the information displayed on this map, there would be no feasible way for him to make an informed choice. The characteristics of each sect were not something that could be easily you could search up on the web, there would be a lot of minor details people who are unfamiliar with the sect itself would never understand.

Accord answered while looking at Garen seriously.

“To be honest, Garen, your actual combat prowess is absurdly strong, if you feel the styles that use Frost Radiation suits you the best, then you should narrow it down to the sects that specialize in Frost Radiation. Give me your map, I’ll help narrow down the list for you, then you can choose one that fits your style the best. I’ll also key in some of the key strengths and weaknesses of these sects for you.”

“Mmm, thanks!” Garen nodded.

“Don’t worry about it. My actual combat ability was too weak, as you were telling us about your combat experience, I was covered in cold sweat. If you didn’t bring up a lot of those tips and common problems, I would most likely be destroyed as soon as the fight started. Let’s benefit from each other,” Accord calmly said as he adjusted his glasses once more.

He grabbed Garen’s map and rapidly pointed out thirteen Frost Radiation based sects and their respective arenas. At the same time, using his PDA, he made minor changes to the contents on Garen’s map, displaying the characteristics and styles of these sects.

It could be seen that he was still a baby in the woods, still treating others with a heart full of sincerity.

After a while, Garen was handed back the map, it now displayed thirteen bookmarked locations for the sects and arenas.

“What are you guys doing?”

Nearby, a group of young Level 2 energy machinists seemed to have gotten into an altercation with another Level 3 energy machinist. The noise was loud enough to be heard even from their location.

The Level 3 energy machinists had her hair in small pigtails, her face was showing an arrogant expression.

“How can good-for-nothing trash like you, being only Level 1 and Level 2, even wish to come to Burton Island? Keep on dreaming!”

This person did not release their energy machine but rather lunged over personally. Surprisingly, he used a set of very familiar combination combat skills. Suddenly, two gill-like breathing organs appeared on the back of his hands, continuously spraying out a white gas. In an instant of explosive acceleration, every punch packed he threw packed two to three times the original power.

The group of Level 1 and 2 machinists were only kids, they stood absolutely no chance against him. All of them got knocked to the ground in an instant. Many youths started surrounding them to get a look at what was going on, but none of them attempted to stop the fight but instead, they just stood there looking at the scene coldly.

There were countless similar cases that had happened in this place, a few of strong young energy machinists, to reduce the competition in their arena, would hire an even stronger person to stand guard outside the arena to take care of their competitors.

Garen surveyed the surroundings, he had already memorized the basics of the map in his hand, carefully keeping it back into his pocket.

At this moment, the Level 3 energy machinists who started the fight glanced over, his sights falling on Garen and company.

The others also looked on as if a show was going to happen.

Garen looked around once more and realized that amongst all the people nearby, their Level 3 strength was considered quite high in comparison. Furthermore, the path they were headed was directly past the place where the fight took place.

There were a lot of people coming to this area, most of them seemed to have similar dressing styles, with pale yellowish accessories on them, seemingly all locals. On the other hand, the handful of people in varied clothing all had slightly stronger Willpower and spoke with weird accents. Clearly, they were from a foreign land.

Garen also noticed that it was not just the three of them. Everyone from foreign lands was at least Level 2 or 3, one whole tier higher than the average of the locals.

“Let’s not stay here, we need to move,” Accord said softly.

The three minded their own business and started to walk away, this made the tense face of the guy who started the fight to slowly relax. He looked over, gave them a smile and left the scene.

The group of knocked out energy machinists was left out cold on the ground.

After walking a bit more, Liz was the first to part ways. The arena she was headed to was just up ahead.

The three exchanged their contact information via their energy machinists key, promising to keep in contact. Briefly, after that, Accord also walked off on his own. He seemed to be quite mature for his age and very introverted, but he might also be slightly overambitious. He had looked down on Liz slightly but was able to see Garen as an equal. His tone towards Garen was very respectful.

Garen had too much life experience and has also seen countless types of people. He had no trouble noticing the slightly hidden intricacies in Accord’s shifts in his tones, though he didn’t point it out.

A person’s life passes by in the flash of his eyes, who knows what type of person Accord would grow up to be, how he would treat others. He would never have a condescending attitude and look down on others, especially towards this group of energy machinists who posses frightful calculation and analytical prowess.

After the two left, he looked up the bookmarks on his map and the sects he was interested in, then he picked out what he deemed to be the most suitable sect and arena for himself.

******

At the far right area of the Star Core Plaza near the outer wall, in a middle-sized sect arena, a long queue of people was patiently waiting to have the judge register their names.

While the queue was still growing, there were also people who left the area dejected, after their application was rejected. On the other hand, those who managed to would proudly or calmly enter the arena into an empty space, patiently awaiting instruction from the staff.

Two middle-aged men in white uniforms stood at the sides coldly staring at the surroundings. They had a sign hanging on their chest, clearly displaying the words “Ice Rainbow Sect”.

Garen had been in line for quite some time and it was finally his turn.

Walking to the front, he tapped his energy machinists key in front of the judge in charge of the registration.

Beep.

The key started to light up, the display screen in the hands of the judge also started to display the related information.

‘Garen, 21 years old, Level 3 Energy Machinist, Training Method NIS Universal Simplified Version, Place of Birth: Frontier.’

“Level 3… Not bad,” the judge nodded, signaling Garen to wait at the side.

Garen breathed out a sigh of relief as he walked towards the group of other participants who passed. The Ice Rainbow Sect was one of the strongest major sects below the Big Three Sects, it was a Southern Sect. The arena over here was used only for preliminary testings. There would still be a secondary testing once they head over the headquarters of the sect where it was intermediate in difficulty.

Garen chose this sect because his current body did not have a good enough Willpower quality. It was at best considered average, if he attempted to head over to even better sects, he would no doubt be rejected instantly, wasting his opportunity.

This opportunity was something that everyone had only once a year. If he gets rejected this time, he would have to wait an entire year for his next opportunity. He did not have so much time and money to afford such a luxury.

It seems like the first batch of selection tests had already been done earlier, he was part of the second batch.

After thirty minutes, the number of registered participants had reached the quota. The people who still wish to register would have to wait till after this batch of selection tests are finished. However, no one was in a rush, the Star Core Plaza was open almost every day of the year, the big arenas are opened based on the schedules, whilst the small arenas are always open. As long as you had the potential, it didn’t matter which day you come to take the test.

Garen stood in the middle of the group, he was surrounded by energy machinists’ Willpower force. His Level 3 Willpower did not stand out at all in this group. Almost everyone here was Level 3, with the exception of two Level 2s who were extremely young, being at most twelve years old, and a Level 4 young man who was resting his eyes with his arms crossed.

The judge in charge of registration earlier headed up on stage and took out a sign to put on stage. It displayed the rules of the selection tests. It seemed like he was too lazy to even speak, he just pointed at the sign and went off the stage back to his seat.

The sign said:

Second Selection Test — Elimination Competition. Top three based on actual battles, where ranking are decided based on the number of wins. Those who win 10 consecutive matches may stay. The remaining people will leave the arena.

Third Selection Test. Test for the appraisal limit. Those with high scores may stay, those with low scores will leave.

Final Selection Test. Participate in the combined selection test, those who ranked within the top one hundred will stay.

The rules were simple.

Immediately, two people had already taken the stage. It was a fat boy and a small girl. They familiarly released their respective energy machines, one was a big human-sized spider and the other was a flying swordfish. They were both elite templates. The two jumped straight into an intense battle. The spider’s limbs were as sharp as a knife’s edge, it could also spit out webs to trap the opponent; whilst the swordfish could instantly use an explosive acceleration to pierce through its opponent and had terrifying firepower. The swordfish was repeatedly weaving through the spider webs set up by the spider.

The judge was below with a computer positioned vertically, with the built-in camera pointing towards the stage, seemingly recording the battle.

Garen was stood at the side, observing the battle while paying attention to the two middle-aged men in white uniforms. The two were clearly men from Ice Rainbow. They did not talk to the judge at all, making the atmosphere very tense.

“What the hell?” The energy machinists on his side started whining.

Garen noticed that a batch of participants consists of 30 people, but they would only take in the top three and the people who managed to win ten battles consecutively. This made the competition very intense. Of course, taking the top three was much easier than to win ten battles consecutively.

Given that the Level 4 energy machinist was definitely going to take a spot, no one bothered even trying to take his spot form him.

As for the remaining two spots…

Garen looked through his belongings. He could not bring the biochemical pond over, it was left in the energy machinists’ secret region. Except for his energy machinist key, he did not bring anything at all.

He started to consider how he would rank within this group of people.

He had no way of using energy machine evolved creatures, he did not have an experimental platform, nor did he have a micro-type evolved creature. He was in the same predicament as a lot of the other energy machinists here. There was a specialized public-use biochemical pond somewhere nearby and everyone was allowed to use it once for free. However, he was out of time, the Ice Rainbow Sect mainly targets support-type energy machines, focussing primarily on self-strengthening. Unless absolutely necessary, it would be better to just display his own self-strengthening skills.

Whilst the people on stage were still fighting, Garen saw a few energy machinists coming out from the public-use biochemical pond. There were flower-like items floating around their bodies. Energy Machinists then had countless tricks up their sleeves and he had no idea what those flowers were.

“Black Jade Dragon Beast!!!”

Suddenly, a loud insuppressible roar sounded from afar, almost as if it was the roar of a rhinoceros stampeding towards the arena. This caused everyone to look over at the direction where the sound was coming from.

“Black Jade Dragon?!” The judge’s face lost color for a brief moment as he stood up and looked over at that direction, his face showing signs of jealousy.

Chapter 973: 975 Sect 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Not just him, even the two men in white uniforms were also looking in that direction.

“This has already been the fifth case of special talent prodigies this month… As expected of a big arena.”

“Even if we’re not some talented prodigy, we will still eventually become stronger than them!” A youth said in a dissatisfied manner.

Most of the people here were still kids, only a handful were full-fledged adults, Garen included. Listening to the words of the kids around them, even if these energy machinists had strong calculative abilities, they still lacked emotional stability. At this moment, they could not help but feel a surging feeling of jealousy.

Using this chance while everyone was still saving their full potential, Garen quickly surveyed the people surrounding him. The few youths with a more veiled willpower were all remaining calm, fully confident in their abilities.

“Without an experimental platform, my potential is only limited to my close combat. I’m definitely at a disadvantage against these guys. Whilst everyone was still saving their full potential, I should use this opportunity to go on stage and earn my 10 wins as quickly as possible. No point trying to snatch away others’ rankings.”

A few thoughts flashed across Garen’s mind. He had been hiding, intentionally keeping a low profile, befriending Accord and Liz, all for two goals. The first was to fully understand the unfamiliar situation surrounding energy machinists. Now that he has a clear grasp of the situation, he learned that the energy machinists world has the same rules as any other world. As long as you don’t cross the line, everything is based on your own potential.

The second… Although he originally still had his worries, there had not been any problems in such a long time, there shouldn’t be any big issues happening soon.

He remembered the series of unfortunate events that happened back in the Blackboard Region which he was still slightly haunted by.

At this point, the fat boy on stage had already been defeated. To be defeated by a little girl who was at least seven or eight years younger than him, He frantically fled the arena in shame after he bowed to the judge.

“Now… It’s time to test it out. Let’s see whether or not my original hypothesis is true…”

With a swift leap, he lightly landed on the stage, standing right across of the little girl.

Hiss…

The swordfish next to the little girl started making snake hissing noises.

Without useless chatter, the two just nodded at each other.

“Be careful…” Garen said softly. Before he even finished, he furiously stomped down onto the floor.

Bam!

The entire stage started to shake, an ice blue mist radiation started to rapidly spread, completely engulfing the little girl and her swordfish in an instant.

A small black paper box suddenly appeared in Garen’s hands, inside it contained strong Willpower forces.

Hiss… A void shadow stopped in front of the box in that instant, as if it was a car that activated it’s emergency brakes. It was the small swordfish. If Garen had been even slightly slower in taking out the box, he would have been pierced through and been forced off the stage.

“I concede,” the little girl’s face turned green as she uttered out those words. In that instant, the terrifying strong Willpower forces started to expand, if it was released, her opponent’s Willpower storm would have hit the entire stage. The first victim would be the swordfish, it was very likely that her swordfish that she spent so long creating could have had its Willpower core annihilated in an instant. She wasn’t even sure if she could manage to survive through the Willpower storm herself. Hence, at that key moment, she stopped her attack.

The little girl jumped off the stage, and started bawling her eyes out. Carrying he swordfish in her hands, she left the selection test arena in tears.

Garen started to feel the guilt of bullying a child, but he swiftly discarded this notion and focussed on his next opponent.

At this point, the icy cold energy radiation had completely covered the arena’s stage. This made the energy machinists on the bottom quite concerned. This level of energy field radiation required him to maintain his energy every minute was a frightful task. They realized that he wasn’t just your average joe.

A thin and tall man jumped up to the stage. He looked like a stick of bamboo and he also did not have any energy machines. He relied only on his speed when he jumped onto the stage just now, he attempted to run circles around Garen and shoot him with the freeze ray he was equipped with. Unfortunately for him, the freeze ray seemed to have no effect on Garen. On the contrary, he started to get frost bites from the frost radiation, forcing him to helplessly get off the stage.

The next two who came up to the stage to test their luck were also helpless against Garen. At this point, the frost radiation had reached around -20°C. Even staying up on the stage for a brief moment would start to numb their entire body. It slowed down not just their physical movements but also their thinking speed.

Garen only used two moves so far, releasing the frost radiation and occasionally holding up the paper box. This huge threat he had on his hands was so strong that even the Level 4 energy machinist couldn’t help but put his attention on the box, showing a worried expression.

“The fourth.”

Looking at his fourth opponent was what seemed like a twelve-year-old child, Garen silently counted in his heart.

Ding.

Suddenly, his key emitted a crisp notification tone.

Liz’s voice could suddenly be heard.

‘Garen, I have successfully entered the sect, good luck to you.’

‘Good luck,’ Garen replied.

Using the paper box in his hand to accurately block his opponent’s attacks, after a few more tries, his opponent helplessly got off the stage once more. When the willpower accumulated in the box had reached such frightening levels, even the Level 4 would not be able to block it.

The judge sitting below speechlessly shook his head. Garen employing this sort of strategy had made him slightly disappointed, but since Garen was able to release frost radiation for such a long time, it proves that Garen had a certain talent, so he just turned a blind eye to it.

Next, Garen used the same paper box tactic and his extreme reflexes, he managed to completely stall his six remaining opponents into submission via the effects of his frost radiation. If not for the ruling that they had to finish the battle within a fixed amount of time, he wouldn’t have been so successful.

After successfully winning his 10 matches, Garen decided to quit while he was ahead, so he voluntarily leaped off the stage. This shameless act shocked not just the judge, but also the two men in white uniform.

At the end of the day, Garen only managed to show his extreme reflexes and his ability to release frost radiation, with literally nothing else.

The schedule then quickly progressed to the second phase, the test for their appraisal limits.

Garen barely passed it. The Ice Rainbow Sect’s requirements were not that high, Garen’s modification of the traditional Frost Radiation showed that he had a certain degree of modification and combat prowess. Thus, even though his appraisal limits were not that high, he was still given a pass.

Looking through the results slip of the test, Garen saw the stats for his bottleneck limit stated clearly at the very top.

“Bottleneck is Level 5, that’s not too bad…” Bottlenecks represent the maximum Level one can manage to achieve, just that the amount of time needed in the later levels would be much longer. “50 years…” Garen was speechless.

This estimates shows that in theory, he could reach the level of a Level 5 energy machinists, but that would require at least 50 years of continuous hard work.

However, the most important part was that he successfully passed the test. A few of the Level 4 limit participants had been rejected. Garen learned that even though he barely made the cut, his quality as an energy machinist still wasn’t as bad as he originally expected.

The final combined selection test was also a fluke. The others were having awesome battles, but only Garen was holding onto his paper box and being a one-trick pony. The opponents were all extremely wary of him and chose to avoid him as a whole. After all, there was no need to actually, since the rankings were based off win counts. Thus Garen got past the test easily once again.

Furthermore, he did not break any rules, the paper box he was using was completely built by himself, so it abides by the competition regulations.

In the end, there were a few people attempting to imitate his tactics, but they were easily defeated. This showed them that this type of tactic was not something anyone can pull off, it required an inhuman reaction speed and reflexes.

Out of the final five that passed, Garen was one that was being despised by the others.

Every batch would have around three to five passing participants, Garen was seen as the worst performing person in this group.

After several hours, all of the candidates have been confirmed. From a total of five batches, there was a total of twenty people.

There were three Level 4s ranked at the very front. Surprisingly, the hummingbird user Garen had seen earlier was one of them. However, it was understandable, since the Ice Rainbow Sect is one of the strongest sects outside the Big Three Sects. For him to choose this sect was no surprise at all.

“Howmet, look at this…” The judge saw that the numbers were almost enough, so he softly asked at the direction of one of the white uniformed man.

The white uniformed man slowly floated up and landed on the stage, looking down at the passing candidates.

“These ones should do,” he reached out and grabbed a short dark golden cane from his sleeves and lightly waved it around. The tip of the cane suddenly shot out a white light, as if a peacock spreading its feathers it turned into countless light spots, slowly falling onto everyone below.

“Grounded Prison, Command, Aiz!” He roared in a low voice.

Immediately, the light spots on the bodies of the candidates started to lightly vibrate.

They started to shoot out both weak and strong pillars of light, pointed at the sky.

These light pillars could go up to 2 meters in height, with the shortest barely reaching the top of their heads. With the uneven heights, it looked like a white light pole behind their backs when looked from afar.

Garen’s back also had a pillar of light, it wasn’t too tall or too short, it was in the middle amongst all of these pillars.

The white uniformed man pulled back his hand and slowly flew above all of the candidates. Everyone that his sight scanned started to feel shivers down their spine. The sharp gaze of those two eyes felt like a knife cutting through your skin, making the person ache.

“Nilo, these people, are there too many of them?” The other white uniformed man flew past and said softly. The two bodies were emitting a strong inheriting level energy field as if it was nothing, forcing everyone’s head downwards.

“It does seem like we have too many.” The white uniformed man Nilo nodded his head and frowned. His gaze landed on Garen. “This person…”

“His performance was decent, although he made use of some exploits, his reflexes are extraordinary. In addition to that, he seemed to have made great self-modifications, adapting the radiation and halo-type energies. I’d say that he’s fine,” the judge’s voice rang from below.

Nilo nodded.

“You, you and you!”

He simply pointed towards three others, they were the three people with the worst performance other than Garen. “You may leave. Your ranks are too low, you’ve been eliminated!”

Instantly, the faces of the three candidates changed drastically. It was two white-collar-looking men and a model student-looking girl and after they got called out, their faces looked horrible.

“On what basis!!?” One of the white-collar guys interrupted out loud. “Our performance wasn’t the worst! On what basis do you want us to leave!” He purposely increased the volume of his voice to cause a commotion.

“On what basis?” Nilo laughed coldly, “When I tell you to leave, you will leave! On the basis of me, Nilo’s, authority as the supervisor’s disciple!”

Garen looked coldly from the sides. He was indeed not a match for these people, but after he had experienced their attacks, wanting to beat these people would not be a difficult task. After all, the difference in strength was not that big. The only thing was that a lot of people would dismiss his skills as nothing but fancy flourishes.

Chapter 974: Sect 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The moment they heard he was the infamous supervisor’s disciple, all three people hesitated slightly. The first person who stepped forward earlier turned timid immediately and retracted his outstretched hand.

“Then why is he still standing here despite being ranked last?! You’re doing this illegally! I refuse to accept this!” The young girl yelled loudly unexpectedly.

“You refuse?” Nilo narrowed his eyes. He glanced at Garen but saw that the expression on his face was unperturbed, as though the current situation here had nothing to do with him at all. Suddenly, an ill feeling rose up in his mind when he thought of another member of the sect who was very similar to him.

I strived for your reputation but you remained indifferent without being flattered or even showing the slightest hint of gratefulness? Fine! That’s just fine!

Nilo had always been petty. Now that he was unhappy as well, the four people including Garen looked like eyesores to him.

“I refuse to accept this!!” The girl continued to scream loudly.

“Then just refuse!”

A stern look flashed in Nilo’s eyes before he raised his palm up high and drew it towards the girl below.

Bang!

The stress of the invisible force field sent the girl flying at once. A splash of blood sputtered out in mid-air before she crashed violently against the sharp corner of the high platform. She rolled down and fell on the ground face up.

When Garen saw this scene, his mind tensed up slightly. He felt as if something was amiss and that his previous assumptions were beginning to show traces of being confirmed. Now that the selection quota had been fulfilled, those who had not succeeded would need to wait until next year before they could return. If he had to wait another year, would that mean that he would be left behind by his peers?

He glanced at Nilo and noticed that his facial expressions were becoming more contorted. The feelings in his mind which indicated that something was amiss became clearer.

Suddenly!

“All four of you can just get out now!” roared Nilo in a low voice irritably. Four invisible force fields were shot out in front of his body suddenly. The force fields wound themselves around the four people including Garen and flew out immediately.

Sure enough!

Garen was speechless. This was an unexpected disaster. He could vaguely feel that his assumptions had probably hit the nail on the head again…

While his body was suspended in mid-air, he felt a bout of dizziness from the lack of balance. While determinedly steadying his body, he saw that a few people in the crowd who were standing there earlier now had joyful expressions on their faces because of the misfortune that had befallen him. His mind remained speechless. Despite his best efforts to downplay everything, he could not shake off the bad luck of stirring up trouble.

It seemed as though he had been constantly encountering misfortune ever since Red Moon planted that unknown Willpower inside him. Terrible incidents had befallen him one after another continuously, simply making him a comet of disaster.

There was a ‘bang’ before all four people were thrown out far away again. Garen took a protective stance naturally. After rolling a full circle on the ground, he stood up quickly and did not resemble someone who was in a difficult position at all.

The examiner who admired Garen more than the others sighed faintly when he saw this.

“That person possesses the rare glowing abilities…” he continued to comment. The examiner himself was also threading on the path to become an expert in modifying glowing types. Therefore, when he saw that Garen was of this rare type as well, he was internally somewhat protective of him.

“That’s enough talk of that. Trash like him who can only resort to using tricks will still be useless no matter how much they practice. He’ll only be a waste of resources if we let him through,” Nilo waved his hand. “This matter ends here. How many people does our sect select every year? Do we still lack someone like this?”

The examiner was helpless and did not speak anymore.

On the other side, Garen’s face became slightly contorted. However, it was unrealistic for him to truly use his strength to force these elites to submit. The only thing that he could excel in now were the Big Wild Wolves. Unfortunately, the strengthened Big Wild Wolves only possessed Level One combat power that was close to Level Two at the most. Without an experimental platform, he could not use his Level Three Energy Machinist abilities to create an experimental piece of elite Energy Machinery at all. Thus, he had no other choice but to use tricks.

When he noticed that the examiner seemed as though he had given up completely, Garen’s heart sank. If everything was delayed for a year, Garen did not know how much his progress would lag behind in comparison to the others. At his current age, a single year would mean a world of difference to a year in the future. His body would grow and mature in this year and the time that had passed would never return. This information was part of the Energy Machinist’s general knowledge. Once they had reached twenty-five years of age, the maturing of their rains would stagnate completely. Therefore, every year before they reached the age of twenty-five was a time where they could change their destiny.

Nilo did not even glance at the four people that he had flung outside. Instead, he merely raised his head and looked at the faraway sky.

In the direction of a different contest platform that was far away, a long cry echoed over now. It sounded like a loud yell of a bird.

At that moment, a huge snowy white Giant Hawk flapped its wings and flew towards the heads of the crowd. In a few short moments, it slowed down from its initial great speed. It spread its large wings open and covered the people below while its ferocious talons clawed at Nilo’s head.

There was a whooshing noise before a ray of blinding white light was released from its two talons. The light enveloped Nilo and the other selected candidates. It wrapped them up and they disappeared without a trace.

The Giant Hawk turned and circled the area before flying towards the direction where it had come from. It flapped its wings a few times before disappearing at the horizon.

The remaining people stood on the ground and looked at the Giant Hawk that had flown far away. Some of them sighed admiringly with emotion.

The four people including Garen that had been thrown out arranged their clothes and packed up. Garen glared coldly at the girl who kept shouting her disapproval earlier before turning around and leaving. This was truly unacceptable. He could merely find a job first and pass the year for now.

This world was unlike the previous ones because it was exceptionally difficult for him to develop himself. Moreover, he had jumped into a completely unknown territory and could not even gain much support from his Potential Points. Furthermore, his incomprehensible bad luck had caused him to fall into this state now as well.

“All of you, wait a moment!” Just when a few of them were planning to leave, the last examiner that had remained called out and asked them to wait. “Are you interested in joining the next ranked sect? Although it’s slightly weaker, you will still receive Star Core treatment.”

“Are you joking?!” After being thrown out and getting humiliated, one of the men that looked like a white collar worker turned around and asked crudely. The other two merely ignored the examiner and left quickly without even turning their heads.

“Star Core?” Garen’s mind stirred. He dusted himself off and walked over. From the corner of his eye, he could see that the white collar worker was looking at him as if he was an idiot. However, Garen was unconcerned and walked forward to talk to the examiner.

“I would never lie to you. We examiners are not sent from the sects where the examinations are being held. Instead, we are members of external sects that were merely invited her to be examiners. I have no reason to lie or trick you,” said the examiner sincerely while stroking his white beard. “Of course, I would never force you if you were unwilling.”

Garen had good feelings towards this examiner. He did not know why this man had spoken on behalf of him earlier. Although he did not succeed, at least his good intentions were something that Garen would remember.

“You’re not someone that was sent by the sect to the arena?”

“You don’t even know simple things like this. You’re just another careless hick from the countryside,” cursed the male white-collar worker before he turned around and walked away. He had quickly left for a different arena in another area with the crowd that was not lively anymore. The contest that was being held here earlier had ended already and the arena would only be reopened again tomorrow.

“Will there really be a Star Core?” asked Garen quietly.

“Of course. Although the choices are extremely little and there are only Star Cores of the lowest level, it’s still better than nothing,” replied the examiner while nodding. “What do you say? Are you interested?”

“Is it a frost-type sect?”

“If you’re looking for frost-types, I can suggest a sect that you can go to. It should be rather suitable for you,” said the examiner softly.

Garen asked some questions regarding specific information carefully.

Apparently, the second rate sect that the examiner was talking about specialized in inviting the remaining members that were initially selected by larger sects. However, it was obvious that their resources and other factors such as safety and database were not equivalent to the larger sects and were actually much worse than them. Fortunately, despite only having those of the lowest grade, they still had Star Cores nonetheless. Even if he was able to reach the Inherited Level by relying on this, he would still only achieve the lowest level. Moreover, the success rate of this particular Star Core was frighteningly low.

The second rate sect that the examiner was talking about was called Scarlet Snow Sect. It was a smaller-scale sect that was not far from Ice Rainbow Sect. They had about ten members and their sect was once brilliant. However, the faults of their Training Methods and Inherited books caused them to decline halfway, making them an inferior minor sect now.

Very few people were willing to join sects like these. The examiner had only asked Garen this additional question because he was good friends with one of the Elders inside.

“Scarlet Snow Sect…” Garen had always felt that this Energy Machinist Sect was slightly weird. It seemed as though certain parts of it was slightly familiar for unknown reasons. However, he was indifferent towards all sects. Perhaps the strength of the weakest foundations could be instantly increased immensely once they were strengthened by Distorted Seeds. Perhaps everything would be made much easier when he relied on his powers to find resources everywhere when the time came. Currently, he was lacking the Energy Machinist’s important system education the most. The Star Core was something that he would only need much later on. Moreover, it was still very early now.

“Are there any entry requirements?” asked Garen. “I’m not young anymore and I don’t want to waste any more time.”

“There are no requirements. With your Appraisal, you will definitely become a candidate to be an Elder’s disciple immediately upon joining. However, you’ll need to think this through. Once you join this sect, this will be recorded in the Federation of Energy Machinists. You won’t be able to change sects anymore in the future,” the examiner mentioned kindly.

“It’s very normal to not be able to change sects,” nodded Garen. He was able to achieve Level Three by learning on his own and he believed that he would definitely be able to turn over a new leaf as long as he was given system training lessons!

“Could you take me there to have a look?”

“No, the sect’s encampment is extremely secretive. However, I can tell you that this is the only frost-type second rate sect that I can recommend to you. The rest are of different natures and will not suit you,” said the examiner frankly. “You need to consider this carefully. Perhaps it won’t be late to return next year again.”

“Next year?” Garen shook his head. “Alright, I’ll join the Scarlet Snow Sect.”

“Are you sure?”

“I’m sure!” answered Garen in a calm and concise manner.

The examiner sighed in relief. He had managed to finally get a third candidate for his old friend. He could report back on his task now.

The absence of Star Cores that were of good enough quality was equivalent to not being able to see hope of achieving Inherited Levels. Coupled with the fact that the Scarlet Snow Sect’s powers were declining day by day. Therefore, no one was willing to join this sect that was gradually waning. Faults had appeared within more than half of their Inherited books. There were also issues with the Star Core and Inherited Secret Tactics which were two of the sect’s most important things. Naturally, it was the rationale that no one would be willing to join this sect. Moreover, the other sects had conditions that were much greater and better than those of Scarlet Snow Sect.

However, Garen was unconcerned because he merely needed training for his Energy Machinist systems. Since he was already able to achieve Level Three by studying on his own, there would be no problems throughout the road ahead as long as there was someone here to help him. As for the Star Core, it would be enough as long as it was there. He could not delay this for another year because he was already too old and his assessed value would decrease. More problems would arise as his age approached twenty-five years. He felt that it would be impossible for him to breakthrough to the Level Four Energy Machinist Level after a year. Perhaps his assessment value would be even lower than his current value when he reached twenty-two years of age. His range of selections would decrease greatly as well.

The most important part was that he was still worried about the unknown Forbidden Willpower inside his own body. The thing that Red Moon had planted inside his body was abnormally tight. It was uncertain when misfortune would befall him again. A Star Core with a slightly lower probability was better than none at all, right? This was what he thought.

Chapter 975: Scarlet Snow Sect 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the examiner’s perspective, examiners like himself had outstanding strength within the second rate sects. Many of them were actually bearing the burden of being the third party that was invited here to observe the progress of the examination objectively to ensure that it was fair. He would receive some rewards from his old friend after completing this task, and reciprocation would be considered impressive.

When he saw that Garen had agreed, the examiner sighed in relief faintly and relaxed. This time, most of his quota had been fulfilled already. Moreover, he had something to give in exchange for his reward while preserving his old friend’s reputation.

“Garen, you can come with me now. I’ll inform someone from Scarlet Snow Sect to meet you soon. The distance between their encampment and this place are not that far actually. You will be able to arrive there on your own after being sent there a few times,” he smiled while mentioning this.

“I don’t have any problems with that,” nodded Garen.

Once he had decided to follow the examiner, both of them turned and walked towards the other arenas.

As he observed each of the arenas, every time the examiner encountered the remaining contestants who were not chosen in the end, as long as they had pretty good fitness levels, he would go forward and attempt to attract these contestants by speaking to them. However, all of the contestants that he tried to attract could not be bothered with him. Meanwhile, those who stepped forward voluntarily to speak to him were merely Level One or Level Two Energy Machinists who were already more than twenty years old. Despite achieving high levels, their Appraisal was too low and they had already reached their personal peak levels. Therefore, they were useless individuals who were not impactful enough to reach Level Five or Inherited Levels.

Along the way, there was only one more individual that joined Garen’s side. That person was also a young man like himself who dressed plainly and only possessed average Appraisal and Level Two Willpower. However, he was only nineteen years old.

After walking circles around all of the smaller arenas, the examiner was unable to enlist any more recruits. He could only take Garen and the other young man back resentfully.

“Next, we’ll be going to the main arena. However, we’re mainly going there so that both of you can expand your horizons and gain greater knowledge. It’ll be impossible for me to recruit people there but both of you should take this opportunity to broaden your view of the world. It’ll be good for you to see what the stronger prodigies are like,” said the examiner while turning around to speak to Garen and the other young man.

Garen and the other person nodded faintly to indicate that they understood.

The trio left the smaller arena area and was enveloped by an Energy Field before rising into the sky. They soared upwards for more than a few hundred meters at once before flying directly towards the centermost area of the Star Core Plaza.

Below them, the entire Star Core Plaza was oval shaped. There were three white high platforms in the center that were the same exact size. The tops of these platforms were currently shrouded in a layer of light yellow energy membrane.

Through the membrane, they could see that a few people were engaging in close combat while others were prompting beasts to sprint forward and attack.

Garen lowered his head and looked over. He could feel that the three of them were flying directly towards the centermost arena.

A familiar silhouette was coincidentally driving someone off the platform in the arena.

“Red Skeleton, one hundred and twenty-three victories!” said a gentle female voice.

It was truly the girl in red who had compelled and seized Hummingbird previously. Tiny red skeletons with two wings each were currently flying around her. Almost six of them could be seen if you counted carefully.

“Tch Tch… Red Skeleton, this girl has managed to touch the edges of the Inherited Level despite only being eighteen years old… Once she has obtained the Star Core and continues to work hard for two more years, she’ll definitely reach the Inherited Level once she comes out,” praised the examiner while clicking his tongue. Behind him, Garen and the other man became jumpy with fear. Was she only eighteen years old?

“That’s impossible! Her current Forces are clearly almost Level Five so how could she only be eighteen years old?” The other young man found this somewhat hard to believe.

“It isn’t impossible. This little girl is probably the successor of her household. She had probably undergone special nurturing and training ever since she was young,” the examiner shook his head. “Moreover, it’s obvious that she possesses the best talents in her household. She would definitely possess Accelerated Talents. Therefore, it’s almost certain that she will enter a large sect.”

Many other Energy Machinists had stepped forward to observe the match, much like these three people. Most of them had lowered their altitudes gradually while suspending themselves in mid-air around the high platforms below. These people could rely on their Energy Fields to hang in the air. All of them were Inherited Level individuals who released Forces that were extremely powerful. They had also weaved a densely packed Willpower net high up in the sky.

A few people who had used aircraft to fly up did not have enough strength to support themselves. Within the blink of an eye, they were entangled by the numerous Willpower webs that forced them to drop downwards.

The examiner glanced at these people coldly.

“Only Inherited Level individuals have the right to suspend themselves here. Aircraft? They obviously don’t know their own strength.”

The trio descended gently on the edges of the high platform in the center. They paid close attention to the movements inside quietly just like everyone else.

“Examiner, what are Accelerated Talents?” Garen had noticed this term that he had never heard of before.

“Accelerated Talents refer to a higher level of talent Appraisal that is present within most talents,” the examiner turned back and glanced at Garen. “Since your Appraisal is Level Five, Level Five would be your maximum limitations in theory. Although there is a probability that you can rush to the Inherited Level, it’s extremely low. Elites would regard your Appraisal as being weak but you would be a prodigy in the eyes of the average person.”

Garen nodded to indicate that he understood.

“In other words, the thing that would be accelerated is my Appraisal?”

“Right, there’s still one level or division above your Appraisal that we call Resonance. This level corresponds with the Resonance of the Mech Pilot inside, or simply replaces them. This means that their combat powers can definitely achieve Resonance Levels. People like these would have computing powers that are slightly stronger than yours once they are upgraded. Any higher and they would be the supposed Accelerated Talents,” said the examiner while praising them slightly.

“How much stronger are the Accelerated Talents in comparison to us?” The one who asked this question was the young man who stood on the side and sounded somewhat unsatisfied. He was only nineteen years old and after hearing that he was naturally unlike others, his train of thought had diverged somewhat.

“How much stronger?” the examiner shook his head. “Statistically, once they have upgraded them, the computing powers of Resonance Talents are forty to sixty percent stronger on average. They improve much faster than you and are able to develop themselves into stronger combat elites. They can also use stronger and more complicated Secret Tactics in actual combat.”

“Sixty percent!! Then… what about Accelerated Talents?” The young man was slightly subdued now.

“The increase of their computing powers are usually almost similar to those with Resonance Levels. However, the key aspect is that they have an ability called Acceleration which can upgrade their computing powers by twofold in a short span of time. When they release it after integrating it with their Secret Tactics, most obstacles or bottleneck situations that resemble natural moats to others are simply pieces of cake to them. Perhaps both of you will be able to rely on your determination to catch up to them in the beginning. However, as time passes later, the distance between you will become bigger. Both of you will be unable to surpass the obstacles while they will continuously force their way forwards without stopping for even one step.”

“Are there many Accelerated Talents?” asked Garen quietly.

“No, it would be impressive if there was even one of them within a thousand Energy Machinists. Of course, within a large population base like this, there would be more than a few who had reached the Accelerated class,” replied the examiner. “The Accelerated class is a standardized division for the most outstanding talents.”

All three of them stopped talking and merely looked downwards quietly at Red Skeleton’s fight.

The girl called Red Skeleton did not move. She was hugging her own chest with both of her arms while numerous red skeletons flew around her as quickly as lightning. They continuously flew towards her opponent quickly and attacked him from all sides.

Within such a short span of time, three people had already collapsed after stepping forward and were all disposed of quickly.

Among the people who had stepped forward was a person who was similar to Garen. This person possessed a rare radioactive glow as well and was able to use this radiation to affect their opponent while strengthening their own Energy Machinery. However, they did not have radiation achievements that were equivalent to Garen’s own. The defense systems that this person had established seemed nominal as he was sent flying immediately after being defeated.

“Too weak! Are you sure that you’re an Elite who’s here to participate in the Star Cloud Arena and not a piece of trash that merely came here from the dump to try and make a fortune?” sneered Red Skeleton sharply in a loud voice.

There were some Energy Machinists below who had been attacked to the point where they were afraid. It looked like there were hundreds of them there who were now somewhat indignant after hearing the things that she had said.

A few middle-aged male and female examiners were sitting at the side of the arena with looks of admiration on their faces. They sat at the side of the arena and chatted while looking like they were enjoying the current situation very much.

Boom!!

Suddenly, a thunderous noise could be heard not far away. They could vaguely tell that it came from the high platform on the right side of the main arena.

“Red Skeleton! I heard long ago that your powers were astonishing, so what use is it for you to simply yell while standing inside your little circle over there? Everyone here possesses triple Acceleration, so why don’t you fight me if you dare!!” A deep and resounding male voice echoed from another side. Although his voice was deep, a tinge of immaturity could still be heard in his tone.

“Do you think that I’ll go over just because you’re asking me to? Wouldn’t I just lose my reputation that way?” sneered Red Skeleton sharply. Her voice traveled towards the protective membrane that was far away and pierced through it.

“If you’re afraid then so be it. Why do you have to resort to hiding it?” said the voice disdainfully.

“I’m afraid?!” Red Skeleton’s hair stood on end immediately like a hissing kitten as she was slightly threatened now. “You’d dare to come over here if you had the skills, right?!”

“What are you yelling about?! Just get over there if you want to fight, stop yelling here!” Another person in the main arena who did not want to seem weak began to make noise as well. The voice of the person sounded like a young boy who did not sound older than fifteen.

“Black Jade Dragon Beast?” A hint of dread appeared on Red Skeleton’s delicate face. It was very rare for her to stop disagreeing or refuting.

The deep male voice on the other side did not turn silent.

“The Black Jade Dragon Vitality? That’s one of the legendary peak Talent Vitalities. I, Mammoth, desire to experience if your powers are truly stronger than my fierce brute force!”

“You’ll get a chance to see it,” replied Black Jade Dragon coldly.

After that, all three of them stopped speaking. The three main arenas were extremely close to each other but the trio continued on with their selection procedures quietly. However, these procedures were merely formalities to them.

After taking Garen and the other person to observe Red Skeleton, he took them to see the other two remaining arenas.

The youth called Black Jade Dragon was a child of only fourteen years old. He was dressed like a girl and was covered from head to toe in gold. He operated a type of Energy Machinery that resembled a large golden peacock-like bird. It was obvious that this kid loved the color gold. He had an extremely fine appearance and was abnormally pretty while golden ornaments and jewelry dangled from his whole body.

Meanwhile, Mammoth who stood on the other side was quite the opposite because he had a rough and boorish style. The top half of his body was naked and his skin was dark. A picture of a white sun was tattooed on his body while numerous Unihorn White Wolves were creeping beside his body. Each of these White Wolves were the size of little calves and were at least Level Four Energy Machinery. He had dominated the entire arena and would only charge forward and personally engage in close combat with peak Level Five Energy Machinists that the White Wolves could not handle. This person had managed to modify himself to reach peak Level Five degrees. His strength was astonishing and he was able to use a set of combined boxing techniques. There were only a few Energy Machinists who could withstand his set of boxing techniques.

The youth Black Jade Dragon, Red Skeleton, and young Mammoth were the three strongest and most eye-catching individuals within the three main arenas.

Garen and the two other people walked around the main arenas. Most of the people who were selected to join the contest were extremely confident in themselves. The ones with the weakest Talents were of similar levels to Garen and the other youth. Therefore, both of them clicked their tongues in admiration secretly.

Chapter 976: Scarlet Snow Sect 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The battles of each of the three main prodigies ended quickly. The examiner then took Garen and the other young man and flew towards the outside of the main arena.

“Guru, you only managed to bring two people today, huh?” A bald man with a white beard who was fully dressed in white flew over from the faraway sky. Three youths followed behind him. There were two girls and a boy.

“I could say the same about you. Your gains weren’t much bigger,” said the examiner helplessly while shaking his head.

“We only get our turn after the main sects are done with their selections. This is something we can’t help,” nodded the bald old man while stroking the bushy white beard that covered his entire face. “Alright, I’ll send these people off first. Let’s go drinking at the same old place later.”

“Mmhmm, okay,” the examiner agreed. He took Garen and the other young man away before walking past the bald old man.

Garen flew off with him while being wrapped in the Energy Field. He gazed downwards while they traveled past Star Core Plaza below them quickly. Stretches of areas filled with light yellow buildings were left behind instantly.

He passed by the inn that he was staying at yesterday quickly as well as the monumental forest of famous people.

Whoosh!

A light green aircraft shuttled past the three people. It created strong winds that caused ripples to surge through the examiner’s invisible Energy Field.

The examiner was unbothered and continued flying forward. High-speed aircraft would occasionally fly past him quickly.

Soon, the long stretches of houses and buildings below them became more spaced out and dilapidated. The aircraft that were flying past them at low altitudes decreased significantly as well.

A soft crashing noise that sounded like a moving water source echoed from below.

Garen looked downwards. They had currently arrived at the top of a continuous stretch of yellow rolling mountains. Down below, a gigantic white waterfall was slowly flowing behind it.

“This is the Guana Great Falls which is one of the most famous scenic spots in Planet Naga. There are many types of creatures living inside these waters. Energy Machinists from different places who want to research natural genetic banks come here to retrieve samples. Both of you can come here next time too,” explained the examiner softly.

He pointed at the edges of the waterfall. Many tourists were currently taking pictures there. There were even a few suspended aircraft that were hanging in mid-air above the waters of the waterfall. They were trying to salvage something unknown from the there.

After passing by the waterfall, the trio entered a gigantic yellowish brown ring. It was actually a ring-shaped building that was made up of layers of circles that were stacked on top of each other. When looking down at it from above, it resembled a pile of rings of various sizes that were placed together.

A white beam of light was shooting out of the center of the ring in an eye-catching manner. It was abnormally thick and faint buzzing vibrating noises were faintly echoing from it.

“We’re here,” the examiner flew downwards and rushed into the gigantic light beam in the middle. His speed continuously increased as he kept going.

“Pay attention to your balance! This is a public teleportation light beam. Accelerate and go towards the transfer zone on your own!” He threw out the last sentence quickly as his current speed had reached an extremely fast degree.

Garen could only feel that light beam approaching him at full speed. It was getting bigger and thicker before his entire field of vision was filled with white light instantly.

Hum!!

That buzzing noise flooded his ears and made it completely impossible for him to hear any other noises. There were no sensations throughout his body either, as if he had immediately fallen into a world that had nothing but white light.

About a few seconds later, his vision brightened suddenly before a vast wild forest that was filled with vibrant and dark green shades appeared.

The earth was slightly black while the surrounding plants were lush and green. The herds of deer below them scattered and ran off in all directions because they were frightened.

In the faraway sky, a thick clump of purely white clouds were shaped like a funnel. The lowest point of the funnel that was also the sharp end at the bottom happened to be connected to the top of a white tower in the forest below.

The tower was slender and serene like a thin inclined pyramid. Black aircraft that were the size of flies revolved around it. From afar, these aircraft that were moving extremely slowly emphasized the hugeness and magnificence of the tower.

“This is the Fermium Cloud Tower. It was Scarlet Snow Sect’s most dazzling and illustrious symbol previously. However, once the sect dwindled, it lost its Cloud Circulatory System. Hence, fewer people were willing to come to come here after that,” the examiner Guru sighed.

“It’s truly magnificent…” the other young man praised sincerely.

Garen praised it as well and nodded. Although he did not know the function of the Cloud Circulatory System, it was obvious that it was an extremely important installation.

“Is the Scarlet Snow Sect inside this place?”

The examiner glanced at him and nodded impatiently.

“Just wait a little longer, we’re almost there.”

The trio floated mid-air silently. The white light beam that teleported them here was only capable of performing one-way teleportation. Hence, there were no traces of the white light beam on the place where the trip had appeared. It was clear that they would need to use other means to go back from here.

Within less than five minutes, a white streamlined Flying Ship approached them from afar. It shot out towards the front of the trio before halting quickly.

“Alright, this is the designated public transport Flying Ship. You can get on now,” said the examiner while patting Garen’s shoulder.

A little square shaped door was opened on the Flying Ship now. A White youth with a delicate and pretty face was standing in the doorway.

“Master Guru, I apologize for the troubles you had to undergo throughout your joinery while escorting these new members here.”

“It wasn’t a big deal. I made a promise to all of you and I would certainly deliver. These two are little prodigies from the Central Metropolis who can also be considered as Elites. Including the three previous ones, I have fulfilled my promise to the Elders,” nodded Guru. Unlike the incident in Nagadako, he sounded slightly more dignified and proud this time. There were also subtle changes in his manner.

“Many thanks, Master Guru,” the youth bent his waist and bowed respectfully. He wore a little pauldron on his shoulder. This piece of armor was entirely white and had sharp edges. A little red heart was painted on it as well.

Guru turned his head and nodded at Garen with a kind expression on his face.

“Alright, you can go now. He was sent by Scarlet Snow to meet you. The Core Disciples with white armor and red heart statuses are specially sent to take you to the sect’s headquarters,” his attitude was completely different while speaking to people like Garen who were prodigies that had a chance of entering the Inherited Level.

Garen nodded while a hint of shyness on his face.

“Thank you very much for your care throughout our journey, Master Guru. Would it be possible for you to leave a method of contact so that you could teach me again in the future?”

“Of course I could,” Guru smiled. He used one of his hands to pat Garen’s shoulder again before a hologram of a key appeared in his hand suddenly. He burrowed it in Garen’s chest before it disappeared without a trace. “Okay, I’ve given you a method to contact me. Work hard and keep advancing. I have very good prospects for you!”

“Yes,” responded Garen certainly and respectfully. Despite being an Inherited Level powerhouse, the other party treated him kindly. This treatment was also given to him to see his future potential. Therefore, he needed to work hard and give him a good impression on the surface at least.

While watching Guru fly away with the other young man swiftly, Garen turned around and embarked the Flying Ship while smiling at the other youth who had a delicate face.

“Hello, I’m Garen. This is my first time coming to the Scarlet Snow Sect. Senior brother, could you introduce the circumstances of the sect to me please?”

“My name is Bainster but I’m unworthy to be your senior brother,” said the youth while smiling and waving his hand. “Of course I can explain everything to you because that’s my job. You came from the Central Metropolis and were able to become Two Hearted Disciples directly. In comparison to prodigies who can compete with each other for the Star Core, One Hearted Disciples like myself are nothing, but come with me first, it’s not convenient to talk here.”

“Okay, yes.”

Both of them walked along the path inside. There were only a few people who were sitting in the seats and most of them were closing their eyes and resting in a sleepy manner. A few others who were slightly more awake evaded the gaze of the delicate looking youth slightly. They lowered their heads and did not look at him. Some of them looked at Garen instead with hints of admiration in their gazes.

Both of them walked into the front section of the Flying Ship. They entered a luxurious VIP cabin and sat down in their own seats.

Both of them were the only two people inside the entire white cabin that was the size of a hall.

The youth took out two bottles of beverages that resembled fruit juice from a machine beside him and passed one bottle to Garen.

“Although our Scarlet Snow Sect isn’t impressive in the Central Metropolis, we are still a pretty good mid-range force within the White Cloud Continent. We also have more than ten Three Hearted Disciples with the highest Cores. Oh, that’s right, the Three Hearted Disciples in our sect are all powerhouses that have entered the Resonance Levels.”

“They only become Three Hearted after they’ve achieved the Resonance Levels?” asked Garen in a slightly surprised manner.

“Yes,” nodded Bainster while smiling. He was already extremely glad to be able to get this job because this was a good chance for him to form a good relationship with the new Two Hearted Disciple prodigies in the first instance. He had paid a heavy price in exchange for this job.

“Our Scarlet Snow Sect currently has three Elders that whose rankings have never deteriorated. The strongest one is the guardian beast, Lord Labourcast. We don’t even know the grade of this old man’s true strength but we do know his level has never worsened. He’s the strongest support pillar within our sect. He’s also one of the five Inherited Level supervisors. After that, there are more than ten Three Hearted Disciples who have achieved the Resonance stage. Following them are the Two Hearted Disciples including yourself, senior brother. There are probably a few hundred of you. Next up are the One Hearted Disciples like myself of which I’m afraid there are more than a thousand. At the bottom of the pyramid are the odd-job workers, servants, and maids. There’s also a trade center for radioactive people slaves. Energy Machinists like ourselves no longer need to fear the radiation disease after achieving Level Three. Therefore, the radioactive people slave Center exists for us to select goods at valuable prices. Senior brother, you can go there and take a look later.”

“Radioactive slaves? Where do these slaves come from?” Garen’s mind trembled slightly.

“It’s rumored that there were captured from the radiation belts on other planets,” Bainster moved closer to him and lowered his voice. “I’ve heard that the larger sects have their own slave planets that are specially used to breed radioactive people.”

“Slave planets…” A thought stirred in Garen’s mind. Slave planet?! They were using the populations of entire planets to breed slaves?

Massive plans, policies, and forces like these… were simply shocking!

He had never imagined that ancient and savage practices like slavery would actually exist on such a technologically advanced planet in this era.

“There are probably more than ten thousand odd-job workers, maids, and radioactive people in total. Therefore, our Scarlet Snow Sect’s headquarters have fully occupied an entire mountain. One of these mountains has been separated into five bases. Three of the main Elders occupy one of the bases respectively while Lord Labourcast occupies one of them. The remaining base is used as the dwelling area for most of the disciples, odd-job workers, and slaves.

“Then who provides for the daily needs of the sect?” asked Garen quietly while suppressing his shock at the slave planet.

“The daily needs of the sect are sent to the hill of the mountain every day by specialized people. They will then be transported up the mountain. The food and drink will go through various safety measures. Moreover, our sect has its own group of corporations,” said Bainster softly. “Do you know the Planet Naga Space Transportation Corporation? Our sect has shares in that as well.”

The blank look on Garen’s face indicated that he was slightly disappointed. However, he fixed it quickly.

“You will discover more things when the time comes.”

The Flying Ship turned quickly. It traveled for ten minutes above the forest before quickly descending near the bottom of a large mountain on the left side of Fermium Cloud Tower.

There was a popping noise before the door of the Flying Ship was opened. After that, both Garen and Bainster walked out.

There were already people who were waiting for them at the foot of the mountain outside the forest. There were all dressed in similar white clothes with the symbol of the One Hearted Disciples on their shoulders. There was a middle-aged man at the front who had a Paul from that was silver and different from the others. He was currently smiling while looking in the direction of Garen and the other youth who were walking out of the Flying Ship’s door.

Chapter 977: Strict Training 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Welcome to the Scarlet Snow Sect,” said the middle-aged man in a clear and loud voice while stretching both of his hands once Garen and the other young man approached him. This man had long thick golden curls that resembled a large hairy towel that was draped over his head. It looked somewhat strange.

Simultaneously, the remaining One Hearted Disciples opened their mouths and spoke in a synchronized manner.

“Welcome to Scarlet Snow!”

“My name is Garen and I’ve come here to gain knowledge. Please guide me,” Garen bent his body slightly and bowed respectfully.

“You’re the Elite who rushed over from the Central Metropolis. By choosing our sect, you displayed your faith in us. Please put this on,” the middle-aged man smiled while taking out a tiny black jewelry box. The cover automatically snapped itself open quickly and exposed an exquisite crystal carving inside.

People would find it surprising when they noticed that the crystal carving was actually floating in mid-air slowly and was not merely laying inside the box quietly.

Rays of nearly scorching sunlight were shining on the surface of the crystal, causing a faint silver glow to reflect off it.

“This is…?” asked Garen because he was somewhat unable to comprehend it.

The middle-aged supervisor smiled faintly. “This is the symbol of entering our sect, the Communication Crystal. It will disintegrate into a tiny structure on its own to enter the human body. It also possesses special abilities that allow it to modify Willpower gradually.”

Garen understood now. Although he knew that this item was definitely not as simple as the man had described, he was aware that this represented a necessary procedure for entering the sect that was similar to an identity verification. This crystal would definitely possess measures to restrain the disciples as well. However, he was sure that they were necessary. Cruel sects would not be easily passed off as others as there were also sects that did not interfere with their member’s freedom.

A thought stirred in his mind. Garen reached his hand out and used his fingers to pinch the crystal gently. Suddenly, he felt a slight chill flash past the moment his fingertips came into contact with the surface of the crystal. He then realized immediately that the crystal had quickly disappeared despite being right in front of his fingers.

“It has disintegrated already,” said the supervisor, smiling. “Alright, your room has been arranged. You’ll need to rest in the public base for some time, probably a month or so. Next, there will be internal competitions within the sect. Highly ranked competitors can choose to listen to the teachings of various Elders on their own at different bases. If you’re able to breakthrough to Level Four, you can request for the Elder examination. Once you’ve passed that, you can become an official disciple of one of the three main Elders.

“Understood,” Garen nodded.

“Then follow me,” the supervisor brought a group of One Hearted Disciples and turned around before clustering around Garen and walking towards the forest.

A strange phenomenon appeared. When the crowd approached the lush green forest, the greenery disappeared at once and was replaced by a white fish shaped Flying Ship that was parked on the grassy lawn.

Along the way, the supervisor explained the Scarlet Snow Sect’s situation. It was mostly similar to what Bainster had said except that it was less detailed.

Garen nodded while sizing up the One Hearted Disciples beside the supervisor.

There were both male and female disciples. Some of them had solemn expressions on their faces while others were gazing at him respectfully. The Forces surrounding their bodies were mostly only Level One or Level Two.

After speaking for some time, the supervisor finally became silent. Next, he went into another room inside the Flying Ship and answered a phone call.

His actions seemed intentional as Garen and these One Hearted Disciples now had space and time to interact. As expected, the group of disciples rushed over automatically right after the supervisor left.

One of Garen’s junior sisters who was slim and beautiful was the first to speak.

“Senior brother, welcome to Scarlet Snow. I was certain right away that you weren’t an ordinary person when I saw you walking out of the Flying Ship dashingly! This is a little gift from me. I hope that you remember my name in your Trusted Slip…”

She smiled like a beautiful flower and quietly passed a tiny blood colored ball into Garen’s hand. It was shaped like a peach but its surface was filled with fine and closely woven lines that looked like they were tinged with blood.

“This is… Beast Root!” Garen recognized this material. He could use it on his experimental platform when he was leveling up. It was used to increase the success rate of creating experimental Energy Machinery by about ten percent and was worth a hundred crystals.

“Dear senior brother, this is a little gift from your junior brother. I hope that you will be able to remember my name in your Trusted Slip…” Another person gave him a present with a respectful look on his face.

Next, while Garen was scratching his head and trying to figure out something to do, most of the disciples in the group gave him presents.

Bainster then explained everything to him softly.

“Every Two Hearted Disciple has the right to be placed in an optimized radiation villa as their own dwelling. These villas can release radiation that will optimize and accelerate their computing powers while improving their vitality. It provides many benefits towards our bodies. Clusters of houses have been placed around the area as well. These houses are provided for the followers and servants of Two Hearted Disciples. As these clusters of houses are too close to the main villa, the benefits of the optimized radiation will affect them too. Therefore, the houses that were meant for the servants were rented out to the One Hearted Disciples by the Two Hearted Disciples instead. Unfortunately, there weren’t enough houses to satisfy the demand.”

“In other words, they’re coming over for the sake of those clusters of houses? So the Trusted Slip that they were talking about was merely a sort of permission slip?” responded Garen immediately.

“You could say that,” Bainster nodded. Next, he whispered beside Garen’s ear and said, “Of course, there could be a possibility that they weren’t eyeing the clusters but the main villa instead,” he smiled pervertedly.

Garen understood suddenly and glanced at a fiery golden-haired young lady who was batting her eyelashes at him not far away.

Incidents like these were very common everywhere.

After the disciples had given him their presents, the supervisor returned and acted as if he had an abundance of free time. He chatted with Garen leisurely and allowed him to walk around on his own and take in the Scarlet Snow Sect’s scenery.

Through the Flying Ship’s side window, stretches of green forests and mountains passed them continuously. The whooshing sound of wind could be heard occasionally as well.

Whoosh!

A white Flying Ship flew past the outside of the window suddenly from the opposite side. A bald youth was sitting with his legs crossed on top of the Flying Ship. Both of his eyes were tightly shut and his arms were intertwined in front of his chest in a twisted pose that resembled a snake. He gave off a strange feeling, especially the fact that there was a faint red scar in the middle of his forehead that looked like an unopened third eye.

Garen’s gaze fell on the youth for a moment before he felt a faint but stabbing-like pain in both of his eyes. In an instant, the other person’s Willpower Energy Field had attacked him. It passed through his Energy Field and hurt his eyes which caused him to fall into a state of shock!

“This power… Even the previous Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia was not this strong!”

Garen secretly compared these two individuals in his mind. He noticed that Nadia’s power was truly unlike the power of the man from earlier. Although he had only caught a glimpse of that man’s power but he could already detect the grade of his Willpower. He could also feel the spatial distortions that were produced from a natural flesh body that was too strong. He had seen power like this in Nadia previously but had never experienced it so intensely.

“That’s the Third Elder of the Scarlet Snow Sect, Lord Copper Sera,” Bainster explained softly.

The moment that person flew past, everyone inside the Flying Ship lowered their voices unconsciously.

“Lord Copper Sera?” murmured Garen softly.

The Flying Ship flew above a lush green forest and passed it quickly.

They could occasionally see Energy Machinists who were engaging in combat on the flat platform in the forest below. The white circular platforms were abnormally eye-catching in the middle of the forest. Some of them were empty while others were filled with numerous people that were sparring. They fought extremely intensely while people stood on the side and cheered loudly.

Some disciples who were escorting the slaves of losing groups walked on the path below where the Flying Ship was traveling. They raised their heads and looked at the Flying Ship where Garen was located and gazed at him in admiration.

On top of Scarlet Snow mountain on a lonely silver circular platform stood numerous people in white who were already waiting there.

Their leader was a quivering old woman who was fully dressed in white. She raised her head and looked at the Flying Ship that was flying over from afar. A cute and charming young girl in a red skirt stood beside her. Her little mouth was fully pouted as if she was in a bad mood. Her long black hair cascaded down her vest in braids and reached her bright red miniskirt that was tight around the waist, emphasizing her girlish charm.

“Another Two Hearted is here. Why do I have to meet him this time? I’m not happy with this. I’m not happy at all!” the girl muttered to herself quietly.

“Both of the two other senior brothers have had their turn while you’re the only one who has yet to do it, senior sister. It’s very likely that the Two Hearted Disciple that has arrived this time is going to be one of us. As long as he passes the identity origin examination and does not have any temperament issues to be found, this is something that has already been set in stone. Teacher told you to come for a similar reason, so that you would leave a good impression on the new person,” explained the old woman quietly.

“Good impression?” the little girl continued to pout. “Are you sure that’s not just lip service? It’s a good thing that I’m naturally pretty and possess an abundance of beauty. Would I still be here to meet people if I was as ugly as an old man?”

The old woman merely smiled bitterly and nodded without refuting her.

A few disciples behind her had impatient looks on their faces as well. The young mistress’s bad temper was infamous throughout this branch. She had a good face but every time she opened her mouth to speak, two out of her three sentences would be self-praise. Moreover, she would only compliment herself by putting others down. She was also the most famous person within the entire sect.

“Senior sister, please don’t speak for a while. Let me handle everything,” said the old woman helplessly.

“I know, I know. So annoying!” the young girl nodded impatiently.

The Flying Ship floated above them slowly and stopped there before making humming noises and descending slowly.

The ship door was opened with a ‘puff’ before the One Hearted Disciples walked out from the inside. When they saw the crowd that was waiting for them, they lowered their heads and bowed respectfully before separating themselves on both sides and spreading out. Bainster was one of them.

Next, the supervisor and Garen walked out.

“Two Hearted Disciple Garen has arrived. Your subordinate requests to withdraw,” said the supervisor softly while bowing to the old woman.

“Yes, you may leave,” the old woman nodded. She looked at Garen who was walking towards her as her gaze considered him for awhile.

Garen’s entire body had been cleaned up inside the Flying Ship, making him extremely clean and neat. His disposition was steady and strong while his body was muscular but balanced. Both of his eyes particularly made people feel as if they were staring into a deep abyss. His shoulder-length black hair was arranged behind him neatly without a strand that was out of place.

“Disciple Garen, I’m here to learn!”

He walked forward and lowered his head slightly while illuminating his Energy Machinist key. They could clearly see that he was a Level Three Energy Machinist from there.

“I’m your senior sister, Rainy and my rank is number five. She’s also your senior sister, Eva Regar and her rank is number three. You may just call us fifth senior sister and third senior sister,” said the old woman quietly. Her voice was throaty and weak as if she could start panting at any moment.

“Yes,” Garen nodded.

“This special treatment is only given to new people like you who choose to join our division. Take it,” the old woman moved her hand and threw a little black ring towards Garen.

When he picked up the ring, trembles ran through Garen’s mind slightly. This ring apparently possessed faint traces of spatial distortions.

“Space Equipment?!”

“Not bad. Take a look at it yourself and check it. Everything should be there already. Within a month, you can visit the speaker’s halls and the first floor of the library to read anything and listen to the talks. The other places within your field of vision that are displayed as red zones cannot be entered. You will be punished if you trespass into these places, so remember that. You may freely enter the places that are displayed as green areas,” the old woman explained quickly.

“Understood,” Garen checked the ring for awhile. This was his first time using Space Equipment. Apparently, it was the size of a little bedroom. So many large materials were placed inside it and most of them were used to create Biochemical Pools and experimental platforms.

“You should create your Biochemical Pool and experimental platform as soon as possible. However, our sect’s main principle is that self-modification is the best path to power. Don’t invert it,” reminded the old woman.

The greeting from the supervisor and the guidance and explanation of the Three Hearted Disciples showed that they had already treated Garen extremely well. Garen was also able to experience the high positions of the Scarlet Snow Sect for himself on the inside. It looked like the people who were only trying to make a fortune from the one-time selections at the Central Metropolis had a different experience. They had missed this accidental opportunity by being blinded by the prospect of the bigger sects. After receiving praises from the Inherited Level Masters, it now seemed as if this sect had been painted with a bright layer of attractive gold paint. Moreover, he had also received such exceptional treatment upon stepping into this place.

“The Scarlet Snow Sect is the ultimate ruler within a range of ten thousand kilometers from here. Alarms will be released around you automatically when you encounter dangers so don’t panic when that happens. The nearest powerhouses will come and assist you then. Of course, if there are disciples who are facing similar risks nearby, follow the rules of the sect and help them to the best of your ability. Everyone here has a responsibility to help others when needed.”

Garen listened to the old woman as she explained the house rules while following the line of people down the side of the high platform before walking down the little mountain path.

Chapter 978: Strict Training 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The white buildings in the middle of the hilly forest rose and fell like faintly discernible waves. Most of them were surrounded by big tall trees while others were simply built on top of these trees. Meanwhile, Two Hearted Disciples like himself seemed to be treated very well. They were people in front who were specially assigned to the task of opening a path while the old woman and the beautiful senior sister led the way behind them and introduced everything.

The most beautiful part of the Scarlet Snow Sect’s public base was its gigantic triangular library that was embedded in a precipice halfway up the hill. This library used the most primitive method to record their books. The largest books were as tall as a person and as wide as two people, while the smallest books were the size of a palm.

All of these books were made of metal. They were unusually solid and could not be removed from here.

When the line of people walked past the library on the precipice and looked afar, they could see clusters of One Hearted Disciples who were stepping on suspended flying platforms, carefully reading the contents of the books as they faced the forceful strong winds.

“Alright, we can take a better look another day when we have more time.” The old woman led Garen through a sparse forest of peach trees. Suddenly, the area in front of them turned bright as neat rows of white villas and buildings came into view. A pair of these buildings were grouped as a unit. Meanwhile, their surroundings were covered by a thin protective membrane layer.

The two other people allowed Garen to pick a little three-story villa on his own. These villas were located in an area that was slightly lower than where the library was built. The administrative areas and the library were located on higher ground while the dwellings of One Hearted Disciples were located at the lower areas, making everything very convenient.

Once they had helped Garen settle in properly, the old woman and the beautiful Third Senior Sister told him the ways to contact them before leaving on their own.

“Senior Brother, I’ll return first for now. You can message me anytime if you require any assistance,” said Bainster to Garen, respectfully.

After nodding, Garen exchanged contacts with him as well before standing at the front of the villa, watching him leave quickly.

The entire villa was snowy-white and filled with faint chills that were of low temperatures. The surrounding areas were also desolate as he could only see a few people passing by in the distance. They left right after stepping on a flying platform the moment they exited the door and did not seem to remain at all.

Suddenly, Garen’s eyes shifted to the right. He saw that the grey curtains behind one of the windows on the second floor of a nearby villa on the right had been opened. Inside, a silver eye was staring at him right now. He could instantly feel icy chills crawling up his spine.

“What is that?!” He was certain that it was not human. When he noticed that the eye was shifting away before it finally disappeared behind the curtains, he looked away as well.

“Looks like the neighbor isn’t very friendly…” Garen furrowed his eyebrows slightly while his mind stirred as the main door of the villa closed on its own instantly.

He turned around and returned to the main hall on the first floor. After that, he took out the Space Ring as a thought flashed through his mind.

Boom!

There was a dull thud before various items flew over and suddenly shot out of the floor of the main hall. Some of the things were presents from the One Hearted Disciples, whereas most of them were provided by the sect.

Most of these large piles were made up of various materials and metal pieces.

Two blueprints were laid aside as well.

Garen picked the blueprints up and glanced at them. The instructions for building Biochemical Pools and experimental platforms were written there. The part of the villa that was allocated to them was written there as well.

‘Two Hearted Villas have specialized Biochemical and experimental laboratories that can house Biochemical Pools and experimental platforms respectively. There are people who will be specially in charge of delivering your food and drink. Besides that, you will need to wear the sect’s uniform and adornments at all times when going out. Please note, when the assembly bell rings, please be sure to abandon all tasks and rush to the transmitting beam at the doorway to be sent to the center of the main plaza to gather there. — May the honored Two Hearted Disciples receive a promotion as soon as possible (from Scarlet Snow’s logistics supervisor: Donlai Olsen)’

Garen put the blueprint down and walked around in a circle, inside the villa for a few times. The layout of this villa was very simple. He had seen this too many times in the other world and was too lazy to look at everything properly. He merely checked whether any surveillance equipment was present here. At the same time, he went to check the locations of the other important rooms like the bedroom, toilet, and kitchen.

Both the Biochemical and experimental lab were nearby each other on the right side of the first floor. All of the rooms had automatic lights. Therefore, the lights would turn on by themselves once he approached the room. The important part was that the main door was controlled by his mind, making it extremely advanced.

The materials for the Biochemical Pool, experimental platform, and Nutritional Liquid were fully prepared. The other blueprint explained the fixed proportions that were allocated for each period of time. However, he would need to pay a price in exchange for enjoying these privileges. He would need to complete a task for the sect every five years that was corresponding to his current level. Fortunately, he could go to the task center and select it on his own.

Beep beep…

Suddenly, a faint trembling noise echoed from Garen’s key again. A voice that sounded slightly familiar drifted into his ears.

‘Garen, I’ve entered successfully! The Star Cloud Sect!’

It was Accord. Prideful and happy tones could be heard clearly in his voice. However, he also sounded exhausted.

‘Where did you go? Why couldn’t I find you?’

‘Congratulations, I’ve entered a little group far away called the Scarlet Snow Sect,’ Garen smiled. Although Accord was someone who he had just met on the road, both of them had gained a close relationship with each other during their journey.

‘Why did you join a small sect?’ echoed a voice that was indicated that the other party could not comprehend the current situation. ‘Someone with Appraisal like yours would not need to enter a small sect, right?’

‘We don’t have to talk about me first. How’s Liz now?’ Garen changed the subject.

‘She went to the Dragon Light Sect and entered it smoothly without any obstacles. Unlike you,’ Accord sounded troubled. ‘Didn’t I recommend some mid-range and large-scale sects to you that were pretty good? Why did you join a small sect?’

‘Don’t worry, I’m very certain about my choice,’ Garen smiled in response. He could sense that Accord did not have much experience with the negative feelings of others. His nature was still pure and he did not plan to abandon their friendship despite the difference between their positions.

‘I can only wish you good luck then,’ said Accord helplessly. ‘Alright, I have some things to take care of here. I’ll contact you again when I’m free.’

‘Mmhmm, okay.’

Both of them disconnected the call.

Garen stood at the hall on the first floor and muttered to himself for awhile. He used the key to send a message to Celine again but he did not receive a reply. Perhaps the distance between them was too far and the key’s message transmissions could not pass through planets. He did not know whether she had received it or not.

Since he was currently in the Scarlet Snow Sect, he would only need to wait to get past the Judge at the time when he would grant the sect’s important Inherited Secret Tactics. Only then would he become one of Scarlet Snow’s true disciples. However, he did not think that this would take a long time as this meeting was more important than the usual. Despite being individuals who had always preferred jobs that allowed them to research things on their own, these Energy Machinists had managed to dispatch so many groups to meet, explain things, and even arrange everything for him. One could well imagine that he was an outsider who had only entered this place after being introduced by someone else.

After walking out of the villa, he could faintly see a few silvery-white Flying Ships that were continuously shuttling back and forth in circles from afar. They formed a white river that was dense and unusually magnificent.

‘If you want to enter my Scarlet Snow Sect, you’ll need to pass through four rudimentary checkpoints and undergo strength and physique examinations, as well as a computing test. Those who are eighteen-years-old and above may not enter. Those who cheat will be killed!’ echoed a low voice from the faraway sky.

Next, music could be heard faintly. Occasionally, it sounded like a lively child was yelling as well.

Although he could not see the scene below the Flying Ships because he was too far away, Garen guessed that this was probably from the selection and recruitment ceremony.

“Scarlet Snow has been dismissed by the main central city but it’s obvious in this area that they’re a powerful force. So these are the regional limits…” He sighed and recalled Blackboard Region where he had stayed in previously. Was that place not similar as well?

“Rise well…” Everything was prepared and in order. He only needed to wait until the examination was over before he could immerse himself in training fully. Garen’s mind began to calm down.

With the protection of the sect, he would use his spare time to dash determinedly towards higher Energy Machinist levels. The Seventh Divine Wind General was waiting for him in Blackboard Region!

He turned around and walked into the main door slowly before the heavy white large doors sealed themselves automatically.

******************

Without any obstacles, Garen passed the examination successfully half a month later. Although his true identity had been discovered, as long as it did not harm the interests of the sect or threaten it, it was not a problem at all.

As a Two Hearted Disciple, he had successfully obtained the Scarlet Snow Sect’s most precious Core Inherited information, a training secret method that was used to counter one’s own radiation — Scarlet Snow.

Scarlet Snow was similar to the previous Black Wind except that it was more complicated and it was of a higher level. He could see that the Black Wind had modeled itself after Scarlet Snow’s rank faintly.

From this Training Method, Eighteen Grade Cold Scarlet Snow, Garen could vaguely detect something that was unusually familiar. This training technique resembled Secret Techniques and felt like advanced and top Secret Techniques.

Eighteen Grade Cold Scarlet Snow was an extremely terrifying Secret Method that was slightly similar to Living Secret Techniques. As long as he practiced this and upgraded it by one level, it would spur on all aspects of his Willpower, Vitality, Secret Method powers, and computing power. In other words, it would improve all four factors simultaneously. It would purely separate out the physical tactics and secret tactics as both of these skills would need to achieve higher levels before they could be elevated at the same time.

These peak eighteen grades referred to the peak environments that the sect leader had achieved previously. Level Nine Energy Machinists were close to the level of the Perpetual Motioners, while the current Elders were around Level Fourteen. Most of them would stay at Level Seven because those with prodigious Vitalities could not depend on their talents to break through the limits either. In the future, they would need to rely on other things to continue advancing because the uses of their talents would disappear completely.

Their levels would not drop once they had reached Level Fourteen of this Secret Tactic Training Method. This was extremely similar to the Living Secret Technique in which Garen was currently practicing. From this Secret Method that he had obtained, he could vaguely see a reflection of his Secret Techniques… He had his suspicions that it was very likely that Secret Technique Users had come to this place previously.

However, he could not be bothered to overthink it now. Instead, he would rather concentrate on practicing the strict training of the Scarlet Snow Sect.

Garen discarded the thoughts of his Living Secret Technique and Mech Pilot Willpower so that he could focus wholeheartedly on improving his Energy Machinist skills.

He focused all of his attention on practicing the Cold Scarlet Snow Secret Method. Due to the influence of his Level Three Willpower, as a Level Three Energy Machinist, he was able to reach Level Three of this Secret Method after practicing it. However, following that, his progress slowed down instantly.

Those with average Appraisals would need at least seven to eight hours of accumulated computing from Level Three to Level Four. Garen did not even leave the area and merely spent all his time computing determinedly inside the sect. Other than contacting Accord and Liz occasionally, he would only send messages to Celine.

He had found a way to contact Celine as there were long distance message transmission services within the sect. However, he would need to bear the expenses of sending these messages on his own.

Only then did Garen discover that the Planet Naga and Mother Planet were in different dimensions. This was a dwelling planet that the almighty Energy Machinists had pioneered in an antimatter universe.

Everything was well on Celine’s end. She had sent people to look after Nono’s parents, especially to keep them safe and secure. The only ones who were still lost were Baylon and the others. Clint, Baylon, and Red Moon had disappeared without any news for a long time.

By training his computing power strictly while using the resources of the sect, he was able to build a good foundation for his Energy Machinist Willpower. As expected, Garen’s computing powers began to increase gradually and steadily.

Chapter 979: Breakthrough 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Five years later…

By the edge of the Scarlet Snow Mountains, at the peak of an abnormal rugged mountain.

The snow was piling up and the cold wind was brewing strongly. On top of a small snowy mountain, Garen sat by the edge of the cliff with his legs crossed and both eyes closed. Behind him, not far away, was a snow-white miniature Flying Ship with the number 15 clearly printed on the outside.

Whiz!

A ray of red light shone suddenly. Garen opened his mouth and a red glow shot out to encircle his body once before darting completely into his nostrils.

“Begin!”

He commanded in a low tone. A translucent pyramid, the height of a human then appeared before his eyes. On top of it was a dense flow of statistics and formulas.

The strange pyramid floated slowly before Garen; the statistics on it moving non-stop while beads of sweat were forming on Garen’s forehead.

Rushing for Level Four from Level Three Energy Machinist turned out to be an entirely different thing compared to a Pilot — it was so much harder.

Yet this sort of increase in his computing power was enough to keep Garen satisfied, just a mere four years to double his original strength. However, using the last one year to rush through it was not enough of a success, which made him slightly worn out. Within this one year, he had lost count of the number of times he had rushed for Level Four.

Back when he was a Pilot, rising up was an easy task. Though now as an Energy Machinist, he did not expect the chances to be this hard. All because of this, he stayed in the sect for a short period of time before he realized that he was not the only one. Advancing to Level Four from Level Three was indeed a difficult task and there was a lot of Energy Machinists out there who were not able to pass this test. This meant that the second Energy Machine Imprint was not that simple. It was a sort of qualitative change to increase the position of the Energy Machine Imprint, and it might even be harder than securing the third imprint.

It is because this was the stage where the Energy Machinist’s gift in computing power is put to test.

Garen finally understood how mediocre his computing skill was. Even though he could slightly increase his computing speed, reflex speed, and computing comprehensiveness through his potential points, he was still unable to change the kind of creative thinking and critical thinking skills that only mathematics prodigies portrayed.

This was not something one could improve just by intelligence, but more on imagination, creativity, and even a positive mindset that would relate to the world.

So now, he was not just trying to overcome this Level Four barrier, he was also trying to break through his mental obstacle.

After all, he was still considered a man-made prodigy. Perhaps his computing speed, depth, and complexity were nothing less of a prodigy. He was definitely lacking some other elements.

The cold wind whistled violently. Garen crossed his legs and opened his eyes slightly. He did not know how much time had passed but the sky was gradually getting darker. He opened his mouth lightly, the sweat on his forehead was still increasing.

Whiz!

Another ray of red light shot out from his mouth, towards the translucent pyramid.

Clang!

The fierce sound rang throughout the area. Garen arched his back violently as he spurted out fresh blood. Instantly, his face darkened.

Far away in the snowy grounds, two focused disciples in white glanced warily at the cliff Garen was at. One of them was Bainster, the one who went to meet Garen back then. The other one was a girl with maroon-colored long hair, along with bangs styled neatly on her forehands which gave her a pure and lovely look. The white women’s sect outfit hugged her curves perfectly, but the only unfortunate thing was that her actions were somewhat stiff. Even an action such as raising her arm to tidy her hair seemed a little hard.

This person was Hillco, the one chosen by Garen among a bunch of other loyal disciples to be the master occupant of his villa’s sub-building — the one chosen to enjoy the friendly effects of radiation.

Hillco used to be a normal person with ridiculously low talent as an Energy Machinist. However, she was not willing to sell herself out to gain the resources and conditions she needed either. So, she made her way to the ancient ruins and after a near-death struggle, she barely opened a small part of her computing brain. With the rise of her computing power, she managed to become a mere Level One Energy Machinist.

After that, she was accepted into the Scarlet Snow sect because of such peculiar transformation, to run experiments on how she managed to break through her brain’s computing power. In the end, the experiments were unsuccessful and abandoned. Hence, she was let alone to fend for herself.

Among the others, Garen chose her because he saw the perseverance within her, the kind of firm belief only those who had experienced near-death experiences would only understand.

As for her slow actions, that was an after effect of her coming back from the near-death experience the last time.

Other than the head, for movements that people only need a second to prosecute, she needed at least ten seconds. Even if she had ten seconds, it was extremely challenging on her part. A simple gesture such as raising her arm to her forehead required at least ten seconds.

As for her rent, as a Level One Energy Machinist, Hillco was able to waive her daily quests as she was cooperating with the lab experiments. Besides food and accommodation, she was able to earn some allowance as an Energy Machinist, but a hundred Spar Stones a week was a very low price.

At this moment, Hillco and Bainster had their eyes glued on the snowy cliff that Garen had just attacked. As the red light escaped Garen’s mouth and towards the translucent pyramid, Bainster’s expression changed instantaneously.

“Brother Garen is using his secret method! Once the Cold Scarlet Snow secret method is used, if he can’t breakthrough within the ten minutes, his injuries will be even more severe!!”

“What do we do then? We have to think of something to help Brother!” Hillco frowned.

“There’s no way! This is a critical moment. The secret method has started already. His computing power will expand immediately to 150%. These four years, Brother Garen has trained the Cold Scarlet Snow secret method to the third level already, slow and steady with each step. He has attacked multiple times just now and didn’t use the secret method, but now that he has used it, the power accumulated will be exerted all at once… He’s able to succeed!” Bainster said heavily.

By then, the both of them were joined together with Garen. Within the second, among so many disciples, they were the only ones who had Garen labeled on them. The power of Garen would affect their future. Within the five years, they had paid a price too, but how many more years would they still need to pay? They were almost twenty-five already. Once they reach the key age, their brain’s computing power would settle down and their limit would be set once and for all.

Right then, a ray of red light shone again at the edge of the snowy cliff, shooting accurately at the center of the translucent pyramid.

Garen roared and another ray of red light came out.

Clang!

The pyramid finally shook lightly and a small crack appeared in the middle.

Garen closed his altogether. Countless dense formulas of statistics computing formulas started to flow through his mind, with every possible computing thread circling his mind.

The cracks in the pyramid increased and became bigger.

“I understand now…! This level isn’t about problem-solving, it’s the breakthrough that matters!!” Opening his eyes, Garen opened his mouth again but the ray of red light remained in there.

The dense flow of statistics in the pyramid was gradually getting denser and more complexed.

Time was ticking. The cold wind continuously hit Garen, converting his sweat into ice cubes, layer by layer, almost turning him into a snowman.

Finally, with a raise of his jaw, the fourth ray of red light shot out and struck the vertex of the pyramid.

Crack!

Cracks instantly covered the whole surface of the entire pyramid, followed by crisp sounds of numerous silver bells chiming.

The whole pyramid shattered!

“He did it!!” Over here, Bainster and Hillco could not retain their excitement.

After Garen’s hard work, he had finally managed to breakthrough successfully and achieve the Level Four Energy Machinist.

Compared to those prodigies in bigger sects with better resources, his breakthrough was unusually difficult, but compared to smaller sects like Scarlet Snow, to be able to reach Level Four before the age of thirty was an achievement above the ordinary.

The entire sect was pretty small. Among the disciples, there were the three of them. In addition to Garen, that would be four people. Among hundreds of people, only the four of them were able to reach Level Four before the age of thirty. The younger the person is, the more potential the person has.

To be able to reach Level Four at an age like Garen’s, it meant that he was highly likely to be able to reach the Inherited Level. Just the thought of it made Bainster and Hillco smile in delight. Every year, approximately ten or so people are scouted and recruited from Central Metropolis to join the Scarlet Snow sect. They were all disciples, but how many of them actually managed to reach the Inherited Level? Technically speaking, although these elites had potential, each potential had its own limits too.

The competition within sects was unusually cruel. Some other sects had inside competition that led to hundreds of disciples being ambushed while fighting for resources. The Naga planet was full of danger, the mutated creatures in the ancient ruins were extremely dangerous; if ever faced by anyone from the sect, one would be dead for sure.

There was a high death rate for Energy Machinist competitions, which was also why Energy Machinists at the apex of the pyramid were able to put pressure into a Pilot’s head. Natural selection of life and death was known as the cold-blooded competition system, and that was why the surviving Energy Machinist would be acknowledged to have truly strong combat skills. Compared to Energy Machinists, Pilots received lesser training, especially those fighting on the void battlefields to defend their planet.

After the pyramid broke into pieces, the second Energy Machine Imprint appeared in the back of Garen’s mind. Both prints were floating side by side. The left one had a Big Bad Wolf mosaic print, whereas the right one was still empty, waiting for him choose a print when he got back.

Garen stood up with an overworked expression and ripped off the parts of his clothes that were stained with blood. Staring at what was left of the pyramid while it gradually disappeared into thin air, his body gave a violent shiver as he let out a breath.

With a crack, the layer of ice on the surface of his body shattered and fell to the ground.

“I’ve finally reached Level Four… Can’t believe it took me five years… But it is still shorter than an average person’s ten years, I guess it’s not bad.” A hint of satisfaction filled his eyes.

Turning around swiftly, he walked towards Hillco and Bainster. As he approached the both of them, Garen smiled and waved his hand.

“Let’s go for a round of celebration. Now that I’ve passed this major threshold, reaching Level Five should be so much easier.”

“Congratulations Brother Garen! Once you pass this obstacle, you can easily breakthrough Level Five using the Mars Radiation Stone distributed by the sect!” Bainster said excitedly, “Once you make it through Level Five, you’d be qualified to be a third disciple and become an elder Grandmaster!”

Hillco, who was standing by the side nodded in agreement. The smile on her face expressed a sense of heartfelt joy.

Garen shook his head with a smile.

“You’re thinking too much, that’s so far in the future. Just take care of yourself first, you’re still at Level One after such a long time.”

Bainster’s expression stiffened as he rubbed the back of his head embarrassingly.

Chapter 980: Breakthrough 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Brother Garen, what are you going to do next?” Hillco asked in a hushed tone.

“What I intend to do?” Garen clenched his fists, “I still need some time to get used to the jump from Level Four to Level Five. If I want to reach Level Five, the Mars Radiation Stone won’t be the only thing I need…”

“Brother, our small territory has always been peaceful, relatively stable. With you as our leader, the area of the snowy peaks has always been calm. But I wouldn’t say the same for the other snowy peaks,” Hillno said simply, “every second disciple will be assigned to different houses and a snowy peak to practice alone; this is the rule, in the sect, to protect the followers and first disciples in the surrounding. But I heard something recently from one of the sisters, that one of the Brothers at a snowy peak nearby wants to contact you. Even though I’m unsure of the details and who…”

Before she could even finish her sentence, a soft voice broke through the air from a distance.

“Ha ha ha ha!”

In between the laughter, a white shadow leaped down from the sky and barged towards the three of them who were standing at the top of the snowy cliff. Followed that, a huge snow hawk circled above.

“Let me see what kind of special ability does an elite from the central have!!”

As the last of his voice fell, he rolled over and let out a piercing screech. Countless snowflakes were gathered, immediately forming a gigantic white dragon which darted towards Garen who was standing in the middle of the trio.

The dragon swept up the snowflakes from the surrounding ground and formed a huge snow column which was at least meters thick. The tip of the column was a sharp edge that was pointed directly at Garen’s face.

Garen snorted, then proceeded to activate his Level Four Cold Scarlet Snow technique and clouds of white frost emitted from his body. Holding out just one arm, he pointed his index finger at the sharp edge, as if he wanted to use his own flesh and body to fight against the solid ice thorn.

However, his finger and the ice thorn closed in quickly. Just when they were about to touch, Garen’s finger suddenly shot out like petals of a flower. Within a second, his palm turned into a pale icy-white shade and hit the ice thorn at the side.

Bang!

The ice shattered into pieces. The snow column was thrown to the side by a shadow by the side, whereas Garen remained still on the spot.

“Nice!!” The person made a flip in the air and landed on the ground steadily. His feet sank into the snow, leaving two deep footprints.

“Indeed the elite of the central. Just achieved Level Four, yet such strong lethality. Among all the brothers, your power should be ranked top three.”

“Who are you to show up at my snowy peak without invitation and behaving so atrociously?” Garen asked icily. After the series of hand-to-hand combat and his style of speaking earlier on, Garen seemed to have a wrong impression that he was meeting a secret powerhouse.

When all the snow debris finally dissipated, the trio was finally able to see his true face. It was a white young man with a handsome face and white short hair. He had only one arm but there was a sense of emotion in his eyes that gave others a relentless feeling.

“I’m the owner of the twelfth snowy peak, Joyson but you can call me Joey. Garen, master of this peak, I’ve been observing your breakthrough for the past few days. What about it? Well, are you interested to join me in competing for the top ten snow peaks?” This person’s previous rage was nowhere to be seen anymore — he was slowly warming up.

At this moment, Bainster and Hillco were still unable to regain their composure. Bainster stepped back in shock whereas Hillco just seemed pale. Even though she felt a sense of threatening death during the ambush, she did not step back, which truly showed her strong sense of will.

“How will I benefit from being in the top ten snow peaks?” Garen asked calmly.

His opponent was a similar Level Four Energy Machinist. However, during the short fight just now, he noticed that the opponent was just testing the waters, that’s why the opponent did not unleash his full power. Being a second disciple meant that his qualifications were not bad, so he should be at least between the third to fifth rank among the disciples.

“Obviously, there are plenty of benefits!” Joey laughed, “Second disciples in the top-ranked snow peaks get special treatment. Since you just recently managed to break through, you will need some sort of treasure to secure your position. Or else, you will need at least another two years to completely stabilize your position before you can try for the next level. Think about it, without the help of extra resources earlier on, you would have spent five years to break through from Level Three to Level Four. Do you know how fast the disciples from bigger sects progress after receiving resources? If you don’t fight for some things, you’ll just be long forgotten behind by others who have leverage above you!”

Garen frowned.

Spending five years to break through Level Four was something he did not think of.

Speaking of disciples from bigger sects, wasn’t Accord one of them?

In comparison to Accord who was already focusing himself on passing Level Five already, he thought that it was just their differences in talents. But come to think of it now, things seemed different.

Joey laughed at Garen’s expression. “I’ve been searching in the snow peaks for the longest time and after selection, only you Garen, you’re the only person I can’t see through. And that is why I am here to ask for you to team up with me. You’ve relied completely on yourself to reach Level Four already. Other than the treasure to secure your rank, you still lack a suitable Energy Machine Imprint. If you’re in the top-ranked snowy peak, you’d be able to buy more powerful Energy Machine Imprints… Not just the ordinary ones you see in the market, like… The new batch of mutated imprints that are stronger than the ordinary ones by a couple of times — Winter Night Wolf!”

“Winter Night Wolf?”

Joey stepped closer, within five meters range from Garen and the two others.

“Seeing that you chose a wolf Energy Machine Imprint, I have the impression that you have a liking towards this sort of Energy Machine creatures. The Winter Night Wolf is a rare mutated Energy Machine Imprint. Although it isn’t much of a difference from the initial Giant Wolf Cannon Fodder, once cultivated in the right way, which is three by three from the biochemical pool, it will have strong jumping abilities and facing flying units would be no big deal. Most importantly, it’s group increment would rise according to quantity! Now that’s the scariest part!”

Increment rises according to quantity.

Suddenly, Garen was slightly moved. If he was to add the Distorted Seeds to these wolves…

“How do I fight for the top rank?” Garen asked in a low voice.

With the sight of Garen being moved, Joey smiled lightly. “That’s simple, kill!”

“Kill?!” Garen was stunned.

“Brother, he meant killing disciples of the opposing sect. The more you kill, the more evaluations you get, and the higher you would advance in rank according to your battle records,” Hillco explained softly.

“So what about it? You and I team up against the Dragon Eye Sect. I’ve been keeping an eye out for them for three days.” Joey even had a target selected already.

“How are battle records calculated?”

“The sect imprint will automatically calculate the power extent and proportion of impact,” Joey explained.

“I should look this up.” Garen nodded. If the other person was speaking the truth, then he really had to fight others for resources that he would need to shorten his time of practice so that he would not be suppressed by the others. As for the resources, conflicts were bound to happen.

Survival of the fittest — that was the natural selection of life. This was still a path of life, whether it was the Combat World or the Technology World.

“I shall be waiting for your good news then. This is my communication device.”

Joyson threw a clear crystal brand towards Garen who caught it easily.

A gust of snow rolled up. Once again, he turned into petals of snowflakes, dissipating into the cold air. Who knew what kind of supporting tool he was using that allowed him to walk on air.

“To be able to fly away, that is something only a Legacy Master can do!” Bainster stated with envy. Only now did he dare to reveal himself from behind Garen.

“That was just some help from a prop.” Hillco cast a glance of disdain towards him, “You’re a man yet you were the first one to retreat.”

“What can I do when I have no power? If I were to have power like Brother Garen, do you think I will still be scared of him?” Bainster asked unconvincingly.

“Come on, just you?” Hillco rolled her eyes.

As the both of them continued to bicker, Garen fell deep into thought.

Originally, whether he was in Combat World or Totem World, he had the potential points to provide him with resources so he did not have to be swept into this battle vortex of limited resources. However, things were different in this world. Potential points were nowhere to be found and the second Staff of Absolute Yin was yet to be found. Even after such a long time, the remaining potential points left in his Attribute Pane were not to be easily used. It was only for emergency life-saving purposes.

To be exact, he had always been practicing alone, excluded from the world of interest.

“Turns out I’ve never really been into the vortex of natural selection of life.” He let out a breath.

“Let’s go.” He picked up his feet and walked towards his villa situated at the foot of the hill.

The both of them followed suit behind him, though still bickering. However, as if everything was blocked out, Garen was still lingering over the sudden realization that had never occurred to him.

It was his past all summed up.

Because of the potential points, he need not have to fight others for the limited resources. All he had to do was practice silently and continue advancing so that he could be the best. This was his luck, not his unfortunate.

Though the disadvantage of relying on potential points too much in this world had finally surfaced because he never had any past experiences. So, he would not take the initiative to find the resources he really needed. As for the path he took part in, he had to rely on himself to move forward and as a result of that, he kept being thrown off by others, further and further away. This was the consequence of not having resources and not trying to fight for them.

Accord, who should have been the same as him was already trying to reach for Level Five. Yet here he was, only achieving Level Four recently.

However, he remembered.

“With the help of external objects, I can improve faster. If I were to rely on just myself, it will be a sort of training for myself. This path would be more simple and pure, but it will not only take a much longer time, but it is dangerous at the same time. On the other hand, my foundation will be steady throughout, and it will be easier for me to achieve a higher realm in the long run.”

He held out his hand and stared at the snowflake that was slowly melting in his palm.

“If I want to reach a higher state, to reach the Army Level or even higher, speed is not the only thing I’m looking for.”

Horrifying images of devils destroying the world from ancient mythologies kept popping in his head.

Garen then realized his own determination.

“What I want is not just temporary strength, but a power that will last me in the long run. I don’t need any foreign objects that will affect my foundation. As for what Joey mentioned about the Winter Night Wolf, it’s something I should give up on. It is a trick that allows people to accelerate their progress in a short period of time by sacrificing their potential. Anyway, the power spawned out is still not as good as one’s natural capabilities.”

Although he had understood this principle since long ago, he had never truly experienced it as he did at this moment. From what he saw, the potential points he had used to advance in the past was no different from an external support tool.

He may not be able to observe the after effect of using potential points to push himself into secret combat level, maybe because it was too high level, but there would definitely be a consequence. If he wanted to progress rapidly, would it be possible that he need not pay a price?

Chapter 981: Teamup 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

All the way back, Garen kept thinking about the question earlier.

With the aid of resources, he could be able to face more challenges stronger and faster. He could also progress faster if he had sufficient resources within the short period of time — this was the advantage. However, doing so would bring rise to many enemies and dangers everywhere. More so, he would also face the danger of an unstable foundation.

Fighting was the only way to rise rapidly in a short period of time.

All the way down to the central mountain villas, the trio could see flying ships in the distance circling the snow peaks. Those were the hosts of other snow peaks communicating.

A few of the flying ships were flying towards their direction. One of them especially had an extremely clear target and was flying towards the stop at the bottom of the snow peak.

Bainster let out a sign of acknowledgment when he saw the flying ship as if he could recognize it.

“Is it someone you know?” Garen whispered.

“Yeah, it’s my friend’s flying ship but I don’t know what’s up.” Bainster nodded, “Let me have a look first.”

“Alright, just call out for me if you need any help,” Garen replied lightly.

For the past five years, Bainster had been helping him take care of various transactions and services, collect materials, handle social matters, arrange schedules, and collect data and information. This was something him and Hillco were in charge of all the while, and it was the main reason to why Garen trusted the both of them more. With the both of them handling most of his matters, he had so much more time to practice.

There were hundreds of snowy peaks in Scarlet Snow Sect; most of them were owned by second disciples. Such delegation, such system, were almost similar to the records seen in ancient mythologies. The behavior of powerhouses within the sect was similar to a secret combat powerhouse, and not at all an Energy Machinist from the Technology World.

If Garen had once suspected that the secret combat powerhouses had come to the Scarlet Mountain sect before, he was now a hundred percent sure of his suspicion. Scarlet Mountain sect was basically established by a secret combat powerhouse, and there were definitely secret combat powerhouses who used to come to this world.

Due to the fact that the Cold Scarlet Snow secret method was just a simply changed name from the Cold Scarlet Snow Technique, the eighteen levels would completely match the level of the Living Secret Technique and Dying Secret Technique. However, this was the first time Garen had witnessed the Dying Secret Technique of such a high level. After all, in general, the secret techniques he had always been practicing were considered the Dying Secret Technique.

Back in the villa area, Garen took a glance, by habit, at the villa above where the windows were pitch black and no light could be seen. Though sure enough, a pair of eyes flickered and disappeared instantly. It did not seem humane as it gave off an eerie sense of feeling.

Opening the doors of his villa, Garen was just about to walk out when suddenly, he heard a gust of soft wind behind. When he turned around, his eyes swept the surroundings with a trace of vigilance.

A young lady with red hair was standing calmly behind him, watching him. Upon knowing that she was noticed, the lady shot him a gentle, sweet smile.

“Mr Garen, so you’re back so early today?”

Garen nodded his head and replied with a polite smile.

“Ms Monica, you’re early too.”

Monica nodded with a smile.

“You’re welcomed to be a guest here anytime.”

“Unfortunately I’ve been busy recently, but if there’s ever a chance I will definitely accept your offer,” Garen replied casually. He had always felt that this lady was somewhat weird. He had heard from the second disciples once that some people never had the chance to set a steady foundation when they were young due to the restriction of resources. Therefore, they were unable to reach higher levels. Once they reached their limits, some would start running prohibited experiments that would cause them to lose their minds. Garen had a feeling this woman was one of those people.

Both of them exchanged a few words before Monica retreated to her own villa.

Her movements were swift, and in a blink of an eye, he could hear the sound of her villa’s door shut.

Seeing that the door was shut, Garen then only walked to his own door. Hillco had already gone back to her own place. Besides the occasional workers sent by Hillco to clean the villa, she usually lived in a separate villa.

The white hall was clean and spotless. The floor could literally be used as a mirror.

Garen held out his hand and smacked the wall. He then walked into another big hall.

The lights in the hall switched on automatically without a sound, and a cup of hot ginger tea appeared on the table in front of the sofa.

This world did not have such a thing; it was all just Garen who had searched for multiple materials all over the place before settling with a plant similar to Ginger, with the same medicine property. So he decided to just use it to make tea. The taste was somewhat identical in which he considered as a form of nostalgia for his previous life.

Sitting down and sipping his ginger tea, he flipped open his notebook on the table and began to find out more information about what the twelfth host, Joey, said.

The insides of the Scarlet Snow Sect was slightly complicated. Most of the transactions were sales of different materials and Energy Machine Imprint objects. However, most of them were premature and the flying imprints were rare, making them extremely expensive too.

Something as big as the ranks of the snowy peaks was of course something easy to find out more about.

“The top ten peaks will have the opportunity to select an award corresponding to the value of the prize deserved according to the prize list published above.” It did not take long for Garen to find out the description of the ranks of the snowy peaks.

This was the information Joey gave.

This was exactly what he had imagined. Joey was for sure a cruel one and he was ranked twelfth in the top hosts of snowy peaks. He had killed over hundreds and he was only twenty-eight years old, one of the elite powerhouses nurtured on the grounds of Scarlet Snow Sect. He still had some sort of reputation in the eyes of second disciples.

Garen straight away stole another glance at the first displayed portrait. Similar to a lot of other cases, the first familiar face was still Carthage.

“The prodigy who had always looked down at us among the entire Scarlet Snow Sect, Carthage.” He shook his head lightly. Carthage was someone who did not need to compete for planets, yet he could be chosen straight away as a prodigy of a certain new planet. Even if he was to compete with disciples from a larger sect, they stood no chance against him. Now that he was entering the resonating phase in accepting the third disciple exam, he was a definite pass if nothing goes wrong.

If Garen was to be asked who were the valued prodigies recruited from the central in the entire Scarlet Snow Sect, Carthage was definitely the one. He was the hope of Scarlet Snow Sect, the hope to rehabilitate the Fermium Cloud Tower.

The Fermium Cloud Tower used to be the symbol of Scarlet Snow Sect’s peak, but now they do not even have the qualifications to enter the tower. Without a Level Nine Elite powerhouse, there was no way they could enter the Fermium Cloud Tower.

After retrieving the information he roughly needed, including the information regarding the Winter Night Wolf, Garen cleared the history and left for this biochemical room.

Two huge Big Wild Wolves were crouched down at the doorstep of the biochemical room. Once the door was opened, two wolves as strong as bulls wagged their tails eagerly when they saw Garen.

“Here you go.” Garen smiled and took out a few pieces of black dried meat from his pocket for the two wolves, letting them tear the meat apart and share among themselves.

He then walked to the front of the aquamarine biochemical pool and sat in front of the control computer of the biochemical pool. As he progressed into Level Four, even the increment effect of the biochemical pool increased. Every level of the NIS training method provided the biochemical 0.5 level of defense and speed. The NIS rank within the Scarlet Snow Sect was not considered as low at all. Therefore, Garen had no need to change his training methods.

“I’ve finally reached Level Four, which means every single one of my biochemical creatures will have a double rank increment of 0.5*4.” Garen stared at the Big Wild Wolves as they gobbled down the dried meat. He then used his Mind Force to command them to go back to the biochemical pool.

With the sound of water splashing, both the Big Wild Wolves jumped down into the biochemical without hesitation, submerging themselves into the blue nutrient solution.

Garen started to run his fine-tune work by simply adding his Energy Machine Imprint and Willpower into the biochemical pool. With just that, everything would be strengthened naturally by the imprint over time.

The Big Wild Wolves were rolling about in the biochemical pool, yelling in pain as their fur began to shed. Blood red muscle veins appeared on their body and started absorbing the nutrient solution.

The scene lasted for at least ten minutes before the fur of both the Big Wild Wolves began to grow.

They crawled out to the edge of the biochemical pool and shook off the nutrient solution from their bodies. Their bodies were slightly distorted, emitting a slight force of a Level Three Willpower Field.

“Level Three? Not bad, not bad.” Garen stood up and smiled in satisfaction.

Cannon fodder creatures of a Level Four Energy Machinist were usually of Level One standard. Even if they were strengthened by a Distorted Seed, they would only be strengthened by three times, which would put them somewhere in between Level One and Two. That was the original standard of a Big Wild Wolf.

However, now that he had reached Level Four and had enough nutrient solution to carry out reformations, the Big Wild Wolves produced had managed to obtain an increment and had the power of a Level Three Mech.

“Even though they seem like they have the power of a Level Three Mech, we still need to test the effectiveness through combat.” Garen was just like any other Energy Machinists, except the fact that he had the Distorted Seed which was able to cause a triple increment of his cannon fodder creatures, almost exceeding a Level One extent by far — that was his ultimate secret. However, this was related to the Living Secret Technique. So he could not risk other people finding out or else it would be impossible to explain.

Only the elite version of experiment objects by an ordinary Energy Machinist was able to have a battle force similar to a Mech of the same rank. Whereas ordinary cannon fodder creatures were usually at least two ranks lower than the creator itself.

However, Garen’s cannon fodder creatures actually had the power similar to an experiment object. It would be extremely bothersome if word got out. This was only something that could possibly happen to those prodigies from bigger sects because they used more optimized materials and skills, unlike Garen who used his Distorted Seeds. Not to mention Garen’s Energy Machine Imprint was just a normally weak type used by the investigation army. To be able to strengthen the investigation army to this level, Garen was probably the only one who could do it. The prodigies from bigger sects would not even waste their time to strengthen such garbage.

After strengthening both Big Wild Wolves, Garen left the biochemical pool and went to his own laboratory.

Inside the laboratory, a cylindrical yellow bronze platform was floating in the air. Subtle electric arcs flashed from time to time at the smooth surface.

This was Garen’s experimental platform that was used to create the elite version of tools. It basically consisted of all the resources Garen had been retrieving from the Scarlet Snow Sect for the past five years.

An ice-blue gigantic wolf was crouched on the experimental platform. This wolf was so much more powerful than an ordinary Big Wild Wolf. Its entire body was poked with all kinds of tubes. Just a glance of it could ache one’s heart.

Garen made his way towards the computer by the experimental platform, and started pulling out information and monitoring statistics.

“My experimental platform can only strengthen a Big Wild Wolf to a Level One standard. That’s the most simple experimental platform and it has cost me so many resources already. Being an Energy Machinist really costs a lot of money…”

He sighed softly. If he wanted to fight for a place, he would have to go out and kill the disciples of the Dragon Eye Sect. It seemed like he had no choice but to use his experiment subject that he had been nurturing for two years.

Now that he had reached Level Four, his Willpower instantly enhanced the ice-blue gigantic wolf’s automatic reformation.

The reformation only lasted about two minutes.

‘Charging energy furnace… Ice Wolf Number One, activated…’

An icy woman’s voice was heard from the experimental platform which was the sound device installed by Garen later on.

Chapter 982: Teamup 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Hoo…

As Ice Wolf opened its eyes, long tubes automatically withdrew from its body, retracting back into the experimental platform.

Its gigantic, three meter length body rose slowly from the experimental platform, leapt down, and landed beside Garen.

Underneath its layers of soft and warm coats of fluffy blue fur, the Ice Wolf was at least a Level Five in terms of combat strength.

“I have now almost fully regained my overall strength level when I was a Pilot,” Garen stroked the Ice Wolf’s head and grinned with satisfaction. “The experimental subject has no duration, so there is no need to eat as long as it recharges enough, that’s the only good thing about semi-mechanization, but unfortunately each person can only own one.”

He could feel the other two wolves’ Willpower connecting.

“My greatest strength is in energy machine creatures, but if there is a lack of space to carry them away, there is no way I can build them in time. The building process will take a longer time, and I would not be able to fully unleash my true potential…seems like we will just have to find a better Space Equipment.”

If he intended to use the Big Wild Wolf and the Ice Wolf, he definitely could not let the enemy know, therefore ensuring there would be no chance to expect his power card.

“Space Equipment that’s big enough…”

In Garen’s hands now was a tiny Space Ring used to store materials. It was given to him by the sect as a prize, and it was the cheapest kind, the kind that could not be used to store objects.

He scrolled through his computer, filtering out the top ten prizes given for the top-ranked.

“Space Equipment…”

Soon he turned to the individual division column.

‘Valledoria Stone, one standard unit space, worth 1,000 points, cannot hold living organisms.’

‘Al Stone, one standard unit space, worth 1,500 points, can hold living organisms.’

‘Thunderous Stone, one standard unit space, worth 2,000 points, can hold living organisms, additional single release and group release function.’

‘Moonlight Stone, one standard unit space, worth 3,100 points, can hold living organisms, additional release swap function, additional ten meters beam projection function.’

There were only four of these stones in total for selection. They were all Space Stones, so all he had to do was choose and simply mount it on an earring or a necklace.

One standard unit space can store up to at least five creatures as big as a Big Wild Wolf, or maybe three creatures the size of a Saber-Toothed Tiger.

Garen checked his savings. A bitter smile flashed across his face as he was greeted with a mere amount of five measly points.

“In the past five years, other than the necessary quests, I’ve only accepted one quest that rewarded me very little points, and they are even the lowest ranking points.”

“Besides getting another Space Equipment, I need to progress to the next level as soon as possible to secure my current rank. With such a stable Willpower, what I need is…” He searched the list of prizes once again but sadly, the prizes this time around were just external goods, Space Equipments, items that strengthen energy machines, and a few rare training method handbooks.

Inherited secret methods were fundamental in the sect, as for training methods, nobody cared what kind of training methods the Energy Machinists chose, because no matter what training method it was, it was disguised by a scientific name of an inherited secret method. Basically, they were private and confidential secret techniques that could change an Energy Machinist’s life.

After many inquiries, Garen had confirmed the information regarding the qualifying competition, the method of participation was fairly simple. All he had to do was integrate his results before the 30th after two months. If he qualified in top ten, he would automatically have the rights to choose a prize, the higher-ranked ones would get the priority to choose first.

The higher the placing, the more points will be accumulated too. Being the first to choose a prize would also mean that the most valuable item would be chosen first, naturally, the reward of power was extremely high too.

After all, there were only so few items.

There were even specific details about the reward-punishment system at the bottom of the web page.

Among the details was a simple method to gain points.

With a flick of his hand, Garen scrolled down the page to read the content displayed.

‘Integral system: Kill first disciples of the Dragon Eye Sect — Ten points per person.

Second disciples — 100 points per person.

Third disciples – 1,600 points per person.

Lufthansa – 3,000 points, Ferrero – 5,000 points.’

The further he scrolled down, the bigger the gap between the second-ranked and third-ranked disciples, ranging from 100 points to 1,600 points, it was crazy. Did that not mean that 16 first disciples barely equaled to the value of one second disciple?

Even though Garen had no clue, but from the looks of Lufthansa and Ferrero listed at the bottom, it was obvious that they were the elite third disciple powerhouses of the Dragon Eye Sect. Just like Carthage from the Scarlet Snow Sect.

He carefully reviewed the prohibition guide once again. Those already participating in the killing zone were at the Dragon Swap region, a piece of wasted, vast land between the Dragon Eye Sect and the Scarlet Snow Sect. Most of them were jungle areas, a small area of hills, mountains, lakes and various sorts of complicated terrains. Moreover, mutated monsters were all over the place. Numerous bones were piled all over the place, who knew how many of those bones belonged to the aftermath of the killing between both sects.

After looking through the information once more, Garen then only took out the communication device given to him earlier by Joey.

Gently knocking on it, a tract of Willpower converted into a piece of thread and entered the small hole.

All of a sudden, a virtual three-dimensional image of a body was projected in front. It was the white powerhouse earlier on, Joey.

“I’m glad it didn’t take you long to get in touch, my dear friend.” Joey held out his arms as if he was enveloping Garen into a hug with a large smile on his face.

“How are we cooperating on this?” Without further ado, Garen jumped straight into the topic. He needed a good enough Space Equipment or else his power card would not be able to be used to the maximum of his advantage. He really needed the Space Stones. If he was to go onto the market now and buy from the black market at the bottom of the hill, the resources needed to trade for points would not be a small number. Besides starting on quests now, he had no other way. Not only that, quests that offer a high number of points were remarkably dangerous. If that was the case, he might as well not join the competition at all.

It was also pretty normal for the price to be pushed up at least double in the black market. To be able to enjoy such resources without risking one’s lives and just splurge on resources that were acquired by those who put their lives into danger, setting a sky-high price was normal. Some even raise it by three-four times, maybe by five-six times and it was still nothing out of the ordinary.

“Nice!” Joey extended his index finger and drew a mark before his eyes, immediately the face of a lady appeared in between them. It was a lady with short, green hair who looked about 20-ish years old. Her looks were charming and beautiful, and she had a hint of flirtatious aura.

However, someone who is an Energy Machinist who was capable to reform one whole self, looks and age were not something to be trusted. Although she looked mid-twenties, she could easily be over 100 years old.

“This is just a temporary team up, I’m the leader, Yiling,” the green-haired lady spoke. “Each killing integral naturally shows how powerful your imprint is, everything is decided on the force of impact. The system is pretty fair, if the both of you have any comments please do speak up.”

“So the three of us will be teaming up?” Garen frowned. Originally he thought it was just him and Joey, he did not realize that he would be teaming up with somebody else.

“Yes, I am in charge of the main system, Joey’s the deputy, and you just broke through so you will be responsible for investigating the situation. Garen, your group of wolves should be at least Level Two, right? How many more can you breed?”

An ordinary Training Method Level Four Energy Machinist could generally only control three wolves, which was when a Level Two Energy Machinist just have the qualifications to earn an Energy Machine Imprint, every level allowed them to control one more cannon fodder. But most of the Energy Machinists found ways to increase this number through special training methods like scarce resources, and special secret methods.

Garen nodded. “I have three Level Two wild wolves but I don’t have any Space Equipment, so I can only make them on the spot, their duration is about three hours.” What he said was all the ordinary cannon fodder.

“Three hours? That’s not bad. I have five Level Three Pentatonic Bats, their duration is about five hours.” Joey smiled in return.

This information was enough to quicken Garen’s heartbeat, and these were just cannon fodder creatures, nobody had even brought up the elite version of experimental subjects, and Joey already had Level Three creatures. This guy seemed like a master powerhouse. The accumulated power he had was indeed strong.

“I have two Level Four Mountain Apes, so just let me handle frontal combat, Pentatonic Bats are white in colour and is not good for investigation, so Garen, investigating task will be all up to you.” The green-haired lady spoke lightly. It was obvious from the looks of the power of her cannon fodder, this lady should have reached Level Five already, but she was still not a third disciple, he could tell that she had not entered the resonation phase.

Level Five! That would be the peak of a second disciple, at least a powerhouse ranked top ten. Garen observed this lady carefully. He completely did not expect her to be a host ranked top ten.

“There’s a lot of cannon fodder for investigation, why did you choose my team?” Garen asked.

“Idiot!” Yiling could not help but cursed before vanishing into thin air.

Garen felt a rush of anger. His face darkened as he was about to say something.

“Don’t be mad, calm down.” Joey immediately plastered an apologetic smile on his face. “Let’s go form our teams and finish our quest, now that we’ve returned late, the others are preoccupied with other matters. Among those still here, only you have the strongest power, so both of us benefit from each other. Moreover, this is your first time so you’d have a promotional discount. If your team receives a small integral point, it can also be used as 1.5 points. This is the treatment only newcomers get, just for this one time.”

“So that’s it.” Garen now understood the newcomer treatment. No wonder they approached him. Besides being one of the few stronger ones among the other new recruits, the others had been dragged away.

“Don’t hold a grudge against Yiling, although they don’t allow murders within the sec, once you get hit or injured, you might just spend the next one or two years lying alone…” Joey explained in a hushed tone, “Yiling has a very bad temper, now that the crucial impact resonation phase was approaching, her rival had already entered the phase before her, so it’s best if you don’t piss her off, or I wouldn’t be able to save you either if she goes cuckoo.”

“Hurmph.” Garen grunted and remained silent. Approaching the critical point of Level Five, he did have true potential, a Level Four cannon fodder must have cost a lot in order to upgrade the biochemical pool, this was a powerhouse with a huge amount of accumulation, it was not worth it to create nemesis with such a powerhouse over a petty little issue.

This was the only way to come in contact with such a social circle, he then only realized, the triple effect his Distorted Seed gave off seemed nothing next to a powerhouses’ who had other ways to achieve the same effect as he could.

This also meant that his level was just considered average compared to the other Energy Machinists, if he was not a little more careful he would not even know what hit him when he gets killed.

“Alright, we shall now discuss the topography of the Dragon Swamp region and some information on what the Dragon Eye Sect’s disciples’ expertise are…”

Chapter 983: Combat 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the vast forest, a dark green flying ship flew speedily just above the trees. The strange thing was that with the ship flying at that speed, it did not bring about the slightest surge of wind and air flow, as if it was just brushing off a welcome gesture.

The sun above shone mercilessly with its fiery gold rays. A mild trace of translucent distortive force rose in the air.

Zoom…

A giant black squid was floating mid-air, its many tentacles waving about, blocking the flying ship’s path.

With a whiff, a five-metre thick tentacle went flying towards the flying ship. It seemed to view the flying ship as its prey and started to attack.

At an inhuman pace and faster than a bullet, the tentacle was already in front of the ship.

“Turn around!” A female’s voice rang out coldly from the flying ship. Suddenly, the flying ship was like a small green bug, turning sharply to the left, and thus missing the giant tentacle by just a few millimeters.

“Recalculate! Accelerate!” The female voice shouted again.

White flames emitted from the back of the flying ship as it accelerated and soared through the side of the squid, disappearing within the trees in seconds.

Inside the flying ship.

Yiling had a cold hard expression, staring intently at the scene in front of her. Garen and Joey were standing towards her right, one had his arms around his chest, the other was leaning against the wall, silently staring through the high-strength glass window as everything passed by in high speed.

Large tracts of scenery constantly backed up from the edge of the windows, blatantly showing how terrifyingly fast the flying ship was travelling at.

“Our target this time is a small base in the Dragon Eye Sect. There’s about 15 of them, among them there are three people that you have to look out for who are Level Three Machinists and above, one of them should be a Level Four.” Joey seemed to have something in his ears as he was reporting accordingly to what he heard.

“What rank is the Level Four one?” Garen lowered his voice and asked.

“I’m not sure, but as long as they’re not the top ones, we don’t have to worry about the others,” Joey replied with a reassuring smile.

“How’s the situation on the mutated monsters nearby?” Yiling was concerned on other matters.

“The mutated monsters are all below Level Two, seems like this base was probably a location where some Level Four Energy Machinist chose to bring other disciples and so to carry out their quests… Haha, luck is on our side! Our first call and we’re already meeting such excellent prey!” Joey exclaimed excitedly.

“Are you sure that there are no powerhouses?” Yiling asked.

“Most probably no, my Pentatonic Bats surveyed the surroundings within a ten kilometer radius and they did not sense any trace of high energy.” Joey’s Pentatonic Bats lent the help of the flying ship’s equipment to investigate a vast range of area.

“We are soon approaching the high-pressure area. Garen, it is up to you then.” Joey cast a glance towards Garen.

“Leave it to me,” Garen nodded.

The three of them had already left the snow peak station for three days. Just being on this planet’s vast earth travelling for three days straight yet they just left the Scarlet Snow Mountain terrain and entered the communal area before the Dragon Eye Sect.

This communal area was extremely huge. Its surface area was probably three times bigger than both Sects. It even had many dangerous places in between, fortunately, they had the communal map back from the sect, or else the three of them would never have been able to find the Dragon Eye Sect’s small base that easily.

The flying ship soared through the threes into the air, soon enough they noticed a small, white circle base in front of them. The base was built on the grounds and was really conspicuous.

“Those idiots, I wouldn’t even dare to use such a bright color, they really are seeking death!” Joey let out a laugh.

“Let’s finish this quick.” Yiling said in a low voice.

Garen and Joey nodded in agreement.

Whoosh!

The flying ship’s side door opened gently and three figures leapt down from more than twenty meters above in the sky. Each of them had on a pair of gliding wings and with it, glided smoothly towards the white base skillfully.

Inside the base, a middle-aged man with a scar on his face was explaining something to a few Energy Machinist junior brothers and sisters. All of a sudden, he sensed something was off and looked towards the sky.

“It’s the hunters from the Scarlet Snow Sect! Red alert!!!”

His expression changed instantaneously and he roared.

At that very instant, an ear-piercing alarm rang through the base as a dozen of young people stood up in panic. Each of them pulled out their guns, missile launchers and other weapons, and aimed at the three people gliding down from the sky.

However, a strong trace of Magnetic Field swept through and the alarm stopped immediately. All the metal weapons suddenly failed to work; a person who was carrying a missile launcher even got hit by the missile that suddenly exploded on his shoulder. He picked himself up and had ashes on his face; it was obvious he had suffered a severe injury from the explosion.

“Idiot! You actually dared to use a Pilot’s weapon without the protection of an energy field. A Pilot’s long-range attack is the easiest to interfere!” Joey yelled arrogantly in the sky.

“They are just Level One or Two Energy Machinists, you don’t need these weapons, your own energy machine is just an investigative standard, how are you going to save yourself? You’re thinking too highly of them.” Garen did not have a liking towards Yiling, so naturally, he was slightly closer to Joey.

The three of them fell from the sky and landed with a thud inside the base, each of them threw a high magnetic interference force field device to the ground which exploded within seconds.

Such a magnetic field device could last for an hour. Every living creature covered in the range within this period of time would be carrying a strong disturbance of magnetic energy and would not be able to use any weapons consisting of metal parts.

Suddenly, a white beam of light shot straight at Joey’s face who was taking the lead.

“Huh? Plastic missile?” Joey smiled. As the missile was about to hit him, he swerved to the side suddenly and with his sharp nails, he instantly tore apart the external shell of the missile as if he was peeling off the skin of a banana.

The missile components scattered onto the ground with a clatter without exploding.

“The both of you split between yourselves, I’ll take care of here.” Without another word, Yiling dashed towards the Level Four Energy Machinist.

A few Black Panthers shot out in lightning speed, seems like they were energy machine biochemical beasts, but they were caught between Yiling’s palms, instantly turned into ice blocks and fell onto the ground, unable to move.

Her body instantly turned into a black thread as she darted towards the middle-aged man with a scar. The moment the both of them started fighting, ice pieces and a pale yellow mist gradually dispersed from the flying ship.

Garen and Joey rushed towards the remaining Energy Machinists, getting rid of an Energy Machinist every now and then. A Level Four Energy Machinist against a Level One or Two was basically a heartless massacre. Not using any high-tech metal weapons in addition to the huge difference in practicing secret methods, even when a crowd of energy machine baboons pounced on them, a strong surge of Frost was released from their bodies and delayed the baboons’ movements. The baboons could not even catch up with their shadows, and could only scream in excruciating pain.

Screams were constantly ringing in the air.

Garen crashed into the arms of an Energy Machinist, elbow hitting the man directly above his heart. Garen turned around with a kick and hit the white shadow that pounced on him from behind. Garen’s body turned swiftly several times and within seconds, another four or five Energy Machinists were frozen to death.

Suddenly, he realized that there was nobody else in the surroundings so he glanced over to Joey’s side, broken limbs and wreckage were everywhere, blood was streaming down his right finger, it was extremely gory.

“And we are done.” Joey smiled triumphantly.

There was about ten or so Energy Machinists, all killed by two people in just a blink of an eye. These young prodigies would not even get the chance to enjoy the luxurious life an Energy Machinist could bring, each corpse still had a look of shock and disbelief on their face.

“You all want to die!!” With a howl, a shimmer of gold light fleeted across the Dragon Eye Sect middle-aged man’s eyes. A gold crack split open between his eyes, shooting a dazzling beam of gold light straight at Yiling.

“Humph!” Yiling activated Scarlet Snow Technique, a strong surge of Frost exploded from her body, covering her entire body in huge mass of a sticky white snow storm. Instead of retreating, she made her way towards the gold light.

The gold light imitated the storm and rushed forward, the instant they made contact, the gold light was straight away gobbled up by the storm soundlessly.

The middle-aged Energy Machinist actually escaped to a few hundred meters away and threw himself at a well-hidden yellow-green flying ship as its cabin door open slowly.

“Blizzard!” Yiling pointed at the flying ship. A white block flew out from her body towards the flying ship.

The snow block was moving in a seemingly vicious speed, almost covering few hundred meters of distance in a blink of an eye, hitting the slightly flickering ship.

Boom!

The flying ship was set ablaze. Instead of freezing once hit by the snow block, it exploded. The middle-aged Energy Machinist was shot back violently, as he was drifting through the air with a shocked expression on his face, Yiling pointed a shard of Frost at him puncturing him between the eyes. He fell to the ground and shattered into countless pieces.

“Let’s gather up all our trophy goods, we leave after ten minutes.” Throwing her last sentence, Yiling made her way towards the Level Four Energy Machinist.

Garen and Joey nodded silently and began to search the corpse’s bodies and loot the base.

********************

Ten minutes later.

Yiling, Garen and the others’ flying ship gradually rose up into the sky and soared into the distance.

At the same time, inside the entire communal area, big and small groups of the Scarlet Snow Sect were frantically moving in the direction of the Dragon Eye Sect for the ranked fight.

Approximately ten elite groups including Yiling and the two others were making their way towards Dragon Eye Sect’s base, the battle was getting intense.

Clang!!

Garen punched the palms of the beautiful woman with yellow eyes who was opposite him. Each of them took turns and laid a dozen of hard punches in a second, every punch causing a strong burst of sound. Both of them were Level Four Energy Machinists, with such a short period of time, they would not be able to make out who was the stronger one. In order to truly test out who was the winner of the both, they needed more than half an hour at least.

There were corpses and bones lying around everywhere. Yiling led Joey and Garen to attack this small base, but they did not expect the opposing powerhouses would not be in and just came back. The opposing powerhouses were also three Level Four Energy Machinists. Three against three, a direct battle broke out straight away.

Garen seemed as if he was giving his full strength keeping his opponent in a lock, maintaining the standard of a normal Level Four Energy Machinist, but in reality, he was just observing the fight over at Joey’s and Yiling’s.

“Fanged Hound!”

The woman let out a growled and a khaki colored enormous wolf pounced out from behind and bit Garen on his side.

Chapter 984: Combat 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Level Four Energy Machinery!

Garen was surprised as he quickly moved backward to evade the giant wolf’s attack. While doing so, he saw a petal shaped yellow item in the girl’s hand and started smiling.

Becareful! A huge sense of threat spread out as Garen retreated to the back, using the Instantaneous Paper Box to block an incoming attack without any hesitation.

At Level Three, the Instantaneous Paper Box was enough to threaten the Level Four Energy Machinist geniuses who were on the verge of becoming a Level Five. Its potency was extremely threatening.

Boom!!

A red light as thick as a pillar shot out as it hit onto Garen.

Boom!

Snowflakes were everywhere as the force greater than of a Level Five hit directly onto Garen.

Garen used his Scarlet Snow Technique and his powerful physical attributes to defend himself. He was slightly pushed back for about ten steps or more. His throat tasted sweet with the blood which he almost vomited out.

“Still thinking of escaping after taking a direct hit from my Red Laser Cannon?” The beautiful woman started smiling. This guy was hiding his true strength as well!

“Go!!”

Yiling shouted from afar and one could feel a sense of anxiousness in her tone.

Joey was entangled with a young man and couldn’t gain any upper hand against him. The frosty chill kept spreading out and he was in a draw against him.

Garen and Joey looked at each other in the eyes and both of them sensed trouble.

They had finally met upon a tough opponent!

A sonic boom could be faintly heard from afar and an intense force field, which wasn’t disguised in the least, were closing onto them quickly. It was obvious that another powerhouse was approaching and it didn’t feel like they were from the Scarlet Snow Sect.

“Retreat!”

The three of them retreated without saying another word as they leaped up into the air, to be captured by a green Flying Ship which flew past the sky in lightning speed.

The leader of the Dragon Eye Sect raised his head as he licked the blood mark under his chin.

“It’s the Thousand Shades of Hand Yiling… I’ve fought against her two hundred years ago… I didn’t expect to be able to meet her during this return.” He started to smile cunningly.” This little girl who was hunted by me has finally grown up so well. Nice…”

“Captain, we should go after them and kill them!”

A few Level Four Machinists landed behind him. Although some of them had the Experimental Energy Machinery Body while some didn’t have anything in their hands, each and every of them had a very powerful aura. Although they were only a Level Four, they had the presence which far surpassed of a Level Four.

“It’s alright. Our current objective is to obtain achievement in this war and that girl Yiling won’t help us achieve our objective. She’s incredible good in escaping. Although we may be able to kill her if we chase after her, it’s not worth the amount of time.” The man said coldly. “Pass on this intel to senior Agalla. Her team is most suited to deal with them.”

“Yes.”

*************

The green flying ship kept flying at great speed in the sky with no hint of slowing down.

The three persons in the flying ship were trying to catch their breath.

Both parties were fighting cautiously as none of them had activated their sophisticated Experimental Energy Machinery Body and it was fortunate that nobody was harmed. One had to realize that the Experimental Energy Machinery Body was the Energy Machinist’s root. The more advanced the Energy Machinery was, the higher the maintenance cost. This was the reason why no one would use it so casually. Energy Machinist, especially from Planet Naga’s central city would probe the situation with their real body before deciding to activate the Energy Machinery.

“That was a special force that was created such to kill off the elite teams.” Yiling’s face turned pale as one of her hands pressed onto her chest while the other wiped off the blood beside her lip. “It was fortunate that I discovered them in time and the enemy had just gathered up. Our bodies would definitely remain there if that was not the case.”

“The leader of the Level Four team was Beast, who was the fifth Powerhouse of the Dragon Eye Sect. I’ve seen him once fifty years ago.” Joey was tending to his wound on his face and he seemed to be in a life threatening situation just now.

On the other hand, Garen was sitting on his knees at one corner as he monitored his body’s condition quietly. The three of them was injured more than the eyes could see.

While the others didn’t realize, Garen was very sure that his body kept vibrating from the light strike he took head on just now. His muscles and organs shook non-stop, greatly exhausting a lot of energy that was supposed to be used in his recovery.

He had no choice but to keep his internal body’s condition in check to prevent any similar Willpower injury similar to the Seventh Wind General.

The other two seemed to have suffered the same injury and it seemed to be a technique unique to the Dragon Eye Sect.

“What do we do now?” Joey looked at Yiling as he waited for her to give a suggestion since she was the strongest among the three.

“Let’s hidden ourselves to create some cannon fodder and exhaust some material to recover ourselves.” Yiling said softly. “The Dragon Eye Sect has started to attack and we have no idea how many powerhouses they have sent. We are outnumbered so we should let the large force to clash with them first before deciding on our next move.”

“Alright.”

Joey and Garen both agreed on the plan. Since they were lacking on intel, they could only take this course of action.

It wasn’t just Scarlet Snow Sect who was in the qualifier. Since it was the grand opportunity for the disciples of the Dragon Eye Sect to attack to obtain first place, these two sects would have to fight against sooner or later.

The three of them flew into an underground crevice in the sea of trees. They then dug a hole on the side of the wall deep within the crevice, hid themselves while they tried to recuperate and recover their strength.

Although Garen had hidden his true strength, his strength would only reach the level of an average Level Five even if he were to release the Cold Radiation and use his Ten Thousand True Technique. Seeing how the girl performed her skills with ease, Garen had a feeling that his opponent was also hiding her true strength. No one would know who were to win if they were to really battle it out. Afterall, an Energy Machinist had a lot of methods to achieve their means and no one would know what trump card an elite Energy Machinist had.

Inside the cave.

“Rumor has it that that guy Beast spent sixty years in researching the strongest killer move. I thought I could force him to use his Killer Move but I didn’t expect to not be able to handle him in his normal state…the Level Five is indeed something else.”

Yiling was in the Flying Ship’s driver seat and her injury seemed to have settled down and she was feeling much better.

“The one I encountered just now was most likely a new Powerhouse. I’ve heard that they have recruited a few Powerhouses into the Central Metropolis.” Joey said softly.

“I’ve already informed Mei Tilan’s team. Those who are in the top 5 should fight among themselves. All we need to do is to attack at the right moment.” Yiling said coldly. “To not take revenge is simply not my style.”

It was merely a grinding process with no bottlenecking to level up from Level Four to Level Five. One would just require to keep on grinding and accumulating and it was very normal for this process to last from decades to centuries. Although Garen was new and curious towards these Energy Machinists always speaking in the span of decades, he wasn’t really surprised at all.

The Beast’s team was not the strongest, but only the fifth strongest during that battle and one of his team member had the prowess of a Level Five. This region was truly a battlefield for the elites.

Garen gauged that his strength was still comparable to theirs. However, that was the result of being in the realm of martial arts which far surpassed everyone and possessing the Living Secret Technique Hellfrost Peacock Technique. Comparing to the Energy Machinists who had been accumulating for a long time, he was still too poor… Wealth represented definite battle strength to an Energy Machinist.

After the previous battle, he knew very clearly where he stood in this world. Among the many teams consisting of Energy Machinists, he was just on par to a normal elite team.

The three of them tended their wound underground. Fortunately for them, the Scarlet Snow Technique and the Dragon Eye Technique counter each other and they were fully recovered within three days. They recovered their physical and mental strength quickly after removing the vibration within them. It was fortunate for them that they had already accumulated some point by hunting the others. However based on Garen’s estimation, they could only obtain the Space Stone if they were able to kill at least fifteen men from the Two Hearted Disciples.

The levels of the Two Hearted Disciples consisted of at least Level Three Energy Machinists. If they were not careful, they would encounter a Level Four Powerhouse or even a Level Five Powerhouse, which was their main member such as Yiling as well.

Given the difficulty, one could imagine how valuable the Space Stone was. If planned properly, it was an achievable feat.

While the three of them were discussing their strategies, the great war outside were already brewing.

*************

Above the sea of trees, two golden and white human figures were fighting each other at high speed. A huge golden light and snowflakes were formed whenever they clashed against each other. Whenever the snowflakes or golden light fall down into the sea of trees, it would either cause a huge fire or ice spreading the entire area.

The forest which was already on fire was put off by the freezing cold air and the whole situation was at a stalemate.

“Hebrew and Beast, bring your men and retreat! Someone else is coming!” The golden man fighting in mid-air at high speed shouted to his back.

Beast, who was standing at the back had blood all over his face and injuries all over his bodies. The majority of his wounds were covered in ice and he looked extremely frightening.

He nodded as he covered his abdomen, shouting at everyone else to retreat.

Then, another muscular man nodded as he brought the rest to retreat.

“It has been so many years Nora, and you still have yet to improve. Not one bit. You disappoint me!” The white human figure in the sky used the Scarlet Snow Technique and hit onto the golden human figure’s shoulder. He then released a huge amount of cold air, condensing the water vapor in the air causing the whole atmosphere to start snowing. He was covered in a pure half transparent layer of Energy Field. It was the indication of a Level Five Powerhouse, who could use their Energy Field for defense.

A loud boom was heard as the golden light and cold air spread about everywhere.

“A pot calling the kettle black eh? You’ve been in the third position for so many years, March!” The man who was called Nora, the leader of the Dragon Eye Sect smirked as he took a few steps back. His body started glowing brightly in gold to the point where no one could open their eyes.

“My junior Mei Tilan is arriving soon. Are you sure you don’t want to leave?” March laughed softly.

“I’m not done fighting yet!” Nora lowered his head as he scanned at his juniors who were heavily injured. His face turned pale upon seeing the situation and scoffed. “Retreat!”

The Dragon Eye Sect used their remaining strength to retreat and left a huge amount of corpse on the battlefield. However upon looking closer, one could see that the corpses were mainly from the Energy Machinist’s followers and Biochemical Beasts. The corpses of the Energy Machinists were mostly Level One and Level Two and there were very little corpses of Level Three Energy Machinists.

Beast had left the battlefield with a group of men. Everyone in the team were practically injured and stricken. Beast himself was emitting chills that could be felt in the bone. It was obvious that he was hit by a Powerhouse with the Scarlet Snow Technique and the effect was still inside him.

Given the emergency circumstances, he had no time to heal himself but to retreat first.

Suddenly, three black figures came out from the trees from the side and intercepted the team…

Chapter 985: Separation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Beast remained calm as he had anticipated an ambush.

“I’ll break them off. Everyone else retreats!”

He growled as multiple green flying snakes which spanned at least one meter long flew out from the side of his body and pounced directly towards the three figures.

“Retreat retreat retreat!!” Someone shouted as a group of men retreated as quickly as they could.

The leader of the three ambushers scoffed and she was surprisingly a girl. The whip that she held with just one of her hands expanded out of the blue and a faint hiss similar to a snake could be heard from the whip as it went towards green flying snakes in the air.

The flying snakes were strangled by the whip and with a gentle motion, they immediately turned into a puddle of blood on the ground. The blood instantly froze and would roll everywhere on the ground like a pebble.

“Energy Machinery Weapon!?” Beast’s expression turned gloomy. “It’s you! Yiling! Are you trying to stop me!!?”

“Stop you? There’s no need for that. I just need to stall you!” Yiling smirked as she immediately went after Beast. Suddenly, a bright golden light and white frozen air appeared around them causing a shockwave around the area which pushed everyone away.

Garen followed behind Joey as they chased after the remainders who were retreating. Before they started the ambushed, Yiling had already warned them that Beast and her were six of one and half a dozen of the other. She could only stall him and would depend on them to deal with the others.

Joey and Garen were ranked top twenty within the Scarlet Snow Sect. As one of the three major sects in the Northern Yu Province, the Scarlet Snow Sect was one of the strongest sects. To be able to rank in the top twenty in the province was considered an elite. Hence, it should be more than enough to massacre these Level Three and Level Four people.

As Garen rushed out, he saw Yiling and Beast fighting against each other from the edge of his vision. He shivered as he felt the residual force field as it was at least equivalent to the strength of the Grade Ten Cold Scarlet Snow. It could be even as powerful as Grade Eleven, which was equivalent to the peak of Level Five, closing to the strength of a Resonance. Furthermore, Yiling and Beast were just Scarlet Snow Sect’s Two Hearted Disciple Level. There were still stronger Energy Machinists from the Three Hearted Disciples. In comparison to a Pilot, the Energy Machinist was clearly much stronger.

Garen moved to the side as he evaded a black bear and two strange-looking blue flying fish that pounced towards him. He immediately rushed forward and crushed a Level Two Energy Machinist’s head as he grabbed onto his head from the side, while kicking two Energy Machinists head with both of his legs, killing them instantly. He then turned around as he attempted to grab hold of the horrified young woman’s back.

“Blink!” The woman took out a yellow flute and blew into it.

Beep… Among the deafening noise, Garen wasn’t able to grab her as the woman in front of him instantly leaped tens of meters away.

“These things again!” He recalled seeing such an escape item back when he was a Pilot in the Blackboard Region.

A blue electric arc then appeared behind him.

He grabbed onto it as it exploded into countless of blue sparks and disappeared.

“Let’s see what kind of escape items you can still use.”

The woman from the Dragon Eye Sect in front of him was a Level Four. Her Willpower was exposed the moment she used the flute. A level Four was definitely the grade of a Two Hearted Disciple, which possessed a hundred points. He could obtain resources from her body as well.

Garen put all of his strength onto his leg as he stomped onto the ground. His body turned into a shadow as he went after the girl who was tens of meters away from him. He had finally decided to use all of his strength to pursue this woman.

“Golden Swallow!”

The woman turned her head around and released a stream of golden light, which turned into a golden swallow heading directly towards Garen’s forehead. As the golden swallow moved towards Garen, the air around it started burning and the surrounding ambient temperature rose drastically to at least a few hundred degrees. The ground and the trees nearby were instantly burnt black.

“Ten Thousand True Technique,” Garen’s pupil shrunk as his body twisted in such an incredible manner that he avoided the Golden Swallow. He then released the chill from his body to cancel off the high temperature released from the Golden Swallow.

After activating the Ten Thousand True Technique, his motions were much agiler as his body turned into the shape of a shuttle, going after the girl at full speed.

“Go to hell!” The woman then threw a black marble, which exploded in the middle of the air. It turned into a black mist, which engulfed Garen who was behind her.

Then black mist immediately exploded as fire rumbled inside. Garen had to stop his pursue due to the explosion, which caused the distance between them to increase.

“What a wealthy fellow!” Garen sensed that this woman was not a typical Energy Machinist. She had so many life-saving items, which far surpassed a typical Level Four Energy Machinist. If not for his current strength which was in the Level Five range, she might have escaped away from his grasp.

“Don’t force me!” The woman turned his head around and shouted at Garen as she realized that Garen was very firm on killing her.

Garen’s expression didn’t change at all as he ran towards the woman. The Eighth Grade Level Four Cold Scarlet Snow Technique had reached its limit. The Scarlet Snow Technique would automatically reach a minimum of Grade Eight once one reached Level Four and its strength increased drastically.

Chills and snow went towards the girl in all direction but it was immediately melted by the high temperature.

“Double Golden Swallow!” The girl’s eyes suddenly brightened up and released two rays of golden light, which turned into two Golden Swallows in the middle of the air as they went after Garen. Two eye-catching golden threads could be seen in the path. It resembled a pair of golden scissors as it tried to cut Garen into half.

“If not for the people coming after me, do you really think I’m afraid of you!?” The woman smirked as she controlled the Golden Swallows towards Garen.

Garen was currently extremely poor. If he were able to kill such an extremely rich Level Four Energy Machinist, it was a win for him in terms of wealth and points. It was worth it even if he was slightly injured!

He pressed on as he felt the threat of the Golden Swallows.

“Cold Radiation!”

A blue radioactive ray immediately released to the surrounding from his body. The chill had reached Level Five as the radiation had mixed with the chill from the Scarlet Snow Technique.

The Level Five chill instantly overwhelmed the Golden Swallow’s scissors and drastically reduced their speed.

Garen took the opportunity to get out from her attacking range and attempted to catch the woman with his hands. The distance between them was no more than five meters.

This distance could be covered instantaneously to an Energy Machinist. All of the Energy Machinist from Planet Naga were all martial artists. As she saw Garen approach her, she was very surprised and she attacked Garen’s shoulders with her fingers without any hesitation. While her speed wasn’t that great, her attacking speed was incredibly fast as afterimages of her hands didn’t even form in the middle of the air. In that instant, her hands reached Garen’s arm and held tightly onto him.

“Ten Thousand True Destruction!” In that instant, Garen released the true strength of the Ten Thousand True technique. His strength and speed in changing his techniques were increased by half in an instant. The true threat of the Ten Thousand True Technique had finally surfaced, which was the ability to change his techniques consecutively.

The most terrifying aspect of the Ten Thousand True Technique was that one could simply change one’s technique’s direction and power in any situation without restraining himself.

After changing his techniques, Garen hit the woman’s abdomen while evading the girl’s attempt to grab onto him.

As the difference between their martial arts was too drastic, the woman wasn’t able to comprehend the situation. Her face immediately turned pale and she wasn’t able to react in time and had no choice but to receive the attack.

Boom!!!

The woman’s body jolted as chills started to spread out across her body.

“Xiao Yu!!” An angry man shouted from the side as Garen suddenly felt a high-temperature airstream approaching him from the left.

Garen was then engulfed inside a ball of red flame.

Garen and the woman were separated as both of them were injured at the same time.

While Garen was under attack, he looked at where the man’s sound came from. What he saw was a man drenched in blood staring back at him. He then carried the seriously wounded woman and escaped. It seemed that he had put all of his strength into that attack as he was barely able to hold the woman firmly.

Garen rolled on the ground and his powerful recovery was able to stabilize the wound. What made Garen terrifying was not his strength but his recovery. As long as he’s not dead, he could recovery and attack as many times as he wanted.

However, there seemed to be a hot invisible force that was holding him in place and it even tried to pull him onto the ground.

Garen looked down to see his legs being held tightly by two arms made from fire. The fires were clashing against the chills and radiation his body was releasing. He could feel throbbing pain in his legs due to the fire.

As he tried to break free from it, the energy field was loosened. Garen then tried to gather energy to pull himself out of the situation once more.

Boom!

The heat aura immediately entered Garen’s body, causing him to vomit a mouthful of blood. His injury had worsened.

He was so close.

It was obvious that the Energy Machinists in front of him was not an ordinary Energy Machinists. If he were able to capture them, he would have obtained a huge sum of wealth, resources and even two hundred points. Garen wasn’t allowed to make any mistake as it was a very special opportunity for him to be able to kill these two. If it were a typical situation, these people would definitely have bodyguards around them and would not come out alone without any good reason.

Garen would rather not fight with these wealthy Energy Machinists if they were in their prime as they were so well prepared that they had a lot of items on them. Furthermore, they even had a huge load of combat experience.

This was especially true to that man, who was able to release an attack of such a caliber even in such a dire state. Garen wasn’t sure if he was able to win that woman in a one on one match if she was in her prime. He wouldn’t be able to have such a golden opportunity where they were seriously injured and running for their lives.

That man and woman were running towards a Flying Ship afar clumsily while Garen was chained down. He needed just a little bit more strength to break away from it.

“Hahaha. Let me give you a hand Garen!” Joey then flew over Garen’s head and rushed towards the two in front of him. Greed could be seen in his eyes. He had already given up with these two as they had a lot of items on them and he wasn’t confident that he could win. He didn’t expect Garen to chase after them and manage to even would chase them off while using up most of their items.

Now that Garen was chained down and the other two was seriously wounded. It was the best opportunity to strike. Even God would have been tempted given such circumstances.

“Joey!!” Garen shouted in anger. “They’re mine!”

“The early bird catches the worm!” Joey ran directly towards them as the chills of the Grade Five Scarlet Snow Technique followed along.

A clear crisp sound was heard as Garen broke away from the chain. He started growling as he ran straight towards them. However, it was too late as the distance between him and Joey were hundreds of meters apart. As an Energy Machinist, he would require at least two seconds to cover that distance. Afterall, maximum speed and acceleration were two different concepts.

Chapter 986: Separation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The man who was carrying the girl turned his head around and despair could be seen in his eyes. Joey hit his head, blood spilled everywhere as his head exploded.

The woman was instantly frozen by him at the same time as fell and rolled on the ground.

Joey took the Space Rings from their fingers and swiftly searched their bodies. He found a few small items and kept them in his pockets before raising his head and looking at Garen who was quickly approaching him.

“You’re too late,” he smirked.

Garen rushed towards the corpses and his face turned gloomy. He had suffered some injuries while pursuing them and didn’t expect Joey to obtain all the good items. It was partially his fault for forgetting to scan his surroundings for any Energy Machinist or else he wouldn’t have let his opponent gain all the loots.

“Fine!” Garen stared at Joey coldly, who knew that Garen needed resources urgently and yet he still took it away from him. Garen’s eyes were filled with a murderous attempt.

He had always been the one who was lawless and rules were nothing but restraint. Whether to abide by these rules or not depended on whether he was strong enough or not.

“What? Are you going to kill me?” Joey noticed Garen’s gaze and started smirking. He was never afraid of killing anyone. “Are you going to blame your incompetence on me?”

Garen scoffed as he turned around and left. He was close to Joey previously because Yiling was even more annoying than him. Frankly speaking, they were just partners for profits. He would hold onto this grudge and make him pay back in the future.

Suddenly, a sharp whistle could be heard behind them. It was Yiling’s signal.

Garen’s eyes gave off a cold vibe as he didn’t want to move with them any longer. His experience wasn’t as rich as them and he wasn’t sure if he would be set up by them. Hence, he rather to move alone.

Determined to do what he wanted to do, he took out a small item from his pocket and crushed it. It was the communication and locator Yiling gave him.

Garen then disappeared into the woods.

At the scene, Joey was the only one left as he crouched down and continued fumbling around the bodies for more resources.

He smiled happily after confirming Garen left the scene.

“Hehe. It’s been a while since I’ve looted from such a wealthy person. With these resources, I can again move to the Grade Ten Level Five Cold Scarlet Snow Technique!”

Joey and Yiling wouldn’t have cooperated with Garen if not for his average strength and the special treatment towards the newcomer. He thought that he could cooperate with Garen for a while more even after obtaining such a wealthy loot. However, he didn’t expect the final battle was just around the corner. Garen was extremely lucky that he had encountered two incredibly wealthy and injured enemies. He couldn’t help himself but to take it away from him.

“Gone already?” He looked at where Garen was standing before. “How stupid of him to move around alone without any experience. He might just die from this action. Same goes for that woman Yiling as well. It would be an extreme advantage if she were able to stall Beast. Even if the powerhouses from the Dragon Eye Sect are all here, we should be fine as long as Lord March is around. We will definitely be able to enter the ranking list when the Spirit Mothership descended. How are you going to enter when you leave now!”

Even if Garen left now, the newcomer special treatment was still applicable to his team so he wasn’t affected at all.

*****************

The Dragon Eye Sect and the Scarlet Snow Sect were fighting with all their forces in the public area. Beast, who was in the top twenty from the Dragon Eye Sect was retreating due to his heavy injury while Nora was pushed back by March. The rest of the Middle and Lower Tier Energy Machinist had perished. The Dragon Eye Sect was seriously impacted as they had lost the majority of their forces in this qualifier match.

The news spread across the whole region, even to a cave deep within the forest.

A few youngsters dressed in black shirts were crouching beside the bonfire as they whispered among each other. One of the tall youngsters had his eyes behind his back as he stood at the entrance of the cave looking out at the herd of birds quietly.

These men’s collar had a silver owl emblem embedded on it.

“Nora of the Dragon Eye Sect has sent us a message. He wants to join forces with us. What should we do brother Wade?” A black-shirted woman walked out from the cave and asked the youngster.

“Nora? He’s ranked third in the Dragon Eye Sect. March is also ranked third in the Scarlet Snow Sect. He still hasn’t improved all these years and the Scarlet Snow Sect seems to be very strong this time around,” the youngster turned his head around and one could see that he had two diamond shaped silver metal on his cheeks, giving off a strange and mysterious vibe.

“The Scarlet Snow and Dragon Eye have been fighting for thousands of years and we the Nine Xiao Sect has no obligation to join in this mess. We should be fine as long as we remain neutral. Nothing else is more important than to be enlisted by the Spirit Mothership.”

“Wade is right. These two sects are wasting the numbers in the enlistment from the Spirit Mothership during this major war,” the other muscular man laughed.

“Although Nora is weaker, he is very intellectual and isn’t that dumb. I fear that the Dragon Eye Sect has obtained some treasure and is found out by the Scarlet Snow Sect, causing them to fight against each other,” the black-shirted woman said softly as she shook her head. “Although the Dragon Eye Sect isn’t as united as us Nine Xiao, they are still much better than the Scarlet Snow. Within the three major sects in the Northern Yu Province, The Scarlet Snow Sect is the craziest and even their internal competition is insane as there is a huge amount of within them during their annual internal sparring. They are definitely at the top in terms of cruelty.”

“What should we do then? The Dragon Eye Sect is currently at a serious loss as most of their newcomers are already dead excluding their powerhouses. Should we…” The thin man started laughing in an evil manner.

“There’s no need for that. Let them fight it out. Our objective is to be acknowledged by Spirit Card from the Mothership. As long as we are acknowledged, we just have to train ourselves for the next fifteen years and we’re guaranteed to be able to achieve Resonance Level. We should try and ignore these battles at the moment,” Wade said coldly.

“Yes brother,” the crowd agreed.

****************

Garen was moving swiftly inside the forest. It had been five days since the major battle between the Dragon Eye Sect and Scarlet Snow Sect. He kept loitering around the area hoping to find some Energy Machinist to kill. Unfortunately, other than encountering a small group of four, the rest were at least middle-sized teams of at least ten people. Among these people, there were at least one Level Three and Level Four Energy Machinists. They’re considered a formidable force considering they have the number and experience.

Garen hadn’t attacked anyone as he knew that he might not be able to win against a few Low-Level Energy Machinists. Afterall, he had to use all of his might just to fight against a Level Four Energy Machinist.

The people from the Dragon Eye Sect seemed to have suffered a few ambushes as each and every one of them were on high alert. He wasn’t able to ambush them at all.

Garen’s ambush capability wasn’t that great and considered normal to an Energy Machinist. They had too many techniques in surveying their surrounding that Garen had never seen before. However, his ambushing capability was considered incredible for a normal commoner.

He had failed numerous attempt in ambushing others and in fact he was almost ambushed back instead. Garen had given up the idea of hunting alone and decided to hide in a path while waiting for the opportunity to attack others.

With him as the epicenter, he had placed countless of miniaturized eavesdropper a few kilometers away from him. After covering these items with his Willpower, they wouldn’t be detected by the electrical instrument easily.

However, as waves of Energy Machinists passed by, most of his eavesdropper were destroyed. There were only a few left that survived as the Energy Machinists were too ignorant to detect them.

Garen squatted on a tree branch as he quietly adjusted the earphone’s frequency to each of the eavesdropper frequency.

Soon he overheard a small team’s conversation which caught his attention.

“…Where did they go?”

“The Mothership’s location. He wanted us to hide as much as possible and not make any rash moves.”

“We have big sister with us. As long as we follow Lord Nora, we should be fine. I wonder how much resources can Nora get hold of.”

“The three major sects have teamed up so let’s not overthink it. It’s considered a good outcome if we can secure half of it. The Spirit Mothership doesn’t care who you are. If it isn’t for the elders from the three major sects to reach a truce, we are considered lucky to come out alive, even without the resources.”

“How savage is this weird race?” Another tender voice appeared.

“There’s nothing we can do about it. They’re merchants who are able to move all the resources and not someone we local sects can deal with. We can only comply with their requirement and do nothing about it,” the former voice said helplessly.

The team left the area as he heard thus far.

“The Spirit Mothership?” Garen frowned. He had heard of this organization where it was created by a minority species which were not human. They had a huge ship which they used to test the strength of the disciples from all sects in return for resources.

They had always been friendly towards the humans and would greatly nurture the most talented people. They had a very long history and were very sociable. Hence, a lot of powerful humans were blessed by them and were even protected by them.

These species were very business minded, had a great eye for people and were very good at gathering people through networking as well. In addition to that, their origin was still a mystery.

Garen didn’t expect the Spirit Mothership to land at this moment. No wonder the three major sects from the Northern Yu Province would organize a qualifier match at this period of time. It was just for this reason as well. The ranking list given by the Spirit Mothership would definitely be fair and the sects would use the Spirit Mothership to discover any hidden talents from their own sect as well. This might be the best plan the three major sects had come up with.

Garen instantly connected all the dots but he didn’t even hear of such a news at all. The Spirit Mothership only stopped for a moment and the Energy Machinist who would first receive such intel would definitely be at least a Level Four. It would be natural for Bainster and his other intel collector to not receive such a news.

However, Yiling and Joey definitely knew about it and they didn’t even bother telling him at all. It was obvious that they had no plan on working alongside with him at all. These two had incredible strength and in addition to that, the Scarlet Snow Sect’s members were all extremely cruel. The sect itself was very similar to Blackboard Region as they would use all sorts of techniques to compete with each other.

Garen understood their action and would find it weird if they told him instead. If not for the newcomer special treatment, they wouldn’t even have brought him along. Afterall, Garen was slightly weaker than them.

Garen felt that he had about seventy percent winning rate against Joey.

He couldn’t find a suitable target in the wild.

“Looks like I have no choice but to go have a look at the Spirit Mothership,” Garen shivered as it was a place for one to exchange quality for resources. Rumor had it that half of the resources obtained would be given to the invigilators. However, even so it would be more than enough for everyone to breakthrough. This region was extremely fair to every Energy Machinist. As long as one had enough quality and potential, they would be invested by the Spirit Mothership.

If Garen wanted to stabilize himself in this world and even obtain Level Five resources in this world quickly, this might be the only place for him to achieve it.